Chapter 728: Enchantment and Leaving Tutelage

Despite a Psychic toxin sounding pretty severe, Han Xiao was not too flustered and only found it pretty troublesome. He had always believed that there would be more solutions than problems.

"Even you can’t clean up the toxin?" Han Xiao asked Lagi.

"I can engrave a soul defense rune formation on your body at the very most to slow down the speed at which the toxin invades your soul." Lagi sighed. "However, these methods won’t be able to treat you. It was indeed a mistake for me to become a Mage."

Feidin then interrupted him and said, "I can also help you strengthen your soul’s defense to defend against the Psychic toxin. As for purging it entirely, this is something that neither of us are unable to achieve. You have to think of another method."

Feidin was the most talented individual in the army, and he had entered the Calamity Grade even before Sylvia. However, his status in the army was more like a guest, and he did not have any responsibilities.

"Then help me suppress the toxin for now. I will think of another way."

Han Xiao felt slightly relieved. Things were fine as long as they were not totally helpless.

Despite a Beyond Grade A Psychic being extremely powerful, a Calamity Grade Super would also be able to defend against it to a certain extent.

Feidin’s body began glowing brightly, and an endless stream of psychic energy rushed out from his body like a tidal wave and enveloped Han Xiao’s mental world. A hexagonal structure then appeared on Han Xiao’s mental wall to strengthen its defense.

Very quickly, the effect of the Psychic toxin was obviously reduced, and the purplish fog also seemed to have become less aggressive.

Han Xiao instantly felt energized, and the feeling of weakness and disturbance was reduced greatly. (Poisoned Soul] only reduced fourteen percent of his attributes from the original twenty percent, and the effects of (Mild Hallucination) and (Sensory Misdirection) had also been reduced.

"I will have to inscribe the rune formation on your body. Let’s exit." Lagi’s mental body then left the chatroom in Han Xiao’s mind.

Han Xiao and Feidin also retracted their mental bodies, and their senses returned to the outside world. Han Xiao felt the scene before his eyes changing, and he was back in the cultivation chamber of the spaceship. Feidin also retracted his finger and walked to the side.

Lagi walked forward, and with a flip of his palm, a small jade green crystal staff appeared in his hand.

Waving the staff, ten or so thick spell books appeared in front of him and began flipping themselves automatically. As the pages were flipped, pages full of magical incantations fell off automatically and hovered around Lagi. These were the formations that Lagi was preparing to inscribe on Han Xiao.

"Take off your top. I will inscribe a formation on your body."

Han Xiao took off his top and revealed his muscular upper body. His muscles were packed tightly, and despite being packed full with power, they were extremely lean, not bulky like a Pugilist. The (Golden Ratio Body] talent that he had transformed his body into a work of art.

"Go ahead." Han Xiao nodded.

Lagi circulated his magic, and his eyes glowed brightly. With his staff as a brush and magic as paint, he began to draw a formation on Han Xiao’s body.

The cool magic energy lingered around his body with a tinge of pain and itchiness. It felt just like getting a tattoo.

After ten or so minutes, Lagi let out a long breath and spat out a mouthful of magic breath. At the same time, the glow in his eyes receded as well. For a mage of his caliber to spend a full ten or so minutes inscribing an enchantment, it could be said that he was giving it his all.

Lagi then took a few steps back and studied Han Xiao’s back as he said, "Although I don’t know if it will work… my drawing is truly nice."

Han Xiao lowered his head to take a look. At this moment, his entire body was filled with exquisite and complicated runes that looked like tattoos.

A bluish-gold circular formation could be seen on the left of his chest, and a horoscope-like shape could be seen on his abdomen. The two formations were connected by a chain-like inscription that covered his entire arms as though they were wrapped up in chains. His back was also covered with runes, with his backbone as a tree trunk and countless branch-like formations extending out from his backbone.

Apart from his face, Han Xiao was covered in runes all over his body that flickered with a dim glow as though the runes were breathing.

"With your body as the foundation, I inscribed plenty of formations on your body through body enchantments. The formations will automatically absorb the elements that exist in nature to replenish themselves."

Body enchantment was an important skill in the enchantment path. It could strengthen certain aspects of the target, and some magical civilizations would use this method to strengthen the combat capabilities of their soldiers. There were some powerhouses who would also inscribe enchantments on their own bodies. Han Xiao was not a stranger to these enchantments, and there were mages from his previous life who specialized in providing such enchantment services.

This was the way a mage could earn money, just like how a Mechanic sold their products.

Han Xiao stroked his arm curiously, and his finger could clearly feel the inscription lines of the rune. Even with his experience, he could clearly feel that the enchantment on his body was extremely complicated.

"The level of enchantment is limited by the strength of your body. The more enchantments, the greater the burden on your body. Thankfully, your body is extremely powerful, and I was able to inscribe plenty of enchantments."

Lagi then said with assurance, "The protection of the Sacred Emperor, hug of the white robed mage ancestor, five different soul protection formations, the thirteen rings of secret soul stabilizing formation, and so on."

"The effects are pretty good. I feel much more comfortable."

The various hallucinations were being suppressed, and Han Xiao’s head was much clearer than before. Looking at the interface, the various negative statuses were weakened once again, and the negative effects of (Poisoned Soul] was reduced to a mere five percent.

On his interface, the effect of these various enchantments was displayed with the majority of them having the effect of increasing his Psychological Resistance. Because of an increase in the base attribute, the boost from his (Advanced Psychological Resistance) talent also increased.

"Right, I also inscribed a mental exploration formation for you." Lagi pointed at a small formation on Han Xiao’s chest. "As long as you gather your attention on this formation, you will be able to enter your own mental world without our aid. You can use this ability to observe the situation of the Psychic toxin."

"This is practical." Han Xiao was overjoyed. A Mechanic did not have any mental abilities, and he was not able to observe his mental world on his own. He could not possibly get their help all the time. With this enchantment, he would be able to enter his own mental world anytime he wanted.

He tested the formation, and his mental body immediately entered his mental world.

At this moment, there were many barriers around the Psychic toxin, and the region of the toxin was reduced to six percent from the previous ten percent.

"These measures are only capable of suppressing the toxin, but if I want to purge it completely, I still need the help of a Beyond Grade A Super…"

There was no need to mention Psyker. Han Xiao did not even know if Psyker was an enemy or neutral party. Furthermore, he did not have any relationship with Psyker, and Han Xiao was not prepared to find him. It would be much more convenient for him to find Austin instead. While Austin was a mage, there were similarities between the Mage class and the Psychic class.

Han Xiao then left his mental world and took out his communicator. After thinking for a while, he put on his clothes and contacted Austin.

"Black Star?" The child-like Austin appeared in the holographic projection. "It has been a few years since you last contacted me. Why are you looking for me?"

"Your Excellency Magus, I hope to receive your help…"

Han Xiao explained what had happened.

"You were actually struck by Psyker’s Psychic attack? You are truly unlucky." Austin laughed. "Alright, come and find me. I haven’t seen Psyker for a long time. Let me see if he has improved."

Among the four Beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring, Heber was tyrannical, Ames was willful, Psyker was arrogant, and only Austin was friendly. Upon hearing that Han Xiao needed his help, he agreed without much hesitation.

After hanging up, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief before turning to look at Lagi. "Do you want to follow me to Austin’s territory?"

Lagi shook his head. Since he had left, he was not planning to return.

"Alright then. You can remain in the Black Star Army and work together with Herlous and Sylvia to tie up any loose ends after the battle. I will be leaving for a short while," Han Xiao said solemnly. "Only you two know of my condition in the army. Don’t let anyone know."

Even Jorde did not know the exact effect of the toxin, and Han Xiao was prepared to seal all news about it. He did not want to expose his temporary weakness.

"Feidin, follow me for now," Han Xiao said.

With Feidin beside him, he would be able to enjoy Feidin’s Luck Glow, and the moment any changes happened to the toxin, Feidin would be able to help him to a certain extent. Most importantly, his energy would become fertilizer for the toxin if he went into battle, and he needed to keep some fighters beside him. Feidin was currently a Grade A Psychic, and his combat capability was reliable.

"I will naturally be beside you since you are in trouble." Feidin smiled warmly, and his entire face seemed to be radiating light.

My goodness, please don’t unleash your charisma already… Han Xiao felt his head ache.

After the battle was over, Section Zero left some forces to guard the borders of the Kant Star System and build up a defensive line to prevent the Bloodshed Land from making a comeback.

The one million players who joined the battle returned full of rewards. Meanwhile, Han Xiao took Feidin and another bodyguard, Marian, and left the main force for Hidden Red Robe Abbey.

Han Xiao would be able to give out missions from the faction interface even from afar. All his products were already placed in the faction store, and Han Xiao did not need to follow beside the players all the time.

The players returned with their bags full of rewards this time, and with the fifty-percent discount still active in the faction store, Han Xiao was not afraid that no one would shop in the faction store. Thus, there was no need for Han Xiao to worry about that for now. Furthermore, after this battle, there would not be another large-scale battle like this in the near future. He had more than enough free time to take care of the psychic toxin.

The Hidden Red Robe Abbey was located in a different Star Cluster, and the journey would take a long time.

At the same time, on Planet Heber, the command team calculated the losses from the battle, and Jorde listened to the reports from his subordinates. Despite the losses being significant, Jorde still had a smile on his face and was not frustrated in the least.

Since Section Zero had sent all their forces, it was only normal for them to be chased out. However, their greatest harvest from this battle was succeeding in their sneak attack on Black Star. Jorde was extremely satisfied about this.

Black Star was only a single individual but could single handedly suppress all the high-level combatants on their side. Over the past ten years, Bloodshed Land had lost more than a hundred Calamity Grade Supers by Black Star’s hands. Even if they had the talents of an entire Star Cluster backing them, this was not a small amount.

Heber’s heart was as hard as steel, and he did not care about the losses that his forces had suffered. However, Jorde could not remain indifferent. He was an extremely meticulous butler and felt his heart ache over the loss of high-level combatants. If not for Heber wanting to rear a pig, Jorde definitely would not have allowed Han Xiao to do as he wished in the battlefield for so long.

He had made use of so many different methods but still failed to kill Black Star. Even if Black Star fell for his trap, Jorde felt as though he still could not threaten Black Star’s life. Thus, Jorde was not prepared to send out more assassins but chose to leave Black Star to His Excellency Tyrant instead.

Jorde was in an extremely good mood that day. He was extremely satisfied with the outcome of weakening Black Star.

Although he did not know what kind of injury Black Star had suffered, Jorde prayed for the best outcome, that Black Star would not be able to participate in the war anymore.

Without Black Star, the high-level combatants of their Bloodshed Land could go all out.

In some Star System within the Colton Star Cluster, Floating Dragon Island was drifting in the galaxy.

Compared to seven years prior, Floating Dragon Island had experienced a huge change. There were now three floating islands, one large and two small.

The largest island was the original floating island, which was now the main island. The other two smaller islands revolved around the main island like two small satellites. These were two new subsidiary islands where the Floating Dragon armed forces were located.

With the support of the Black Star Army, Vilna had only taken seven years to grow Floating Dragon’s second field team to a pretty sizable scale. Even the port of the main island was not able to fit the entire armed force. As such, both subsidiary islands were army camps for the new armed force. The two islands had been created by Ames’ force field.

Seven years of development had given Floating Dragon a new look.

At this moment, Ames, Aesop, Vilna, and Jenny were gathered at the Floating Dragon dock. All the famous individuals on Floating Dragon Island were present.

A small reddish spaceship was parked at the dock, and both Hila and Aurora were carrying on to their suitcases.

Both of their personalities remained the same, but they were much more mature than seven years prior. They were dressed in Battle Suits of different designs and colors. Hila’s outfit was red and black in color while Aurora’s outfit was white with golden rims.

"Are you really not going to consider staying behind to help me?" Vilna asked with a look of regret.

The date for the Black Star Army’s departure grew nearer and nearer, and Vilna’s second armed force was one that belonged solely to Floating Dragon. She was the commander of the fleet with plenty of elites and experts under her.

She had been working for Floating Dragon for a full seven years and had a close relationship with the officers of Floating Dragon. She was especially close to both Aurora and Hila.

It was the day for Hila and Aurora to leave Floating Dragon. They had followed the Dragon Emperor for more than ten years, and it was time for them to leave their teacher’s tutelage.

Vilna had pleaded for the sisters to stay behind on more than one occasion to become her leftand right-hand officers. However, it was a pity that the two were determined to leave.

"I am sorry, Sister Vilna. We promised Uncle Black Star that we would go and find him." Aurora had an apologetic look on her face.

Vilna let out a sigh. The Black Star Army had helped her out a lot, and the sisters had a close relationship with Black Star. She would also be embarrassed to poach them from Black Star.

Jenny then said coldly, "I have deposited 200,000 Enas into your accounts, which will be sufficient for your journey. Black Star is a wealthy individual, and there won’t be a need for me to give you any more money after you join him."

"Thank you, Sister Jenny," Aurora said politely.

"Humph." Jenny turned around without saying anything else. She was extremely depressed that both of them were so insistent on joining the Black Star Army.

Wilsander then chuckled and said, "Remember to say hello to Black Star for me when you see him."

"Alright." Aurora nodded.

"Right, help me say hi, too." The Logistics Manager Haier, who was used to being a transparent bug, also spoke up.

"Alright." Aurora shrank back slightly. Even after knowing each other for more than ten years, Haier’s ferocious appearance still scared her slightly.

Aesop then shook his head and said, "I looked into both of your futures, and I don’t know if it is a good or bad thing for both of you to follow Black Star."

Aurora blinked and said, "Destiny is never fixed and will change anytime. This is something that you have told us."

Aesop let out a long sigh while muttering words like ‘Black Star’, ‘death’, and ‘war’ under his breath.

Finally, both of their gazes landed on Ames.

Ames smiled and said softly, "Be careful."

Aurora smiled sweetly and replied, "Okay, Teacher."

Even the emotionless Hila revealed a look of respect and gave a deep bow. "Thank you for your teachings over the past ten years."

A doting look could be seen in Ames’ eyes, and she nodded without saying anything else.

Hila then straightened her back and looked at her comrades and friends over the past ten years. She then pulled Aurora along with her and boarded the dark red spaceship.

The spaceship then floated up into the air and disappeared into the stars under the gazes of Ames and the others.

Ames placed her arms behind her back and softly muttered, "So, this is the feeling of being a teacher."

Aesop’s ear twitched slightly, and he tiptoed away like a thief.

Chapter 729: Wanted

In the Black Star Army headquarters, the fleet returned victorious. The players received tons of rewards, and most of them were looking forward to spending them.

This large-scale operation had made quite an impact among the players. It was the first large-scale war for the players in the army in Version 3.0. After this battle, most players had gotten used to Version 3.0 and figured out the goal of the main storyline and the current situation of the galaxy.

There were countless discussions about this war on the forums. The Black Star Army’s first galactic war after the ten years period was rather commemorative, and it was recorded in the Galaxy Chronicles.

"Galaxy Calendar Year 704, August 4th, the Black Star Army and Section Zero attacked the Bloodshed Land troops in the Kant Star System and returned with an overwhelming victory."

The Galaxy Chronicles consisted of important events that every player took part in writing; it recorded what countless players had witnessed and formed the storyline of the various areas in Galaxy.

Although it was now just Version 3.0, the Galaxy Chronicles had already recorded a lot of information, categorized by Star Field, organization, and characters.

As for the Shattered Star Ring area, the Black Star Army was the organization and storyline that the players were most familiar with. Han Xiao and the army had their own categories. The players recorded the stages of the Black Star Army’s development according to time, even including the various things that happened during the ten years of the update. It was extremely detailed.

A spaceship left the dock of the Black Star Army headquarters; the hundred or so people on the spaceship were players heading to Klent. They had contacted each other on the forums and decided to leave together. Hate the Heavens and his friends were on-board. They had just enjoyed the last benefits of the Black Star Army and spent most of what they had received in the war.

"After spending so long in the Black Star Army, I have to say, I do feel kind of sad for leaving."

At the corner of the cabin, Hate the Heavens felt down for some strange reason while browsing through the Black Star Army records in the Chronicles. He turned around and looked out the porthole as the enormous Black Star Army headquarters became ever smaller in his eyes.

The players had witnessed the Black Star Army’s growth ever since Version 1.0. They were responsible for how much the Black Star Army had grown. The Chronicles recorded the memories of these players fighting together, and Hate the Heavens felt reluctant.

Hate the Heavens looked at the people around him. Most of the players on the spaceship were gamblers—they did not change faction to experience never experienced before storylines but to be a step ahead of others in grabbing the possible hidden benefits of joining Klent. Hence, they were not as sentimental as someone like him who did it for the storyline.

"Don’t overthink it. My judgment won’t be wrong." A person saw that Hate the Heavens looked nervous and patted his shoulder.

Hate the Heavens turned to him; the ID above this person’s head was ‘Summer Night Flower’.

Summer Night Flower was the initiator of this team. He trusted himself, so he was going to change factions as well. He had contacted these players who intended to join Klent and invited them to move together. As he was the one that had come up with the analysis, which suggested that Klent would be more beneficial, the players on the spaceship saw him as their leader somewhat.

"I’m not nervous." Hate the Heavens shook his head.

Summer Night Flower smiled. He then clapped and attracted the eyes of all the players on the ship. "The target of this trip is the West Wind Star System. The Bloodshed Land has many strongholds there, and their forces are the steadiest in that area. They are currently recruiting on a large scale. This is our chance to join Klent. Only then will our main storyline mission become the Klent faction’s."

The others replied disorderly.

"Trust me, guys, you won’t regret this."

Summer Night Flower smiled as he looked at the hundred or so players in front of him. He was excited; he felt like he was a pioneer.

After several stops and galactic flight changes, they finally arrived in the West Wind Star System after traveling a long distance. They went to the recruitment office and handed over their documents. They then followed the officers onto the ship to head toward a stronghold.

The Bloodshed Land was recruiting locally. With the Tyrant and Klent’s name, there would always be people who were willing to join. Galactic residents were very free, especially in border areas like the West Wind Star System, where there were many foreigners who were not loyal to the Purple Crystal Civilization.

On the spaceship, about a thousand galactic warriors lined up neatly to accept the inspection of the officer. Summer Night Flower and the other players were among them.

The officer browsed through the resumes of the warriors one after another. Suddenly, he stopped before Summer Night Flower, frowned, and said with shock, "You guys are from the Black Star Army? Why join us?"

Summer Night Flower thought about it and answered, "We hope to develop ourselves in the Bloodshed Land better."

"Oh, you’ve made the right choice." Despite saying so, a tint of derision flashed within the officer’s eyes.

The members of the Bloodshed Land were mostly tough people, and this officer was no exception. He had always looked down on people who joined the enemy because of mere profits.

"Okay, you’re now a member of the Bloodshed Land. Missions will be given to you guys once you arrive at the stronghold."

The officer then walked away. He felt that he needed to report this to his higher-ups.

Summer Night Flower clenched his fists in excitement and softly said, "See that? I was right; the identity of being a member of the Black Star Army will give us special treatment from Klent. The earlier we join Klent, the more important we will be to them."

The other players saw that this was a good start and were all joyous.

At this time, a notification popped up on the interfaces of these people.

You have activated a new faction-Bloodshed Land. Current Relationship: Indifferent (0/300)

You have activated a new faction-Klent Kingdom. Current Relationship: Indifferent (0/300)

Summer Night Flower and the others were just about to feel cheerful when more notifications came, stunning them.

Your Grade S Main Storyline Mission (Secret War: Section Zero] has failed. You have received a new mission (Secret War: Bloodshed Land). Accumulated Mission Rating has been reset.

You have joined the opposing faction of the Purple Crystal Civilization.

Relationship with the Purple Crystal Civilization is now (Hostile).

Some of the Colton Star Cluster Star System civilization Relationships have been reset to zero and are now (Indifferent).

You have joined the opposing faction of Section Zero.

Relationship with Section Zero is now [Hostile).

You have joined the opposing faction of the Black Star Army.

Relationship with the Black Star Army is now [Hostile).

You have lost the identity as a Black Star Army member. Faction interface and faction store are shut down. You will no longer receive services from the Black Star Army.

Relationship with the Black Star Army characters has been reset to zero. Contribution Points have been reset to zero.

Summer Night Flower and the others were stunned. Although they did guess that they would lose many things when switching factions, they still felt quite heartbroken when it actually happened.

Suddenly, everyone’s communicator rang. Phillip’s sub-program jumped out. His original cute and child-like voice became cold and robotic.

"You have betrayed the Black Star Army and decided to join the enemy. You will no longer receive services from the Black Star Army in any form. This program will automatically uninstall… Uninstallation complete, hum…"

The next second, the sub-program of Phillip disappeared. It looked like it had uninstalled, but it was actually hidden for background monitoring purposes.

Something like this would not happen if they had just joined a neutral faction. However, joining the enemy meant betraying their former faction, so it was inevitable they would be punished and lose the Favorability of their original faction, thus becoming enemies.

Summer Night Flower felt heartache. Suddenly, he felt the furious looks of the players around him and was forced to the corner.

"You have to give us an explanation!"

Such a colossal loss hurt their weak nerves. They had built up those faction Relationship Points and Favorability through the course of two entire versions, but now they were all completely gone. The hundred or so players were furious.

"Let me explain!" Summer Night Flower said hastily. "I said this long ago. There will definitely be risks in changing factions. The benefits of Klent are more long term. There’s a higher chance of winning the secret war, and there are fewer people to fight for resources with. Most importantly, there is a chance to be affiliated with a Universal Civilization. These are all future potentials. We have to give up the short-term benefits in exchange for long term profits. This is an investment! An investment! Do you get it?"

The others were indeed there because of the future potential of Klent; it was just that the tremendous loss made them lose their senses. After hearing Summer Night Flower’s explanation, they calmed down a little.

Summer Night Flower smiled and said, "Guys, don’t panic. The damage of losing the Favorability of the various factions in Colton is actually not that huge. This is because we will be developing in Klent’s territory in the future, where there’s less competition and more resources. Even though we must start climbing up from the bottom, there will be more benefits in the future. Just wait and see, there will be more people joining Klent because of the Universal Civilization sooner or later, and we will be one step ahead."

The other players had different looks on their faces. These people only wanted to make profits, not losses, but since they were already there, there was no way of turning back. They could only trust Summer Night Flower and keep walking down this path.

Seeing that everyone had calmed down, Summer Night Flower breathed a sigh of relief.

Among the players, Hate the Heavens was the calmest. His goal was to experience a different storyline, so he could totally accept the losses. Seeing that the gamblers around him were so anxious, he thought that it was quite funny.

At the same time, Summer Night Flower and the others did not know that the moment they betrayed the Black Star Army, a new mission was suddenly pinned at the top of the mission list of the army. It was a wanted notice for Summer Night Flower and the rest.

Bounty Mission: (Army Wanted Order]

Mission Introduction: The Black Star Army shows no mercy for traitors. All members will receive a reward for killing the traitors.

Mission Requirements: Kill or capture the traitor alive.

Reward: Based on the target’s strength.

This is a Repeatable Mission.

The players were not the only ones that received this; the hundred million Black Star Army members could all accept this task.

Issuing a bounty was a definite outcome; this was the standard procedure for how most organizations dealt with traitors. Although the players were important to Han Xiao and he gave them enough freedom and benefits, he was certainly not going to miss out on the necessary punishments. Otherwise, his faction would be a joke where the players could join the enemies whenever they wanted.

If the army did not draw a distinguishable line, he would be the one to suffer losses in the end, which would be even more troublesome.

"Someone betrayed the Black Star Army?"

"It’s actually a group of players? I thought they were NPCs."

"Summer Night Flower? Isn’t this the guy that said the Klent faction is better? So, he’s making an example of himself? Not bad."

"This means that these players have joined the opposing faction and will become red names, so will we be rewarded every time we kill them?"

The players in the army were thrilled. It had been a very long time since there were players in the opposing faction; the earliest ones were those unlucky people that joined the Germinal Organization in Version 1.0. After so long, there were finally players who they could PVP in the open.

If the traitors were NPCs, they would be gone after being killed once, but if they were players, they could kill them as many times as they wanted. It was a reusable resource!

On the other side, shortly after Summer Night Flower and the rest calmed down, their friends contacted them privately.

"What? We’re all wanted"

Summer Night Flower’s mouth opened wide with shock.

Doesn’t that mean that the millions of players and hundreds of millions of NPCs of the Black Star Army will all be chasing after us?

This was a much more severe consequence than he had expected!

Summer Night Flower gulped uncomfortably. He suddenly felt a sharp sense of coldness from behind him. He turned stiffly like a robot and saw the enraged looks of the hundred players.

"I–I can still explain…"

Summer Night Flower forced a smile. After a thorough explanation and convincing, he finally put out the flames of rage of the people around him.

Such a severe consequence was something that he did not expect. Summer Night Flower carefully observed the faces of the others still lingering with anger and was scared.

If he had guessed wrong, the people of the army would not even have to chase him; these people beside him would all be waiting at his revive point to kill him countless times over and over again.

In a certain Star System in the Colton Star Cluster, four spaceships surrounded a dark red spaceship. Energy chains and beams locked the dark red spaceship in its place.

The leader of this group of small galactic pirates stared at his prey through the porthole; greed appeared on his malnourished face. The galactic pirate subordinates behind him were also delighted

Due to the rise of the Black Star Army, the lives of the galactic pirates in the Colton Star Cluster had become much worse. The name of Black Star struck fear into the hearts of even the big galactic pirates. A small galactic pirate group like them could only act in an extremely low-profile manner, like mice.

Finally, they met a lone spaceship, and they quickly came to rob it.

"I found it. This is a Crimson Coated Grade spaceship. It’s very expensive!" A subordinate found the model of the dark red spaceship online and was overjoyed.

The galactic pirate leader clenched his fists in excitement. Intending to seize this dark red spaceship, he hastily threatened them through the communication channel. "Don’t run away, and don’t fight back, or we will destroy your spaceship!"

It seemed like the people inside the dark red spaceship were scared. The spaceship stayed stationary and did not show any signs of fighting back. The galactic pirate leader felt relieved. He controlled the spaceship and slowly moved closer. Mechanical arms extended out of his spaceship and were about to connect with the dark red spaceship.

At this time, a high energy reaction suddenly exploded from this dark red spaceship. A red energy wave expanded in a sphere and passed through the four other spaceships in the blink of an eye, penetrating them like they had no physical form.

The smiles of the galactic pirate leader and his subordinates were fixed on their faces.

Flop, flop!

The next moment, all the galactic pirates on the four spaceships collapsed. The smiles were still on their faces, but their eyes had lost their color. Their minds were shattered in an instant, and they became corpses.

Gray shadows were dragged out of the corpses by an invisible force, turning into a rolling cluster of fog and flying toward the dark red spaceship, gathering on a white palm.

With no expression on her face, Hila absorbed that soul energy. Her Esper ability became stronger by a negligible amount.

She could absorb the remaining mind energy of dead beings to strengthen her own Esper ability. She did not have an opportunity to do so on Floating Dragon, but now that she had entered the galaxy after finally becoming Grade A through intense training, she would have plenty of opportunities to kill people. Hence, she discovered this method of becoming stronger.

In terms of growth potential, Hila was not below the average player.

However, she would not be so mad about becoming stronger and slaughter planets for it like in Han Xiao’s previous life.

"Sis, what should we do with these four spaceships?" Aurora asked while controlling the spaceship.

On Floating Dragon Island, other than training her Esper ability, Aurora had also gained other knowledge and knew how to operate a spaceship.

"Bring them along. Maybe Han Xiao will want to modify them."

Hila was not very interested in the loot. She reflected on the battle. Since she had always been training with Ames, she did not know how strong she was exactly.

I seem to be… quite strong?

After a long trip, Han Xiao and the other two finally arrived at Austin’s Hidden Red Robe Abbey after more than half a month.

Chapter 730: Universal Treasure

As a famous Beyond Grade A organization, the location of Hidden Red Robe Abbey was known to the public. It was located in the Gelock Star Cluster and was also known as the Palace of Hidden Spells.

Palace of Hidden Spells was a large palace that floated in the universe, and this palace was Austin’s Mage Pagoda. It was used as the base of Hidden Red Robe Abbey.

The Mage Pagoda was important equipment for a mage, and it was both useful in combat and for research purposes. As the Mage Pagoda of a Beyond Grade A Mage, it was said that the Secret Law Temple had 48,000 different formations. It had a perfect attack, defense, movement, and life support systems. Furthermore, it had projections in a few hundred secondary dimensions and was able to leave the universe and enter those dimensions at any time.

If it was classified into a grade, the grade of Austin’s Palace of Hidden Spells would exceed that of orange equipment and would be at the level of a ‘Universal Treasure’. It was the equipment of the highest grade, the gold grade.

The spaceship approached the Palace of Hidden Spells, and the trio looked out of the window and admired the gigantic palace from afar.

The Palace of Hidden Spells was majestic and luxurious with essence gold and dense silver as its foundation. It was decorated with colorful magical crystals all around and looked like a dream-like castle in the universe. The palace could be broken down into many different layers with plenty of subsidiary pagodas all around. A magical glow enveloped the entire palace and covered it with five colored gas. Numerous energy source formations were inscribed all around the protective shield of the palace to absorb a portion of the dark energy from the universe to replenish the consumption of the various formations.

"How majestic," Feidin said with admiration.

"How luxurious," Marian said with reverence.

"How rich," Han Xiao said with envy. He truly saw things differently from others.

If those from the Mechanic class were like merchants, then those from the Mage class were like local tyrants. Especially a Mage of Austin’s caliber. The thickness of his wallet was something that even Han Xiao could not help but feel envious about.

Han Xiao then sought permission from the Palace of Hidden Spells to land, and after receiving permission, he piloted the spaceship toward the dock.

At this moment, the dock was filled with many different models of spaceships that came from different Star Systems. They were all there to seek apprenticeships. The Palace of Hidden Spells had always been open to the outside world, and countless mages chose to research magic in this place. If one threw a random brick out over there, at least two mages would end up being hit for sure.

Hidden Red Robe Abbey was a neutral mage organization. Austin did not work together with any Star Cluster civilizations and did not attempt to expand his armed force either. He allowed the majority of mages to enter Hidden Red Robe Abbey to cultivate and shared knowledge with them. As long as one raised their membership level, one would be able to gain access to knowledge that was of a higher grade. The organizational structure was extremely loose, and their number of members was certainly greater than that of Bloodshed Land. However, only the Forbidden Sorcerers and a few other armed forces were considered Austin’s direct subordinates.

According to Han Xiao’s understanding, Hidden Red Robe Abbey was like a private mage school, and Austin was the principal. His direct subordinates were the lecturers, and the various armed forces under him was like the security detail of the school.

The trio stepped onto the dock, and there were already people waiting for them. The one waiting for them was Desoro, who had previously appeared to bring Lagi back.

"It’s been more than ten years. You haven’t increased your rank?" Han Xiao remembered him and began to joke.

"You must be joking. His Excellency Magus is waiting in the main hall. Please follow me."

Desoro’s attitude was much more respectful than before. Ten years ago, he had still dared to exchange pointers with Han Xiao, but now, he did not even dare to compete with Han Xiao.

The few of them then chatted casually as they entered the Palace of Hidden Spells.

"The energy level of this place is so high." Marian took in a few deep breaths and felt extremely refreshed.

"Hmm. The Palace of Hidden Spells is capable of absorbing the dark energy and magical elements floating around in the universe and can raise the density of magical energy here," Desoro explained. "A mage who meditates in this place will see their efficiency increased greatly, and there is also sufficient energy to conduct various magical experiments. Even if one isn’t a mage, breathing in the air here will allow one’s spirit to be greatly refreshed."

Feidin then frowned and said doubtfully, "I feel my Psychic energy being suppressed in this place. I am unable to release it too far, and it’s greatly restricted after fifty meters."

"It’s like this. Because many mages carry out their own magical research in this place, they set up various restrictions to prevent any mental probing. Releasing one’s Psychic energy in this place carelessly is a taboo," Desoro said.

The few of them then entered the main hall.

Numerous thick magical books floated in midair, releasing a silver glow like the stars in the sky, seemingly forming a milky way in the main hall. There were a few hundred half-transparent Austins floating in midair and reading different books. They were all his doppelgangers, and Austin’s main body was seated atop his throne with his eyes shut. His hand was currently supporting his head up, and it was as though he was having a good nap.

The moment Han Xiao and the others walked in, Austin detected their presence and woke up from his slumber with a lazy yawn.

"Black Star, you’re here."

Austin wiped off the saliva by his lips, and his saliva transformed into a small, sky-blue dragon about the size of a finger and flew away.

"Your Excellency Magus," Han Xiao greeted, and both Feidin and Marian followed after him.

Desoro left tactfully and shut the doors.

"It is so rare for you to seek my help. We can talk later. Let me see what Psyker did to you."

Austin got off from his throne, and his numerous doppelgangers returned to his main body like birds returning to their nest. He then walked in front of Han Xiao, and his height was only at Han Xiao’s waist. His large and baggy red robes were dragged along the floor like a carpet.

Austin then shook his head, and his feet left the ground. Levitating until he was at Han Xiao’s eye level, he raised his tiny hand and tapped on Han Xiao’s forehead lightly. After taking a look at the psychic toxin in Han Xiao’s mind, he let out a gasp of surprise.

"How is it?" Han Xiao felt his heart sink. For a Beyond Grade A Super to be startled, could it be that his situation was terrible?

"I see… It’s a little troublesome…" Austin retracted his finger and placed his arms behind his back. He then revolved around Han Xiao and asked, "What do you know of Psyker?"

"I don’t really know much about him…" Han Xiao pondered for a while. He tried to recall the information that the players from his previous life had gathered. However, there was too little information about Psyker. Furthermore, the players were not able to reach the upper echelons, and there was plenty that they did not know.

"Alright, I have to first tell you that this psychic toxin’s official name is called Soul Embryo, and I do not have the ability to purge it for you."

Han Xiao was startled. "Even a Beyond Grade A Mage like you can’t do it?"

"Magic isn’t omnipotent." Austin shook his head with resignation.

Lagi had also said the same thing.

Han Xiao muttered under his breath.

"Let me explain it to you. Just like how I occasionally make magic scrolls myself, Psyker also uses various techniques to store his psychic attacks. Our Beyond Grade A disposable weapons are sold on the black market for a sky-high price. This time, the attack that injured you was a psychic weapon that Psyker created.

"More accurately speaking, not just Psyker’s psychic energy is included. Another type of energy is also included within the attack.

"According to my knowledge, Psyker once roamed the Ancient Star Desert before he became a Beyond Grade A Super. That is an ancient Star Field, and he obtained a Universal Treasure there called the Evolution Cube. It was an item from some lost civilization."

Hearing that, Han Xiao was stunned for a moment.

It’s actually that item?

At this moment, Feidin asked with curiosity, "What’s the use of that Evolution Cube?"

Austin looked at Feidin and felt as though he was pleasing to the eye. "Psyker hid the Evolution Cube extremely well, and I have never seen what it looks like. I also don’t know its exact usage. I only know two of its uses.

"First, the Evolution Cube can stimulate the potential of a living being, allowing it to evolve greatly in a short period of time. It can automatically adjust the gene structure of an individual to ensure that it is the optimum gene structure. Psyker relied on this method to become a Beyond Grade A Super. He activated the bloodline of his ancestors, and this was the contribution of the Evolution Cube."

Marian’s breathing became heavy. "Does this mean that this treasure is able to lower the barrier to become a Beyond Grade A Super?"

"Not just that," Austin said slowly. "Psyker also used the Evolution Cube to influence all the members of his race and aided an entire race to evolve and easily complete a journey that would take other civilizations a million years to complete. The genes of his entire race have reached perfection. Their body, lifespan, intelligence, and so on all exceed an ordinary species. The combat capability of a newborn infant is almost that of a Grade C Super."

Feidin’s eyes widened with shock. "Such a treasure actually exists? This is too unbelievable. Won’t other organizations eye such a powerful treasure with greed?"

"Of course, there will be some who are greedy. The Arcane Church also approached him, and Psyker came to an agreement with them. He was willing to serve the Arcane Church with the Evolution Cube in exchange for their protection.

"Originally, Psyker’s civilization was only an ordinary Star System Civilization and grew rapidly because of this incident, looking as though it is about to become the next Star Cluster civilization. Although a Star Cluster civilization already existed in the region that he was born in, Psyker had the support of the Arcane Church, and his competitor wouldn’t dare suppress him openly. They could only watch as he slowly rose to prominence."

Han Xiao nodded secretly. This was pretty much the same as the information that he had. Psyker’s attention was fully devoted to leading his civilization, and he did not like to participate in the conflicts of other regions.

He felt that it was extremely unlikely for Psyker to participate in the secret war.

"He sounds like a hero of his civilization," Feidin said respectfully.

Austin did not deny those words and continued. "The second ability of the Evolution Cube was to increase one’s mental strength. The upper limit is still unknown. Thus, Psyker’s psychic energy is unbelievably powerful, and his mental strength is even higher than mine. Most importantly, the strength of the Evolution Cube had mixed together with his own psychic energy to form a special reaction, causing his sentient psychic energy to have a terrifying life force.

"The toxin in your body is actually the embryo of a new soul. In other words, your other personality. This soul that had yet to be born has taken root in your mental world and is connected with your own soul. While I am able to destroy it, your body will suffer irreversible damage in the process."

"Irreversible damage means…" Han Xiao pushed carefully.

"Not sure. I don’t mind if you want to try." Austin chuckled.

Han Xiao felt his head ache. "Are there any other ways?"

Austin then smiled mysteriously and said, "If Ames or I suffered such an injury, we would be able to recover very easily."

Han Xiao’s eyes lit up, and he seemed to have understood something. "You mean…"

"While Psyker’s psychic energy is powerful, it is only at the Beyond Grade A level, and it isn’t incurable. The mental strength of a Beyond Grade A Super is extremely stable. As long as you become a Beyond Grade A Super, you don’t need to receive help from anyone and can recover on your own."

Austin looked at Han Xiao with excitement and added, "You know that I would not say such words to anyone else. However, you are different. I have great expectations for your potential, and you may be able to become a Beyond Grade A Super before being eroded."

"Actually, there is an even easier method." Han Xiao could not help but say, "You can ask Psyker to help me. He will definitely understand his own attack. Your relationship with him should be pretty good, right?"

"Nonsense, I don’t know him, and I am not familiar with him." Austin denied it without even thinking

Han Xiao rolled his eyes in response.

There’s no way I’ll believe you. You darn old man. That isn’t what you said when I first asked you for help.

Chapter 731: Return

Seeing that Han Xiao did not believe him, Austin said, "Psyker is only concerned about his own Civilization and will not be interested in helping you. Even if I request his assistance, he might not give me face since we don't have any relationship."

Your face isn't worth much, and to think you're a Beyond Grade A… You're also someone who likes socializing, just like me… Han Xiao inwardly complained.

As though reading Han Xiao's thoughts, Austin coughed and changed the topic. "Even if he was willing, if you don't become a Beyond Grade A Super, you won't live for long."

"Oh?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"You killed so many Grade A Supers from Bloodshed Land, but because of the rules of war, the Tyrant has been unable to make a move against you," Austin replied serenely. "However, once the secret war comes to an end, what do you think he will do?"

Han Xiao frowned in response. "He'll praise me for all my kills."

Austin was rendered speechless, an incredulous expression hanging on his face. He shook his head.

"If you manage to reach the Beyond Grade A level before the end of the secret war, the Tyrant will enter the war to deal with you, but you at least will have some hope of surviving. However, if you end up being unable to break through to Beyond Grade A, you will not be able to resist, and even if you try to drag the death sentence, the day will come when you two battle!

"Thus, to say that advancing into a Beyond Grade A Super is your only choice was not me lying to you. Furthermore, the time you have left isn't great."

Han Xiao stroked his chin, not speaking. However, Marian, who was at the side, was already dazed, and Feidin also had on an expression of worry. He glanced toward Han Xiao from time to time, his eyes showing his concern.

Become a Beyond Grade A in two to three years? That's impossible! Feidin could not even imagine how low the possibilities were.

He knew very well that Han Xiao had already reached a very high realm at this point. If he wished to take another step forward, how difficult would that be? In the past seven years, he had practically not improved a single step, and compared to his previous speed of progression that was akin to flying, even his close friends were hypothesizing that Black Star had finally met a bottleneck.

At that time, if the Tyrant went knocking, Black Star would likely die. The huge Black Star Army would also collapse along with his death.

Even if Black Star could seize the slim possibility and advance into the Beyond Grade A realm, he might not survive under the hands of the Tyrant. The Tyrant had long since advanced to Beyond Grade A, and his reputation had been earned through fighting. Thus, his combat capability could definitely crush a newly promoted Beyond Grade A.

With this in mind, Feidin was pessimistic about the future. He reached out and squeezed Han Xiao's shoulder, hoping to give him some comfort.

Deep in thought, Han Xiao must have been feeling very depressed at this moment.

"Where did you get your news from?"

"I naturally have my own sources." Austin smiled.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes as he pretended to sigh. In actual fact, this news was not out of his expectations. Since he dared to participate in the secret war, he was already prepared for the enemy and did not leave anything to fate.

Originally, he was only considered an ordinary member of Section Zero, but he had turned into one of their trump cards, successfully attracting the attention of the Tyrant. Han Xiao had also always been wary of Heber's involvement in the war. He was not scared, however, as he still had the backing of Floating Dragon, and if the Tyrant wanted to move against him, he would have to face the wrath of the Dragon Emperor. Both sides already had a prior grudge, so Ames would never take this matter lying down.

Moreover, once the Tyrant decided to intervene, the Purple Crystal Civilization would also explode and send troops regardless of the cost to surround Heber. A Star Cluster Civilization was sufficient to threaten the life of a Beyond Grade A Super. At that time, Klent would also use this as an excuse to send troops, and the nature of the secret war would become a large-scale war of two civilizations.

Both warring parties wished to control the scale of the war, so the Tyrant had not appeared. However, Han Xiao was not too aggressive. It was okay to take a piss on someone else's head, but sh*tting would go too far.

In fact, after he carved out a name for himself, he had reduced the frequency of his appearances. Having successfully formed an alliance with Purple Crystal, he had obtained a lot of development opportunities and had completed his original intention of participating in the secret war. Thus, he wanted to avoid the situation where the winds howled around the highest peaks.

Although he might have affected the process of this secret war, just based on the strength and status of the Calamity Grades on both sides, it would be hard to change the outcome of the war. He had acted within his means and did not slave away to complete each objective the Purple Crystal set for him.

As such, Austin's words only allowed Han Xiao's speculations to turn into reality, so he was not too surprised.

However, on the surface, Han Xiao still had to thank Austin for reminding him.

"I can only help you so much. The enchantment that Lagi has given you is pretty good. I don't need to improve it. You may leave."

Austin waved his hands, telling his subordinated to send off his guests.

Seeing the situation, Han Xiao did not stay any longer as well, taking the concerned Feidin and Marian, leaving the Palace of Hidden Spells.

Austin returned to his throne, and on his round face, there was an expression as though he was watching a fascinating show.

He never involved himself in disputes, as he liked to be in the position of a bystander, watching the fights across eras even as the seas themselves turned into mulberry fields.

Pressure could be a form of motivation, and he had purposefully stated the intentions of the Tyrant to see how Black Star would behave before this looming disaster. Would he rise against it, or would he be extinguished within? Would he be a defeated dog, leaving the Shattered Star Ring to escape the pursuit of the Tyrant?

Whichever outcome it was, Austin looked forward to it.

Of course, the scene that he wished to see most would be Black Star breaking the situation of the Shattered Star Ring that had been fixed for decades, injecting new vitality into this remote Star Field.

…

The trio boarded the spaceship, leaving the Palace of Hidden Spells.

There was only silence on-board.

Feidin could not resist opening his mouth after a while to ask, "Do you have any hope of breaking past your bottleneck in the next two to three years?"

Bottleneck? What bottleneck? Han Xiao did not respond immediately. He only glanced at him in confusion. Suddenly, it clicked as to what he was talking about, and Han Xiao could only shrug.

"I don't know." He naturally did not mention the matter of his interface.

"What then? The Tyrant is sure to come and kill you." Feidin was a little panicked.

"Maybe we can obtain the Evolution Cube from Psyker himself," Marian suggested. "Isn't that thing capable of lowering the threshold of entering Beyond Grade A?"

"I think there's no chance of that." Han Xiao shook his head.

Austin might have been able to discuss the matter with Psyker, but he had no intention of helping Han Xiao. As for Ames, because she was probably not familiar with Psyker, she could not use her face to talk to Psyker. The Evolution Cube was Psyker's treasure. Even if he wanted to use it, he did not know the other party. There was an eighty percent chance that Psyker would just ignore him.

Furthermore, he himself did not have any real bottlenecks and merely lacked experience.

"Then, what are you preparing to do?" Feidin asked.

"Improvise."

With the players returning in Version 3.0, Han Xiao was confident that he would reach Beyond Grade A, but he was unable to explain that to Feidin.

Feidin pressed on the shoulders of Han Xiao, speaking with a solemn expression. "If this really does not work, we'll just abandon the Black Star Army and escape to another Star Field. Our influence can be rebuilt; our lives are more important."

"And you'll come along with us?" Han Xiao jested.

Feidin paused for a moment before seriously nodding. "I will."

Feeling the genuine intentions of Feidin, Han Xiao was a little touched.

But he shook his head and changed the topic, smiling as he said, "Don't be frightened by what has not come. Let's talk about the issue of the Tyrant next time. Right now, I still have a more urgent problem. I need to find a way to suppress the parasitism in my mental territory. This psychic toxin… oh, I should call it the Soul Embryo. With this thing here, I can't even exert any energy."

"A pity that the Magus was unable to help." Feidin sighed.

"He just didn't want to help. Don't look at him having an amiable expression. In actual fact, that old chicken is extremely sly. Do you think he told me all that intelligence to help me?"

Han Xiao pursed his lips. He was not as easily manipulated as Herlous. To make him go all the way there, only to see him flap his lips a little and send them off, not even reimbursing them for fuel costs, what nonsense was this‽

In the end, he still had to find his own method. If he had known this, he would not have relied on Austin at all. This was a wasted trip.

As Han Xiao thought about it, he suddenly discovered a path.

Since the reason reaching Beyond Grade A could allow him to automatically recover was their strong mental strength, this meant that each time he levelled up, his spirit should increase. Thus, even if he did not reach Beyond Grade A, he should be able to suppress the Soul Embryo.

Because the NPCs did not have an interface, they could only subtly improve themselves through grinding and training. However, Han Xiao's leveling up was an instantaneous process, and the effect displayed was significant. Although upgrading would not allow him to clear away his negative state, it should be able to inhibit the growth of the Soul Embryo.

Han Xiao opened his interface. This trip had taken more than half a month, and the players had long returned to the Black Star Army and made their purchases. He had already accumulated a reasonable amount of experience to raise his level. This would serve to test his theory.

He did not hesitate, immediately raising his level by one.

_____________________

[Apostle Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.23.

+240 Energy, +3 STR, +4 DEX, +5 END, +10 INT.

You have received 8 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

_____________________

Han Xiao connected to his mental territory, and looking down, he saw that the area of purplish black mist where the Soul Embryo was had further shrunk. It had reduced from six percent to four percent.

Leveling up is indeed effective. The stronger the mental territory, the more the Soul Embryo will be suppressed.

As he withdrew his spiritual probing, he immediately came up with an idea. It was not as though he was incapable of attacking. As long as he reasonably upgraded himself, controlling the Soul Embryo to remain below thirty percent, there would be no possibility of a troublesome sub-personality rising.

He sighed in relief. Since there was a long-term plan to suppress it, the threat of the Soul Embryo had decreased. Indeed, enchanting and stuff were all external means; the most reliable path was still to strengthen himself. A matter that a Beyond Grade A could not deal with could be resolved simply by levelling himself.

If that's the case, it's not as if I can't attack. I just have to control the time taken for battle… Oh, but to be safe, I had better look for a stronger partner…

At this time, his communicator rang. Taking it out, Han Xiao saw that it was from Sylvia, who was manning the helm at the main headquarters. There was a photo attached.

In the picture, a dark red spaceship was dragging dozens of spaceships through a traction beam into the dock. A memorable flash of dark red hair leaped into his gaze; it was Hila and Aurora who were standing at the dock, showing contrasting cold and warm expressions.

Hila's back?

Han Xiao looked at the photo, and the corners of his mouth rose.

At that moment, he had the best candidate in mind.

…

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, the ladies have already arrived at the headquarters of Black Star Army."

In the palace of Floating Dragon Island, Vilna had her head lowered as she reported the status of the two sisters to Ames.

Ames had squeezed her force field into tiny little green spheres and was playing with them on her fingers. She smiled when she heard the news. "Did they meet into any problems?"

"Well, I sent out a fleet in secret, and there were eight small bandit groups that tried to attack them, but all of them were easily killed by Hila." Because Vilna was afraid that they would meet with unforeseen circumstances, she had sent out someone to follow them for protection.

Ames nodded in response. "You've done well. Since they have successfully reached Black Star's territory, recall the troops. Black Star will naturally take care of them."

She cared more for the siblings than herself. She did not feel that normally, but now that the two sisters had been gone for more than half a month, she began to feel as though she was lacking something in her life.

By the side, Aesop shook his head. "You don't need to worry about them at all. By following Black Star, they will grow quickly."

Looking over, Ames seemed a little unhappy. "Do you mean to say that I didn't teach well?"

Aesop waved his hands in helplessness. "Hila can absorb the dead's remaining spiritual powers to strengthen her own. She did not have an opportunity to use the ability here, but Black Star is participating in the war, with countless dying every second. For Hila, the best place for her to grow and practice is the battlefield. Even I can't imagine the pace of her growth beside Black Star."

"That's right. Black Star, that b*stard, will definitely make them join the battlefield. It's so dangerous. What if Black Star doesn't take care of them?" Ames murmured to herself, obviously focusing on a different direction. She resembled a worried parent, treating her two disciples who had followed her for more than a decade like her children.

Aesop and Vilna had a bad feeling upon hearing those words.

…

After spending yet another half a month travelling, Han Xiao's group finally arrived back at the headquarters and met the two sisters who had been away for a long time.

In the office, Aurora ran head first into Han Xiao's arms, squirming non stop. Although they were already old, she still felt the same familiarity and closeness to Han Xiao.

"Based on the contract, we're here to work for you." Hila was expressionless.

"We're all old acquaintances. There's no need to talk about an agreement or contract. I'm happy that you guys are here to help." Han Xiao stroked Aurora's hair as he laughed. "To think that a decade has passed just like that. You're all grown up."

The emotions in Hila's eyes fluctuated slightly.

They had once been puppets under the control of the Germinal Organization, but now, Black Star had become a great figure in the Universe, while Hila had also become a Calamity Grade Super. Things were different.

Thinking back to the past, Hila felt moved. The man in front of her had changed her entire life. Without Black Star, she would have grown old with guilt and hatred for the planet and would likely never have been able to enter the magnificent universe.

"The last time we fought side by side was more than a decade ago. At that time, I could not help out at all." Hila's eyebrows rose, and she was full of spirit. "But I've finally caught up to you!"

"I've already waited ten years for today." Han Xiao patted Hila's shoulders as he smiled. He then took two steps back, raising his hands as he said out loud, "Welcome to the Black Star Army!"

Chapter 732: Cultivation Plan

In Han Xiao's previous life, Hila strength had earned her the title 'Goddess of Death'.

Ever since Han Xiao saved these two sisters from the Germinal Organization, he had always seen Hila as a very important aid in the future. After waiting for so many years, Hila had finally grown and was now a Calamity Grade. She was now starting to be helpful.

Han Xiao knew about Hila's ability very well. Being able to become stronger by absorbing the souls of the dead was something that only she could do. In his previous life, she had slaughtered countless planets and grown faster than even the players.

In his eyes, although Hila did not have the Luck Glow, she was undoubtedly a legendary character… of course, a villainous character.

Although Hila was not walking the evil path, it just so happened to be in a time of war. All the dead soldiers could become the source of her power. This was a once in a thousand years opportunity that could make Hila live up to her true potential.

He needed someone that could fight in his place, and Hila was the perfect candidate.

As for Aurora…

Han Xiao turned to look at her, smiled kindly, and said, "How's the development of your Esper ability?"

Aurora chuckled. She flipped her hand, and a golden light appeared above her palm.

"I'm not good at battles, but I can cure any physical damages, and I can also stimulate the vital forces of others and make them stronger. Try it…"

As she was speaking, a cluster of golden light landed on Han Xiao. Han Xiao felt energized as if an electric current passed through his entire body, and many buffs appeared on the interface.

"Can your power be stored?" Han Xiao asked.

"Yes, I've tried to inject the vital energy into potions. These can be stored for a long time. But I'm not as hard-working as my sister, so I'm not a Calamity Grade yet. Thus, the expiration date is a little short. The healing effect of these potions will diminish over time and can last for two months at most."

Aurora scratched her head, a little embarrassed.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He looked at Aurora as if he was looking at a treasure. He saw the hope of expanding the army's business into the galactic medicine industry.

Aurora's Esper ability made her a born healer. When she was still very weak, her healing abilities were already extremely strong. Now that she was a Grade B Super, her healing ability would most likely have increased many times.

"Also, although I can't fight very well, I can regenerate very quickly." Aurora pulled out an explosive pistol from the belt of her battle suit, spun it a few rounds on her finger, and suddenly fired at her other hand.

With a bang, the beam penetrated her palm. Before Han Xiao could even be shocked by her actions, her wound healed up extremely quickly and disappeared. Her palm became white and smooth once again. no signs of it being wounded could be seen anywhere.

"See, I can protect myself now!" Like a child showing off, Aurora's face was filled with anticipation. She wanted to be praised by Han Xiao.

In the training that lasted more than ten years, other than cultivating her Esper ability, Aurora had also learned quite many shooting and fighting techniques to make up for her combat capability. As she had once been tortured by the Germinal Organization, although she looked weak and soft, she was extremely resilient and had a very high pain tolerance. She did not even frown the slightest when she casually shot through her hand.

What a tough girl… Han Xiao smiled and praised her. "That's an amazing ability."

The name [Life Return] sure was not an exaggeration. Aurora was only Grade B now, so when she reached Grade A, her regeneration power would probably be even stronger than his. Sadly, her Esper ability did not have a high combat capability. However, her ability and Hila's ability definitely made up for each other's weaknesses.

After the three of them chatted for a while, Hila said with a serious face, "How do you plan to arrange us?"

"I shall bring you to meet the officers of the army first."

Hila shook her head. "Before you came back, Sylvia took us to meet all the high-ranking officers. She said that when you're back, you'll personally decide our positions."

During the Mutation Disaster in Version 2.0, the most senior members of the army had all met Hila. They knew that her relationship with Han Xiao was not usual, so they definitely treated them well.

"Since that's the case, let's get down to business then," Han Xiao said. "The two of you will follow me as my bodyguards first. After you know more about how the army operates, I'll then arrange official high-ranking positions for you."

"No problem." Hila nodded.

Han Xiao thought for a moment then said, "Rest a few days, then I will bring you guys along."

Hila, however, shook her head and rejected that. "There's no need; we have rested enough. Give us missions as soon as possible. I want to test my true strength."

Why are you in more of a hurry than me? Han Xiao smiled, contemplated for a while, and then nodded. "Okay. We shall head out tomorrow. I'll take you guys to war."

He planned to keep a low profile for some time while reaping the players' Experience and cultivating Hila's potential personally.

…

In the West Wind Star System, Star Zone 11…

This was the border Star System that had been invaded before any others. The forces of the Bloodshed Land stationed there were the largest. They had built around a hundred strongholds spread across the various Star Zones in the West Wind Star System. Section Zero had set up perimeters at some strategically important places to prevent the Bloodshed Land from invading the areas around West Wind.

Perimeter 027 was one of them, with numerous Section Zero members garrisoned there throughout the year. The Black Star Army's fleet was in it as well, and the people stationed here rotated in shifts.

Other than the occasional large-scale military operations, perimeters were where battles occurred the most regularly. The Bloodshed Land tried to penetrate the perimeters time after time. The troops at the perimeters also sent small fleets to disrupt and attack the Bloodshed Land strongholds regularly. Those perimeters were the 'frontlines' of the war.

After the Kant Star System battle ended, the players started to explore freely. Han Xiao had yet to cancel the fifty percent off sale for those taking part in the war. The requirement to enjoy this benefit was to continue participating in the war. Hence, in the more than a month Han Xiao took to travel back and forth, most of the players were scattered across the various perimeters where there were countless battles. This was also the usual way of taking part in the secret war main storyline.

There were also players that did not take part in the main storyline. Some went to do mercenary missions, some went to explore around, and some guild players bought mining devices and small carrier ships and went to become miners on the resource planets under the Black Star Army.

More than 20,000 players gathered at Perimeter 027, participating in the daily combat missions.

Not long ago, a Bloodshed Land fleet had attacked the perimeter but failed. The stationed troops were now cleaning up the battlefield. In the military space station office, the commander of Perimeter 027, Rexson, was looking at the troops outside the window cleaning the wreckages while listening to his deputy report the result of the battle.

"The enemy lost eighty-six small battleships and nineteen heavy frigates. We lost thirty-eight battleships. As for casualties… ahem, it's unknown for the enemy. The casualties on our side are being calculated right now. The initial estimate is that the damage is very small…"

"All thanks to the Black Star Army again?" Rexson said with a relaxed expression.

"Yes. The Immortals of the Black Star Army destroyed many of the enemy battleships through close-quarter battles. Since they don't need any retreat plans, we did not suffer any extra casualties…"

The deputy swallowed his saliva. It was written on the battle report that after landing on the enemy battleships through the charge cabin, many of them instantly detonated the charge cabin and did not consider retreating at all. Some even landed while carrying nuclear bombs. These people were extremely brave.

"Ever since the Black Star Army sent a few dozen thousand Immortals, the combat pressure on our side decreased tremendously. These people are born warriors." Rexson took a deep breath.

It had been two months since the version started. A lot of players had reached level 100 and completed their Promotion Missions one after another, getting the opportunity to experience Race Evolution. The versatility of the players increased once again. The first batch of players had finally entered Grade B.

Although they were just the weakest kind of Grade Bs, the increase in their Grade still made a powerful impact. The mid-tier combatant standard of the Black Star Army instantly increased an entire level. As more than a million of those Supers were sent into the various perimeter battlefields, the situation of many of those perimeters immediately became much better.

For Perimeter 027, the twenty thousand or so Grade B players secured victories for all the recent skirmishes at the perimeter. Rexson could not have been more satisfied with the Black Star Army's players.

The first batch of Black Star Army players were no longer disposable forces like before; they had the ability to make decisive impacts to small scale skirmishes. The players discussed this on the forums. Bun-Hit-Dog mentioned Frenzied Sword's theory during his video and said that as the players became stronger with the version updates, their influence on the world would grow bigger as well, and they would be widely recognized.

Real-time feedback was an important source of fun for the players. If the attitude of an NPC was the same toward max level players and new players, it would be way too boring. The factor that attracted the players the most in Galaxy was that immersive experience as if they were living in a real world.

This time, Rexson suddenly received a notification. He glanced at it, and his expression changed drastically.

"What happened?" the deputy hastily asked.

"Quickly, make the preparations. His Excellency Black Star will be coming personally, and he's almost here." Rexson quickly walked out of the room.

Rexson summoned the high-ranking officers and went to the dock. After a while, the Blacklight Stealth entered.

Han Xiao brought along the two sisters and Feidin. Feidin had come of his own volition. He was worried about Han Xiao's mental state, so he planned to always be around Han Xiao till Han Xiao recovered, just in case.

As soon as they disembarked from the spaceship, Rexson approached them respectfully. To him, Han Xiao was someone that he would have no chance of coming into contact with usually. Han Xiao had gained the respect of all the Section Zero members through his battle results.

"No need to be so formal. I would like to know about the situation of the Bloodshed Land strongholds nearby," Han Xiao said with a smile.

Rexson was flattered. He hastily invited Han Xiao and the others into the battle conference room, opened the tactical star map, and explained the situation.

Han Xiao stared at the star map, nodded, and said, "Got it, I'm planning to attack Stronghold W-58."

Stronghold W-58 was the biggest hostile stronghold around Perimeter 027, and one Calamity Grade was stationed there. Rexson had never thought of attacking it, but once he heard what Han Xiao said, he was secretly content.

"I need some helpers. Don't worry, the merit will all be yours." Han Xiao smiled.

Rexson nodded continuously and said, "I will send the perimeter fleet to work with you."

Although Han Xiao was not his direct boss, Rexson was not willing to give up this opportunity of gaining Han Xiao's favor, not to mention that the merit of eliminating an enemy stronghold would all go to him.

"Okay, we act in one day's time."

Han Xiao nodded. He had gone to the perimeter this time to let Hila test her abilities, so of course, he was going to strike.

…

Manudo was the Bloodshed Land Grade A Super stationed in Stronghold W-58. He was not very worried.

Not long ago, he had received a message from spies that Black Star had appeared at Perimeter 027. He was the only Calamity Grade in the strongholds nearby. Since Black Star was already there, Manudo felt that he would not mind getting rid of a usual Calamity Grade like him on the way. His heart was half-frozen in fear.

Manudo hastily reported this to the headquarters. To his surprise, the overall commander proactively contacted him.

"There's a very high chance that the Black Star will be attacking the stronghold you're in now. However, don't panic. I'm going to give you a mission."

"Is it retreat?" Manudo saw hope.

"Of course not!" Jorde said with a deep voice. "I need you to do one thing—lure Black Star into fighting and battle with him."

"You can just tell me if you want me to kill myself…" Manudo felt the utmost despair.

"Ahem, I will deploy the Calamity Grades around to support you. You're not going to fight alone." Jorde was practically speechless. The fearful name of Black Star was deeply carved into the hearts of the high-level combatants of the Bloodshed Land. There was nothing he could do about it. He could only explain, "Not long ago, Black Star fell into my trap. He's not at his maximum strength now. I need you to test him."

Jorde wanted to speculate what damage Psyker's weapon dealt to Han Xiao through observing Han Xiao's reactions during battle. He could only feel relieved after seeing it with his own eyes.

At the same time, on a desolate planet between Stronghold W-58 and Perimeter 027, Summer Night Flower and dozens of other players who had joined Klent arrived in spaceships.

They were doing the main storyline mission of the Klent faction. As warriors of the Bloodshed Land, they were deployed to the stronghold near the perimeter to take part in small scale skirmishes just like the Black Star Army players.

The Bloodshed Land had very strict rules. They were not allowed to explore freely like they could in the Black Star Army. Summer Night Flower and the others were not used to it. They could not help but to miss the treatment of the Black Star Army. Sadly, they only knew to treasure it after losing it.

This time, Summer Night Flower and the others finally had some casual time. They had gone to this planet to wait for someone.

Their position in the Bloodshed Land was not high, so their privileges could not be compared to when they were in the Black Star Army. Hence, Summer Night Flower contacted his friend who was still in the Black Star Army and told him to buy the fifty percent off products from the army for them. This planet was where they were going to make the exchange.

Chapter 733: Protecting the Law

"Brother, are you here yet?"

"Soon, soon."

A small spaceship was parked on the brown desolate land. Summer Night Flower and the others were waiting beside the spaceship.

Very soon, another spaceship landed beside them. The people in it got out of the spaceship, looked around, and greeted Summer Night Flower.

"Where's the stuff?" Summer Night Flower approached.

"Where's the money?" the person helping to do the purchases replied.

"Didn't I make the transfer long ago?" Summer Night Flower said with resignation.

"Ha, I just wanted to paint the atmosphere of an illegal trade. Didn't it feel very dramatic?"

The person chuckled. Seeing that Summer Night Flower was expressionless, he could only wipe the smile off his face awkwardly and take him into the cabin to see the stuff.

"There, this is all the stuff you wanted. Count it. Don't say I scammed you."

Summer Night Flower scanned through and calculated in his mind that the quantity was all correct. Only then did he say, "No need to, I trust you."

This time, the person helping to make the purchase rubbed his hands with a slightly embarrassed expression and said, "You know, we've known each other for many years. We're quite close, right?"

Summer Night Flower was a little confused. "What are you saying?"

"I'm asking you, are we good friends that play together?"

"Why?"

"Since we're friends, can you sacrifice yourself and let me kill you a few times to earn some bounties?" the person asked cautiously. "After all, you can't accept the Bounty Missions from the army. Instead of letting others kill you, I can split thirty percent of the bounty with you."

"Piss off." Summer Night Flower was speechless. Thirty percent? How is that little bounty reward going to make up for the experience I lose from dying?

"Stop talking nonsense. You've brought the stuff, so I'm taking it away," Summer Night Flower said as he was about to pick up the equipment.

This time, the person suddenly pressed on his hand and chuckled, "No, I think it's better for me to keep it for you temporarily."

"What do you mean? Are you trying to con me?" Summer Night Flower was furious. His friends around him all came closer with hostile looks on their faces, implying they would not hesitate to kill for the equipment.

The person helping to buy the equipment did not panic at all. He slowly said, "This is for your own good. You might be robbed very soon if you're carrying new equipment."

Summer Night Flower suddenly had a bad feeling.

At this time, the sound of spaceships landing came from outside. Small spaceships landed on the ground one after another, and a huge group of players rushed out.

The expression of Summer Night Flower and the rest changed drastically. He knew that these people were there for the bounty. He turned to look at the person who had helped to purchase the equipment in disbelief. "You betrayed me‽"

"Look at it yourself." The person curled his lips and took out the communicator. On it was the location of the person wanted by the army, which was the location of Summer Night Flower and the rest of the people. Their coordinates were constantly monitored. This trade was not a secret to the other players at all.

"Why didn't I know about this‽" Summer Night Flower was stunned. Then he realized with resignation that his army program had automatically been uninstalled.

The Phillip sub-program of these players became a background monitoring device that sent their coordinates to the nearby Black Star Army members at all times. It was like a constant reminder to the army members nearby. Summer Night Flower and the others were as conspicuous as sheep passing through a pack of wolves, except they did not know it at all.

Only the players nearby would receive the coordinates. Summer Night Flower and the rest had only gone to Stronghold W-58 not long ago, so only the players in Perimeter 027 received the coordinates. They thought that this was just a mission reminder, so no one discussed it on the forums. Thus, Summer Night Flower and the rest had no idea.

Suddenly, Summer Night Flower realized something. With a face of shock, he said, "Wait a minute, you knew that our coordinates were exposed all long, yet you didn't tell me and even did not cancel the trade‽"

"Sorry, I'm the cop."

"Speak like a human being!"

The person smiled and said, "Sigh, I have to make a living, okay? Since you're already here, it's a waste not to kill you. Like I said, instead of letting others take the bounty, just let me take it. I will split thirty percent with you."

Summer Night Flower's mouth shivered. He pointed at him and could not say a word.

So, you had an ulterior motive all along!

This was a trap!

I saw you as a friend, but you wanted to deceive me?

What happened to basic trust between people‽

If the furious looks on the Klent faction players around them could turn into knives, Summer Night Flower would have been sliced into a thousand pieces.

Looking at the quickly approaching players, Summer Night Flower hastily raised his hand with a face full of grief. The person helping to do the purchase thought that he wanted to fight, so he quickly jumped back a few meters. To his surprise, Summer Night Flower stood in place and raised four fingers.

"Forty percent!"

The person's eye sparkled. He kindly reminded Summer Night Flower and said, "Remember to choose the faction revive point when reviving, or you'll get killed another time."

"Thank you so f*cking much!" Summer Night Flower clenched his teeth so hard it sounded like pieces of metal rubbing against each other.

Woosh!

With a familiar flash of white light, Summer Night Flower returned to Stronghold W-58. His face was filled with grief, but he had no tears to cry.

This is so tiring. I shouldn't have come to Klent…

The moment Summer Night Flower thought that, he quickly eliminated it. He took a few deep breaths to calm himself down and convinced himself to believe in his analysis.

Although the path ahead would be twisted, he still believed that the future of the Klent faction was brighter.

"I will definitely be able to earn back the damages suffered now." Summer Night Flower encouraged himself then left the revive point. He was not planning to become the target of the rage of the rest of the Klent players.

This time, a message appeared on the interface. It was his friend that helped to make the purchase.

"I'll hold onto your stuff for now. Let's find another time to meet again."

Summer Night Flower was filled with rage.

You want to scam me another time‽

"Piss of! Refund!"

Han Xiao saw this small incident on the forums. A player made a post to show off that he got the first kill of the traitor. He felt this was something worth praising, so he sent extra experience and Enas through the faction interface.

The analysis post of Summer Night Flower became popular again. Many were mocking him and laughing at it. Summer Night Flower said that him getting killed was nothing; it was just a usual faction conflict, and the storyline in the future would prove that he was right. He was clearly very stubborn.

After killing some time, a day later, Rexson gathered the troops and attacked Stronghold W-58.

With Han Xiao's current experience, he had seen many small galactic skirmishes fought around a single stronghold. He did not even need to observe the battlefield to know what would happen.

The fleets fought intensely. Han Xiao was observing from the flagship and did not participate, nor did he let Hila and Feidin participate. Seeing that there were countless deaths on both sides, only then did he turn to look at Hila.

"Try the effect of absorbing souls of the dead on the battlefield."

Hila nodded. A tint of red light flashed across her eyes. Then, black red energy covered her entire body. It was like she suddenly grew more than twenty centimeters taller and gave off a vibe of an ancient God—merciless, enormous, and solemn.

In the wide galactic battlefield, gray fog appeared in the countless spaceship wreckages floating in space. They formed countless gray snakes and gathered into Hila's hand through thousands of miles.

The remaining energy of all the warriors that died on the battlefield was absorbed by her.

Hila exhaled deeply, clenched her fists, and said, "Both the strength and range of my Esper ability are enhanced. That saved me at least half a year's time."

"Great, it works." Han Xiao was delighted. This was good news. The quicker Hila became stronger, the earlier she would be able to fight in his place. He would be able to let Hila help him get rid of those unimportant enemies.

He decided to call the quick growth method exclusive to Hila 'Gray Soul Absorption'. It was almost like a cheat.

At this time, a strange energy suddenly exploded in the middle of the battlefield. From the fleet of the Stronghold W-58, three Calamity Grades flew out. The interference of high-level combatants quickly toppled the balance of the battlefield and became something that Rexson's troops could not deal with. Originally, they were only slightly at a disadvantage, but they were now constantly forced to retreat.

Inside the flagship, the deputy exclaimed with shock, "Why are there three Calamity Grades? The intelligence says that there's only Manudo!"

However, not only did Rexson not panic, he even smiled instead.

"It doesn't matter if there's three of them. With Black Star here, even if it were thirty…" Rexson paused. Although he was extremely confident in Han Xiao, he still did not dare exaggerate too much. He coughed and then said, "Even if there were 13 of them, His Excellency Black Star would still kill them all."

At this time, the scenery viewing window of the flagship zoomed in and focused on Manudo.

In the window, Manudo did a provocative sign toward the flagship, and the flagship received a video message from Manudo. His pale face appeared on the screen. His forehead was covered in sweat, and he had a very twisted mocking expression on his face.

"Black Star! I know you're in there. Don't hide. I'm not afraid of you. Us three Grade A Supers are challenging you right here. Do you dare accept it? Hahaha!"

In the end, Manudo laughed stiffly as sweat rolled down his face. The skin on his face was even shivering as if he was about to cry, and he was barely keeping up the ferocious expression.

The people in the flagship command room had strange expressions on their faces.

The enemy is taunting us, but why does it feel so unconfident?

Han Xiao held his forehead. Taunting with such bad acting skills, are you serious?

Rexson turned to Han Xiao and respectfully said, "Your Excellency Black Star, we can't deal with Calamity Grades. Please help."

In his eyes, if Han Xiao attacked, killing three normal Calamity Grade Supers would be a piece of cake.

However, Han Xiao shook his head and patted Hila's thin waist. "These three people are yours."

Despite having to face three opponents of the same grade, Hila did not look troubled at all. She turned and prepared to strike immediately. She was someone not afraid of obstacles and was happy to conquer them. Since Han Xiao could fight multiple opponents of the same grade, Hila took this as her target as well. She had very high requirements for herself.

Furthermore, she also wanted to fight strong enemies and test her limits so that she could gain a clearer idea of where she stood in the Calamity Grade.

Manudo and the other two attacked the battleships while waiting for Han Xiao to appear. To Manudo, every second was torture. It was as if he had stepped into the execution ground and was waiting for the blade to land on his head. If not for Jorde's orders, he would have run away immediately.

Jorde was also observing the battlefield remotely, waiting for Han Xiao to appear.

This time, a dark red meteor appeared in the eyes of those people at an extremely high speed. It headed right toward the three of them. A Grade A Cannon Master beside Manudo fired from far away. High energy particle beams landed on the dark red meteor one after another, slowly reducing its speed.

However, the next moment, this dark red meteor suddenly erupted and released thousands of red energy beams that almost covered half of the entire battlefield. These energies were extremely thick, like thousands of enormous pythons. They spun their head and crashed into the Bloodshed Land fleet.

Manudo and the other two people were also hit by dozens of almost solid red energy beams. Other than having the usual heat and explosive damage, Hila's energy beams also gave the three of them psychic damages. They hastily backed away with shock.

"This energy is very strange."

"This energy beam tried to absorb my spiritual body away like tentacles with suction cups."

As the tsunami-like red energy release ended, Hila appeared. The black-red armor on her body was focused on mobility and enhancing energy release. She did not wear a helmet, but her head was covered by a half-transparent energy layer, providing life functions and a wide vision.

Manudo was shocked. He had expected Black Star to attack, but who was this woman?

"Is there such a person in the Black Star Army?"

"It doesn't show on the intelligence. Could she be a new officer?"

"She's very strong. I feel a sense of threat from her."

The three of them spoke in their communication channel. They all felt the pressure.

Jorde, who was remotely spectating, was also confused. He carefully sized Hila up and was sure that he had never seen this person before, yet Black Star had sent her to fight three Calamity Grades alone. Was this because he believed in her strength?

"The Black Star Army sure has a lot of talents."

Jorde clenched his teeth. Seeing that Black Star was not going to fight, he had no choice but to tell Manudo and the others to fight with Hila and see how strong Hila was.

At the same time, the others on the battlefield also noticed the confrontation between the high-level combatants.

The Black Star Army players saw Hila's look and were shocked.

"Aye, this beauty looks kind of familiar."

"I remember, isn't this Hila who appeared in both 1.0 and 2.0?"

"That's right. It's her. I thought she'd died by Version 3.0, but it turns out she's still alive and much stronger."

"She appeared in the mid to later stages in Version 2.0. When did she join our army?"

"If I remember correctly, when Black Star went deep into the Germinal Organization's base in Version 1.0, it was to rescue her. Could she be the captain's old lover?"

"Oh…"

Many players let out meaningful grunts before quietly activating the video recording function.

Chapter 734: Mislead

On the battlefield, Hila released dark red energy and fought with the three enemy Calamity Grades at the same time. Hila felt the pressure immediately. She clenched her teeth and tried to hang on, barely standing her ground using the uniqueness of her Esper ability.

Han Xiao observed for a while and figured out Hila's actual combat capability.

These three enemies are normal Calamity Grades around level 180. With Hila current strength, she's in the upper-middle ranking among Calamity Grades. She still lacks experience in fighting with Calamity Grades, but due to her unique Esper ability, she can deal with two such enemies at most. Three is too much.

Although Hila had sufficient strength to be part of the battles that he was in, she was still some distance away from becoming the capable assistant that he wanted.

However, with her growth rate, she would be able to overcome that distance very quickly.

As he was pondering, the situation started to gradually worsen for Hila.

Han Xiao was not worried about Hila's safety. Not only did Hila have the Molding Talent that would lock her health, Aurora was around as well. It would be difficult for her to die even if she wanted to.

At the same time, a small incident was happening on the battlefield that Han Xiao was unaware of.

A small Bloodshed Land assault ship was fleeing in the battlefield, chased by dozens of Black Star Army battleships.

"Quickly run, they're coming again!"

Its shield endured attacks continuously. The spaceship was trembling as the piercing red alarm echoed within. On the spaceship, Summer Night Flower and the others were covered in sweat, panicking.

They were being chased by a large group of Black Star Army players. Phillip had sent their coordinates to all the army members on the battlefield.

Quite a number of players taking part had seen it and thought, Nice, bonuses!

Thus, Summer Night Flower and the others' nightmare began. No matter how they changed their location, it was always shown on the radar of the army players.

Originally, fighting with opposing faction players was very common. However, in this skirmish, the number of players on the Black Star Army's side was more than a hundred times the number of players on Summer Night Flower's side. Hence, it became one-sided, and Summer Night Flower's group was chased by the other players.

Summer Night Flower's mood was extremely bad. He regretted going to Stronghold W-58. He should have requested to be deployed to other strongholds that did not have to face the Black Star Army!

The Black Star Army was full of bad people that were just merciless. He was afraid.

As a player of the opposing faction, he decided to avoid the Black Star Army in the future. Even if that meant that he had to play alone in a remote stronghold, the game experience would be better than being chased by enemies all the time.

As Summer Night Flower was in a meltdown while being chased by the army players, the battle between Hila and three enemy Calamity Grades reached its climax.

The few of them kept shifting the battlefield, moving across the various areas where the fleets were fighting. With continuous explosions, people died nonstop, and gray souls entered Hila and recovered her energy.

So, this is my current limit.

While fighting, thoughts flashed through Hila's mind.

This was the first time that she had fought in a true battle with a Calamity Grade. She quickly gained combat experience and a clearer understanding of her own combat capability.

Ames and Han Xiao who had trained her all along were much stronger than her, so she could not really measure her strength. Now that she was fighting with normal Calamity Grades, although she had the lower hand, she felt amazing. She could now finally fully utilize her strength in a battle where she was not completely thrashed.

Hila thought that she seemed quite strong, but she was not satisfied with that.

I can barely deal with three enemies… but Han Xiao can fight ten at once. There's still a huge difference… Hila clenched her teeth.

She saw Han Xiao as the goal to chase after. Now that she felt the pressure of fighting three enemies at the same time, she had a deeper understanding of Han Xiao's combat capability.

If he was in my place, the battle would have already ended.

Feeling the difference between the two of them, Hila clenched her teeth and increased the output of her energy.

On the other side, Manudo was communicating with his comrades.

"This woman's ability is very strange. It gives me a Necromancer feeling, but it's not really the same."

"Her energy can cause both physical and psychic damage. After getting hit, even the vitality of my cells was suppressed, and the efficiency of cells creating energy decreased. It's as if… as if my life force is suppressed."

"What do you think, Staff Sergeant Jorde?" Manudo asked.

Jorde, who was watching remotely, nodded slowly and said with a serious tone, "I have already saved the video of her battle into the database. Although her ability is strong, it's not the focus this time. Black Star is the target that you're supposed to test."

"But he's not joining the battle. Does that mean we can retreat?" Manudo asked hastily. He did not want to stay even one second longer near Black Star.

"Maybe it's because he's training his subordinates or because of something else," Jorde said with a deep voice. "Attack harder. As long as this woman's life is in danger, Black Star will definitely do something."

Aren't you just hurrying us to die‽

Manudo felt miserable.

The few of them fought intensely for a while. Eventually, Hila showed a flaw under the aggressive attacks from three enemies. Manudo's Cannon Master teammate caught the opportunity. He shot a particle cannon beam that was enhanced with many burst damage abilities right at Hila's hasty defense attempt. It shattered her armor and blasted her away.

"Er…"

Hila stopped herself from rolling in the universe. Her body was covered with black wounds and dead cells. The area around her left shoulder and half of her neck was gone, an injury a normal person would have immediately died from and was considered heavy even for Calamity Grades.

Manudo and his two teammates were just about to chase when Manudo suddenly felt alarmed and slowed down behind the other two.

Hila took a deep breath. Suddenly, thick light shot out from her eyes. Her wounds started to heal as her cells multiplied at an extremely high speed.

The flesh on her neck and her left shoulder grew back in an instant, showing her white skin under the broken armor. Energy was flowing through her entire body, and she was almost back at peak performance.

In the flagship, Aurora's eyes were shining as well. After Hila recovered, only then did the light in Aurora's eyes slowly disappear. She quickly gasped for air as if she had just spent quite a lot of energy.

Hila and Aurora's Esper abilities had a special connection. Through their blood relation, Aurora created a life force link between the two of them. If Hila was too heavily injured, Aurora would send her life force and heal her remotely.

As long as Aurora still had stamina, Hila would be able to recover at a terrifying speed. Its effect was similar to Han Xiao's Aurora Character Summon Card.

Hila fought the battles, and Aurora healed her. The number of times that she could heal depended on her stamina. It was only slightly less powerful than Han Xiao's health-stamina cycle. When the two sisters fought together, they were almost undefeatable.

Jorde was stunned, and his expression changed slightly—this reminded him of Black Star.

Black Star had this kind of horrifying recovery ability as well!

Could it be that this redhead woman had a special relationship with Black Star‽

Could she be his… daughter?

Initially, Jorde did not take Hila too seriously, but he suddenly felt that he needed to do thorough research on her.

Manudo and the others stood in place and were stunned as well.

Hila felt the overflowing energy in her body, but instead of being happy, she was filled with discontent.

She had been keeping Aurora away from harm, but because of her mistake, Aurora had to use her life force to heal her. She felt that this was her fault… Although Aurora could gain that life force back very quickly, because of what had happened back in the Germinal Organization, this was still a taboo for Hila.

Just as Hila was about to attack in rage, a large hand suddenly pressed on her shoulder. She turned around. It was Han Xiao.

"That's enough. There's no training value if you carry on. It will just be a battle to see who's stamina depletes first."

Han Xiao softly pressed on Hila's smooth, soft cheeks. Nanoparticles extended from the tip of his finger and formed a helmet, replacing Hila's broken helmet and allowing her to speak in the communication channel.

Hila clenched her teeth and said, "Understood."

"Leave this to me."

Han Xiao turned around and looked at the three nervous Calamity Grades.

Manudo was panicking. Black Star finally was going to attack.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something.

The enemies clearly knew of his capabilities, yet they made such a bad attempt at provoking him, so their goal should be to lure him into battle. Of course, this was definitely not because they were kind and sending him free kills.

After thinking for a short moment and recalling Manudo's nervous expression when provoking him, it then occurred to Han Xiao. Jorde was definitely behind this. That little weasel had used Psyker's psychic weapon on him two months ago, but he had gone to the Palace of Hidden Spells, so he did not take part in any battles for one and a half months. This had made Jorde anxious, so he was using this to test his current state.

Having realized that, Han Xiao had an idea and did not immediately attack. Instead, he connected to Manudo's communication channel and slowly said, "Are you sure you want to fight me? I don't know if this is your own decision or someone ordered you to do so, but think about it carefully. People are going to die from this."

Manudo gulped. The other two did not speak. Jorde did not want to be discovered by Han Xiao, so he did not speak either.

"I'm now giving you guys a chance. As long as you surrender and announce to leave the Bloodshed Land, I won't do anything to you. What do you say?" Han Xiao said.

"You want me to betray the Bloodshed Land? No way!" the Grade A Cannon Master yelled and immediately fired.

Without even moving, more than 300 Watcher Instruments appeared beside Han Xiao, formed a formation, and created a psionic shield, easily blocking the attack.

Han Xiao shook his head and deliberately said, "What's so good about Heber? Does he deserve such loyalty from you?"

"He's the only one I'm willing to follow. How dare you speak of His Excellency Heber like that‽" this Cannon Master sneered. He was a direct member of the Bloodshed Land, so he was extremely loyal.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and did not speak anymore. He summoned the mechanical army and attacked. It swept over the entire battlefield like a tsunami, scattering all the fleets.

Facing the mechanical army that filled his vision, Manudo felt suffocated. He had no choice but to fight it.

Han Xiao activated Apostilization and joined the battle. He secretly changed the tempo of the battle, increased the attack frequency of all the mechanical soldiers, and sacrificed accuracy to do so, deliberately showing impatience.

Of course, normal people would not notice such details, but he believed that the Bloodshed Land would definitely discover these tiny changes with their artificial intelligence's analytical abilities.

Sometimes, tricking smart people was even easier than using stupid ones. All he had to do was mislead the opponents into the conclusion that he wanted them to have through details, and the opponents would fall for it easily. If they were not cautious enough, Han Xiao's efforts would all go to waste.

High-level lies are always ninety percent real and only ten percent fake. What Han Xiao wanted was to make Jorde speculate that he had become weaker.

As for the reason, it was so that he could use this opportunity to take some time off from the secret war and focus on cultivating leeks. This was the most important matter at the moment. Be it advancing to Beyond Grade A or suppressing the Soul Embryo, they all required a large amount of Experience.

He was completely uninterested in letting his sub-personality be born. It would be best to make sure it never formed.

As soon as Han Xiao struck, the battle became one-sided. Under the True Damage of [Legendary Battle Technique], the Cannon Master was very quickly shattered by the mechanical soldiers. The head of the other teammate was also blown away. Manudo was the only one left barely holding on.

Panicking, Manudo hastily sent a message and said, "Wait, wait, I surrender!"

Han Xiao received the message and stopped the mechanical army. He then waved his hand and pulled Manudo over from afar through the mechanical suit's force field.

Manudo did not dare resist and let the mechanical soldiers restrain him.

"You've made the right choice." Han Xiao smiled.

Manudo nodded continuously. He had thought it through—it was clear that Jorde did not care about his life, which meant that he would die sooner or later in the Bloodshed Land, so he might as well surrender. Furthermore, he did not have another choice if he wanted to live.

Escape from Black Star?

I'm not Hadavy, I can't do it!

As the high-level combatants of the enemy were all eliminated, the battle that followed had a clear result. Rexson destroyed Stronghold W-58 and seized the loot.

After Hila absorbed all the remaining gray souls on the battlefield, she locked herself in her room and digested her first experience of fighting with Calamity Grades.

Jorde was analyzing the recording of Han Xiao's battle in the headquarters.

Losing a stronghold meant nothing to him; what he cared about at the moment was Han Xiao's state.

Very soon, he noticed something strange.

"Two months ago, Black Star never asked anyone to surrender and killed every one of our people. Even when he faced just one Calamity Grade, he never showed any mercy. Why did he ask them to surrender?"

Jorde frowned and looked at the recording a few more times.

Before, Black Star's mechanical army's attacks were all carefully and precisely calculated. Today, however, the attack rate of his mechanical army increased visibility, as if he was willing to waste energy to increase the attack speed and gave up some of the precise calculations. As a result, many attacks completely missed.

This change made him feel a sense of… impatience?

"First, he asked our people to surrender, then he was in a hurry to end the battle…" Jorde pondered for a while and suddenly figured it out.

Black Star was trying to reduce the time of the battle, or he did not want to take part in the battle.

These two details made Jorde feel that he could guess Han Xiao's current state.

Psyker's psychic weapon might have dealt some kind of continuous damage to Black Star, and if he fought others, the damage would be enlarged. This was why Black Star acted differently from before.

"My speculation should be right!"

The threat of Black Star had decreased!

Having proved that Black Star had become weaker, Jorde was overjoyed. Although he did not know what damage Han Xiao had received, with this discovery, he could daringly adjust his strategies.

Chapter 735: Evolve! Advancing on the Path of a Tank!

The battlefield of the secret war was too broad, and the small skirmish did not attract too much attention. Jorde was the only one who paid attention to it.

Not caring about the Bloodshed Land's reaction, Han Xiao rejected Rexson's celebration invitation after they won the battle. He brought Hila along and headed to other perimeters to give her more battlefields for her Soul Absorption.

While Han Xiao was going around the various battlefields, a new popular topic appeared on the forums. Quite a number of players that attacked Stronghold W-58 uploaded the video with Hila in it, which made the players recall memories from long ago.

Initially, this was just a usual video, but when people realized that Han Xiao and Hila had known each other for three versions now, especially after their 'old love' was dug out from the Galaxy Chronicles, the focus of the topic became entirely something else. Articles with all sorts of titles started to appear.

"Shock! Black Star Did This to Hila!"

"Reigniting Old Flames? Or Has He Found New Love?"

"A Love Story That Crossed Twenty Years!"

"Who Really Is the Woman Black Star Loves the Most? Counting Those Beauties He Once Loved…"

The players' spirits were highest when talking about these kinds of topics. After all, they could imagine as much as they wanted, and there would not be any consequences. The topic gradually turned from Hila to Black Star's love history.

Han Xiao was now the most famous NPC in the Shattered Star Ring. His position was high. He was rich, strong, and rather handsome. Ever since Version 1.0, the players had never really gotten to know any storylines regarding his love life, and the players were extremely curious about it.

Not just Hila, all the known living female characters related to the Black Star Army became hot topics of the players' intense discussions. On the forums, the supporters of different female characters were split into factions and argued with each other.

"Hila's known him for the longest. It's clearly old flames being reignited."

"Boo, us Dragon Emperor supporters will never give in!"

"You people know nothing. Sylvia is the one and only!"

"Us Herlous supporters are smiling."

"Us Harmon supporters are unhappy. We're going to chop your heads off."

"Come on, you guys are weak. Greetings from the Phillip supporters."

"Us Feidin supporters announce our exit. Feidin is our husband. Black Star, you're not good enough for him!"

"Right now, Aroshia is still on the way."

"The Germinal Organization Leader is watching you from above."

The popular topics on the forums caused the fame of the various Black Star Army officers to grow. As the focus of the topics, Black Star also gained more attention.

Han Xiao did not pay much attention to these topics on the forums; they were all for the players' entertainment and would not cause any influence. The only possible result of it would just be more parodies…

…

After going to quite a few perimeters, Hila's combat capability quickly increased through Soul Absorption. In just half a month, her Ona grew by more than 400.

In this period, Han Xiao fought a few times. His Spirit Barrier and the Enchantments on his body decreased the growth rate of the Soul Embryo, but the size of the Soul Embryo still grew from four percent to nine percent.

However, many army players had already reached Grade B, and these people started to use Experience to learn Knowledges. In this half a month, Han Xiao finally gained enough Experience to level up to above level 220.

Han Xiao stopped the traveling, touched Feidin, and hastily locked himself inside the training room.

As Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at his total Experience, he smiled with satisfaction.

After seven years, he was finally at the doorstep of another Promotion.

Without hesitation, he threw the Experience into leveling up.

[Apostle Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.25.

+240 Energy, +3 STR, +4 DEX, +5 END, +10 INT.

You have received 8 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

After leveling up twice consecutively, his level was now level 220 and at Promotion.

The Promotion mission popped up on the interface; this time, Han Xiao did not even look at it.

The Mission Completion Cards that he had been hoarding for seven years had now finally come into use!

Use [Mission Completion Card]? [Confirm/Cancel]

"Confirm."

You have used [Mission Completion Card]!

[Edge of Death]… completed!

[Level 220 Promotion Mission completed!

Promotion successful!

END Bonus increased! 1 END = 175 Health = 185 Stamina.]

His Endurance bonus increased by thirty after this Promotion, five more than the previous Promotion.

A hot stream flowed out from his heart and quickly circulated his entire body. Every cell in his body became tremendously more active; he could clearly feel his increased life force.

Han Xiao focused and looked at the interface notification—this Promotion also included a Race Evolution.

He had just got some luck from Feidin earlier. He was hoping to get some good options.

You have taken another step on the path of evolution. You have ascended in the hierarchy of life. Your genes have reformed. You're closer to another new beginning of life…

Race Detected: Void Distorter (Human Form)

Randomly drawing 9 matching evolutionary directions…

Drawing complete!

Please choose one of the following 9 options for your Race Evolution. Warning! The evolution process is irreversible. Please choose carefully! [Appendix—Evolution Path Feature Descriptions]

[Void Rainbow (Force Field Form)]—38% Compatibility

[Void Jumper (Mutated Form)]—44% Compatibility

[Void Spirit (Spirit Form)]—28% Compatibility

[Multi-Dimensional Shadow (Mind Signal Form)]—23% Compatibility

[Void Executioner (Human Form)]—71% Compatibility

[Magomado Blade (Human Form)]—57% Compatibility

[Void Star Pursuer (Human Form)]—75% Compatibility

[High Concentration Void Dragon Hybrid (Human Form)]—66% Compatibility

[Saint—Galaxy Human Race (Gene Limiter Removed)]—54% Compatibility

Looking at the nine options before him, Han Xiao felt a headache coming on.

Not because these options were not good, but because they were too good!

He was in a pickle.

As he had once consumed a Void Lord Core, Han Xiao had skipped an entire evolution stage. Without that, the options that had appeared would have been on the same level as Void Distorter.

However, many options were evolution paths that were higher than Void Distorter.

First, Han Xiao ignored the first four options. Those four options were not Human Forms and all had very low Compatibilities. What he was having trouble choosing from were the remaining five options.

[Void Star Pursuer] was the direct evolution for Void Distorter, a Universe Life Form that fed on universal radiation and Fixed Star energy. [Void Executioner] was more combat-focused and belonged to the upper-middle class of the Void Life system.

'Magomado' was a Void Lord that was recorded in history. It modified strong Void warriors through Void Energy and created special elite soldiers, which were called the [Magomado Blades]. They were extremely strong.

[High Concentration Void Dragon Hybrid] should be the evolution path brought by the Void Dragon Pith that he had once consumed. Han Xiao was not very clear on the ultimate result of this evolution path. Could it be that the Void Dragon genes would take over his genes and turn him into a Void Dragon or some kind of mutant?

The last option [Saint—Galaxy Human Race] was one of the end points for the Galaxy Human Race evolution chain. The removal of Gene Limiter was very tempting; he would gain a ton of attributes from it.

However, compared to the Void Life options, which still had evolution potential, Han Xiao was not very tempted to choose this. Most of the evolution paths would remove his Gene Limiter at the end point, and the Void Life chain was no exception.

"Which one should I choose?" Han Xiao walked back and forth in hesitation.

As he was closer to Beyond Grade A, this might be his last Race Evolution chance before Beyond Grade A, so he was extremely cautious.

"In terms of combat capability increase, Saint—Galaxy Human Race is the best, followed by Magomado Blade. In terms of potential, Void Star Pursuer is the best. Void Executioner is a balanced option between the two. As for High Concentration Void Dragon Hybrid, the subsequent evolutions of this chain shouldn't be very suitable for me…"

After pondering for a while, Han Xiao once again decided to focus on potential. He hesitated between the Void Star Pursuer and Void Executioner.

The evolution direction of the Executioner would lead to Void Lord and Void Duke, while the Star Pursuer developed toward Void Precursor and Void Archangel. Both had their specialties.

"Racial Talents have minimal effects on my combat capability. Choosing something with better long-term potential is more suitable for me…"

Han Xiao took a deep breath and made his decision.

Selection complete.

Undergoing Race Evolution… Evolution complete.

Your race has been changed to: [Void Star Pursuer (Human Form)]. Your molecular structure has been improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed, and adaptability enhanced.

Your potential aptitude has been improved!

You have received bonus attributes: +154 STR, +179 DEX, +323 END, +188 INT, +120 MYS, +70 CHA, +3760 Energy. Energy Level bonus attributes have been changed!

Han Xiao's senses exploded!

As if his soul left his body, his mind slowly ascended while his body descended. It was like his body and soul were separated, but in reality, they were more tightly connected than before.

His senses seemed to have extended indefinitely, exceeding this Star System, this Star Cluster, and this Star Field. It was as if he saw the entire universe in an instant.

Although this was just an illusion, it was almost real, and it made him experience extremely high dimensional vision for an instant.

The next moment, Han Xiao's senses were pulled right back to his body.

In extreme pain, his body structure was quickly changing. Through the changes, Han Xiao's senses became more and more sensitive. He even gained a few more senses and could 'see' the world in more ways than before.

Although everything before him remained unchanged, they felt completely different in his senses.

Whoosh!

Finally, the pain retreated. Han Xiao took a deep breath. The air he exhaled consisted of extremely tiny energy crystals flashing in a dim blue-gray light.

The moment the Race Evolution finished, Han Xiao took out a mirror immediately and checked if anything weird had grown out of his body.

Hair… still dense.

Face… still familiarly handsome.

Body… hmm, great.

Tail… nonexistent, fortunately.

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. Although he was human no more, he still hoped that he looked like one out of aesthetic reasons.

After checking himself from head to toe thoroughly three more times, Han Xiao then opened the interface again and spent the rest of his Experience on leveling up.

After his Promotion, the Experience needed to level up increased by a considerable amount once again. He only leveled up once.

As a Universe Life Form, the Star Pursuer had an extremely strong physique, so he gained plenty of bonus attributes from this Race Evolution.

He opened the interface and looked at his own attributes.

Level: 221

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Void Star Pursuer (Human Form)

Attributes: 810 STR, 1316 DEX, 1658 END, 3455 INT, 654 MYS, 284 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 24

Potential Points: 15

Health: 456,060

Stamina: 382,120

Energy: 35,530 [Lv.13]

[Lv.13 Energy bonus attributes: +279 STR, +374 DEX, +466 END, +544 INT, +308 MYS, +50,520 Maximum Stamina, +467% Machinery Affinity (Super Electromagnetic Sense)]

Energy Rank: 29,277

Grade: A+

Grade A Bonuses: +15 END, +12 All Resistances. +15% Highest Attribute , +8% Other Attributes, +80 Free Attribute Points, +10 Potential Points

Remark: Hello, Tank; bye, Tank.

This amount of health points was nauseating to look at even for himself.

Other than the bonus attributes from the Race Evolution, he also gained a few hundred attributes from the Lv.13 Energy Rank after his energy surpassed 30,000.

The effects of this Promotion were considerable. He was once again closer to a Beyond Grade A.

After not experiencing the satisfaction of increased strength for seven whole years, Han Xiao only had one feeling.

Awesome!

He entered his mental territory to take a look at the Soul Embryo. Its growth had decreased from nine percent to less than one percent!

"Solid, how very solid." Han Xiao chuckled.

You want to be born, sub-personality? Your only ending is miscarriage!

After checking through his attributes, Han Xiao looked at the new Racial Talents that he had gained after the Race Evolution.

Chapter 736: Plans of Expansion

Void Star Pursuer was the most direct path of evolution. Some of his old talents were kept and others were strengthened.

For example, [Advanced Void Travel] was changed to [Void Dimension Jump], and it was no longer a short-ranged blink skill.

Void Star Pursuer was a Void life form and could travel through space without relying on any equipment. It was able to distort the Void Dimension through its abilities and alter spacetime. As such, a Void Star Pursuer was able to remain in the Void Dimension for a very long time, and this skill was like a divine skill for escaping.

[Void Distortion] was changed to [Strengthened Void Distortion]. Its strength increased and cooldown decreased.

[Void Molt] was strengthened slightly, but the name of the skill remained unchanged. [Void Ripple] had disappeared.

Of the four old talents, three were kept.

He had two new talents, which were the core abilities of a Void Star Pursuer.

[Radiation Absorption]. The Void Star Pursuer was able to absorb radiation from the universe to strengthen its own body. This was a special ability of universe life forms.

The first use of this talent was to transform Han Xiao into a universe life form. He was now able to survive in the universe without the aid of any equipment and would be like a fish in water.

The second use of it was to allow his cells to absorb radiation in the universe and increase his attributes permanently. The actual effects of the skill had yet to be tested, and Han Xiao was not sure about its efficiency and if there was an upper limit.

No matter what, this is a new and stable growth path and also the talent with the greatest potential. The universe was filled with an endless supply of radiation, and it was akin to a buffet for him.

His other new talent was called [Cosmic Environmental Adaptation]. The environment of the universe was extremely harsh and filled with radiation and nanoparticles. For a universe life form to survive in such a harsh environment, their bodies need to be extremely adaptable and have a high level of defense. For example, the Interstellar Beasts that Han Xiao had once killed had skin thick to the point it could make one despair.

This talent molded Han Xiao's body into that of a universe life form and provided him with increased defense, physical resistance, and elemental resistance.

Han Xiao tested it a bit and realized that he was twice as tanky as before.

It could be said that this talent was most suitable for him to become a meat shield.

"The talents of a Void Star Pursuer lean toward support and defense. It is extremely well rounded and suited for my combat style."

Han Xiao was very satisfied with the talents of the Void Star Pursuer.

After understanding the changes of his Promotion, Han Xiao had time to think about other problems.

Han Xiao had waited a full seven years for the level 220 promotion, and his strength had finally taken another step forward.

Han Xiao estimated that his Beyond Grade A barrier would be around level 240, and despite being happy about his promotion, he knew that this was only one of the obstacles that he had overcome. He still had a journey to complete.

After reaching level 220, the amount of experience he needed to level up had shot up again to a sky-high number. It would be difficult for a million players to support him.

After all, Skill Impartation and class knowledge was a one-off purchase, and the majority of the players had learned many different skills. Their expenditure would be lowered after the first round of purchases.

It was time for him to find a new plot of land to grow crops.

The new players from Version 3.0 were undeveloped shoots, and they had a huge thirst for knowledge and skills. This was a new market.

"Planet Aquamarine is already within my grasp, but there are a few more novice planets in the Shattered Star Ring that aren't under my control yet…"

Han Xiao opened the star map and directed his attention to a novice planet called Planet Deirdre. It was located in the Gelock Star Cluster, and it would be the novice planet for all those who joined in Version 3.0 and the smurf accounts of the other players. This was like the opening of a new server to Han Xiao.

The new players who joined in Version 3.0 naturally would not have to go through as much suffering as the players who joined in Version 1.0. They will be able to connect to the galaxy immediately. Planet Deirdre was like a galactic interchange with many resource rich planets located around it. Many large financial groups were also situated in this location. To the new players, there would be plenty of missions for them to complete.

These players who were born outside the battlefield could choose to travel from afar to participate in the secret war or explore on their own and use the ample experience provided in Version 3.0 to catch up in terms of level. They also had a third option… to join another Main Storyline mission.

The Crimson Tide was the main theme of Version 3.0, and the secret war was one of the Main Storyline missions. There were various different events in the other Star Clusters as well. As for the players on Planet Deirdre, the large storyline that they would come in contact with was the Mercenary League storyline.

This organization was the one that the Sky Ring Army and other large mercenary groups had requested Han Xiao to set up and lead. They all felt strongly about the chaos in the Shattered Star Ring and thus gathered all the mercenary groups in the Shattered Star Ring to form a super-sized mercenary group called 'Shattered Star Ring Mercenary League' or just Mercenary League for short.

The Mercenary League had been set up for a few years already, and its effectiveness was extremely obvious. With all the mercenary groups working together, the Mercenary League expanded to cover a few different Star Clusters and accepted the hiring missions from a few hundred different civilizations.

Seven years ago, Han Xiao had participated in this Main Storyline mission. Although he did not pay close attention to the changes in the mercenary world, the Black Star Army was still one of the members in the Mercenary League's council and a member of the upper echelons.

"There isn't a need to worry about Planet Aquamarine. Planet Deirdre will also be easy to manage. I just need to expand the scope of the Black Star Army's operations over."

Planet Deirdre was located in the Gelock Star Cluster, which was outside the army's scope of operations. However, with the status of the Black Star Army, it was extremely easy for them to open a sub-branch on Planet Deirdre.

He had built up the fame of the Black Star Army over three versions, and he had left a deep impression on the players. Thus, he definitely had a huge advantage in hiring new players.

There were plenty of people discussing the Black Star Army on the forums. Even a new player would be curious about the Black Star Army under such circumstances.

Han Xiao's main objective of expanding the Black Star Army was so that he could harvest his crops more efficiently. There was not even a need for him to make a personal appearance for Planet Deirdre.

If he wanted to get to Beyond Grade A quickly, he needed to expand the size of his crops.

In his plans, recruiting the players of Planet Deirdre would be an important mission.

"The army can help me hire new players, and I can prepare for my advancement into Beyond Grade A…"

The shadow of the Tyrant was looming over him. Heber was his greatest obstacle. The moment he became a Beyond Grade A Super, he would have to face this powerful opponent in battle.

This was not as simple as dealing with a doppelganger of EsGod. He would have to face a true Beyond Grade A Super, and the pressure would be completely different!

I have to groom Hila while performing some worthwhile missions, Han Xiao thought to himself.

Because of the Soul Embryo, he had sufficient reason to temporarily pull out from the secret war and complete his own affairs in a low-profile manner.

He did not only have to level up but also needed to find a way to increase his combat capabilities. He needed to make enough preparations and obtain more talents before becoming a Beyond Grade A Super if he wanted to deal with the Tyrant.

Compared to others, this was his greatest advantage. He was able to obtain new talents and increase his strength. He would never face a bottleneck.

If only I could obtain a Universal Treasure… Han Xiao lamented.

He was truly envious of Psyker's Evolution Cube, but it was a pity that he would not have the chance to borrow it. He also wanted to obtain a Universal Treasure that belonged solely to him.

In his previous life, the players had many records of Universal Treasures, and in the later versions, there were even players who had their own Universal Treasures. However, most of the Universal Treasures were still in unknown locations, and those Universal Treasures with known locations would be heavily guarded.

If he was able to easily obtain a Universal Treasure, Han Xiao would have long gone to get one.

In his memory, there were three famous Universal Treasures in the Shattered Star Ring. They were in the hands of the three Star Cluster civilizations. Psyker's Evolution Cube was one of the Universal Treasures that he had heard of before but had very little information on.

Currently, Han Xiao only knew of a single Universal Treasure that he might be able to obtain.

It should still be lying silently in the ruins of a civilization.

Its location was in the Flickering World!

What a pity… It's still too far out of my reach. Han Xiao felt a great pity.

At the very least, he would have to wait for the Crimson Dynasty to grasp control over the Flickering World and set up a stargate before he would have the chance to obtain that Universal Treasure. He would not even be able to reach the Flickering World currently.

Thus, he had no choice but to find more talents to increase his strength.

He would still have to think about the exact details of the plan. At this moment, Han Xiao only wanted to relax. He then opened the door of the cultivation chamber and returned to the cabin of the spaceship.

Hila was currently training bitterly in the real combat training room, and only Feidin and Aurora were present in the cabin. They were chatting away merrily like best friends. Upon hearing the approaching footsteps, both of them turned around to take a look.

"Chen Xing, Feidin let you out again?" Feidin's actions were currently extremely lady-like, and it was obvious that Chen Xing was the one controlling the body.

Chen Xing snorted, and she did not wish to talk to Han Xiao. She returned the body back to Feidin, and the aura of her body changed greatly. Feidin regained control of his body and said, "She seemed to be very afraid of you."

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "I've been meaning to ask. Since both of you are sharing a single body, does it mean that both of your biological needs are the same?"

Feidin coughed awkwardly.

"Since both of you can be considered as one, does this mean that it is impossible for both of you to mate?"

Han Xiao laughed. Did this mean that they were forced into having platonic love?

"Must we talk about this? Can we talk about something else?" Feidin felt his head ache.

Aurora blinked and interrupted him. "I am actually pretty curious, too."

Feidin was extremely sociable, and he was already very familiar with Aurora. It was mainly because Chen Xing really liked Aurora.

"Alright…" Feidin replied helplessly. "Both of us are Psychics. We can simulate our biological needs… cough, and organs. We can then use our mental bodies to mate."

My goodness.

Isn't this the same logic as having a wet dream?

Mating in their heads‽

Is this the highest level of being a lecher‽

Han Xiao had a weird expression on his face, and he pointed at Feidin.

"I never expected you to be a pervert."

"Shut up!" Chen Xing hollered with her face flushed red before disappearing back into Feidin's body.

Feidin then shook his head helplessly. "She is ignoring me now. I'm dead."

So what if she ignores you. She is living in your body and won't be able to run anywhere. In any case, both of you share the same appearance…

Aurora's body was swaying from laughing too much, and she laughed to the point tears could be seen at the corner of her eyes. She then said, "Right, I sensed your life force strengthening greatly again."

"You finally broke through your bottleneck?" Feidin's eyes lit up, and he was overjoyed.

Black Star's strength had remained stagnant over the past seven years, and he had finally made an advancement. It was definitely great news.

"You can say that." Han Xiao nodded.

"That's great. We still have hope if this is the case," Feidin exclaimed with joy.

He had been extremely worried for Han Xiao ever since he heard Austin's words. At this moment, he could not help but heave a sigh of relief.

Han Xiao then chatted with the two for a while before returning to his room.

Taking out his communicator, he sent the coordinates of Planet Deirdre to Sylvia and sent her to set up a new branch. For him to send her over to take care of this matter, Sylvia knew that this meant that Han Xiao placed a huge importance on this matter.

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao sent out a message to Bennett to check on the situation on Planet Aquamarine.

It has been ten years since he last returned.

Chapter 737: Changes

On Aquamarine Federation Mother Planet, inside a classroom of the Basic School of the Federation, many seven to eight year old students were reading the textbook out loud with the teacher.

"… Galaxy Calendar Year 694, the movement that would then be called 'The Great Government Unification' occurred. Under Black Star's influence, the structure of society changed drastically. The governments formally known as the Six Nations were replaced by the current Aquamarine Federation. This was the turning point of Planet Aquamarine's civilization progress…

"Black Star, original name Han Xiao, born on Planet Aquamarine, former member of the Germinal Organization who later stepped onto the righteous path. He is now the protector of the Planet Aquamarine Civilization and has the highest veto power in the Federation Council. He guided the drastic civilization changes in the last twenty years, giving us the entrance ticket to galactic societies. Up till now, the Black Star Army is still working closely with the federation…"

A boy with freckles on his face raised his hand and asked, "Is Black Star still alive?"

The classroom burst into laughter.

"Of course, Nero. Black Star has a very long life span. Even after we all die of old age, he will still be alive." The teacher smiled and nodded.

"I—I thought only those who passed away would be known as great men…" The student called Nero's face blushed.

The teacher shook his head and said, "Black Star is a close confidant to the federation chairman, Bennett. That statue in the Central Garden was built by Bennett for Black Star. If you're curious, you can log into the galactic internet and search for Black Star. There's information accessible to the public there. He's the strongest person that stepped out of Planet Aquamarine. He's the pride of our entire planet."

The lessons in the afternoon quickly ended, and the students headed back home. Nero followed the crowd and came to the school gate.

The school was located in the middle of a tall building. When looking around the wide square from the school gate, the entire city could be seen. Tall buildings stood next to each other like a fictional forest of metal, and anti-gravity suspended vehicles traveled along the planned routes.

In the past ten years, Planet Aquamarine had always been in continuous contact with galactic technology. Some common devices in the universe were gradually being integrated into the daily lives of the people. Planet Aquamarine had now built many cities with advanced technology. The styles of the cities were also gradually changing under the influence of galactic financial groups.

It was prospering.

Various private anti-gravity suspended vehicles waited outside the school for their children. Nero boarded one with no license, crossed the city, and entered the government building of the Aquamarine Federation.

Nero followed a secretary-looking man into an office, where Bennett was reading documents. Compared to ten years ago, he had more wrinkles and was gradually showing signs of aging. As he heard the sound and looked up to see Nero, he smiled.

"School ended? Sit down first. After I'm done with these, I'll take you to eat."

"Yes, Dad." Nero put down his small school bag and sat on the sofa obediently. He shook his legs and looked around.

Ten years ago, with Han Xiao's permission, Bennett had become the Aquamarine Federation Chairman and completed the unification of the governments on the planet. After the initial turbulent stages, Planet Aquamarine had begun its stable development while recovering from the damage suffered before.

As peace was perfectly achieved on his mother planet, Bennett's goal was accomplished. As the federation chairman, he needed to form a family. Thus, he got married and had a child. He was a Pugilist, after all, so his physique was more than good enough to carry out the process of creating a human. Nero was his son.

"Dad, the teacher told us about Black Star's story today," Nero said excitedly.

"Oh? What did he say?" Bennett was rather interested.

Nero repeated what he could remember with his innocent voice and then asked curiously, "Dad, is Black Star your friend?"

"Yes, I've known him for close to twenty years." Bennett was feeling a little nostalgic.

"Is he really that amazing? More amazing than you, Dad?"

Nero's eyes opened wide. In his mind, his father, the federation chairman, was the most amazing person in the world.

"He's much more amazing than me." Bennett laughed.

Beep beep!

This time, the communicator rang.

As Bennett saw who was calling, he was a little surprised. He waved at Nero.

"Come here. Aren't you very curious about Black Star? Come and look at him."

After placing Nero on his knees, Bennett then picked up the video call. Han Xiao's face appeared on the screen.

"It's been a long time, almost ten years." Bennett smiled.

"It sure has." Han Xiao nodded. As he saw Nero, his eyes sparkled. "This child is…"

"Hmm, this is my kid, Nero."

Bennett smiled and rubbed Nero's head. "Come on, that's your uncle."

"Hello, Uncle," Nero greeted obediently.

Han Xiao was surprised. "When did you get married? Why didn't you tell me?"

"You're so busy. I didn't want to disturb you for something so small."

"What are you talking about? We go way back. How could you not even tell me about such good news? I'm very disappointed." Han Xiao showed a dissatisfied expression.

Bennett chuckled and did not mind it.

Although he did not say anything, he knew that Han Xiao was on a different level compared to him now.

The daily matters of Planet Aquamarine were undoubtedly small matters to Han Xiao. Bennett did not want to disturb him for these trivial matters, so they contacted each other less and less.

"You're the person in the textbooks…" Nero stared at Han Xiao with curiosity.

"Textbooks?" Han Xiao wondered.

Bennett smiled and explained.

Han Xiao laughed. He did not expect to be written about in history textbooks.

This feeling of being remembered by people… actually felt quite good.

After chatting for a while, Bennett suddenly said, "I'm thinking about letting Nero be your godson. What do you think?"

Han Xiao was a little surprised. He nodded. With his relationship with Bennett, he was willing to be this kid's godfather.

Bennett patted Nero and said, "Quick, greet your godfather."

"God… father." Nero's tone was a little stiff. To him, Han Xiao was a stranger whom he had never met before, so addressing him as 'Godfather' was rather difficult.

Bennett smiled and let go of Nero, telling him to go aside to play.

"What's the matter?"

"Nothing, I just wanted to ask about the situation on Planet Aquamarine," Han Xiao replied.

Planet Aquamarine was one of the birthplaces of players that sent manpower to the Black Star Army continuously. It was equivalent to his logistics base and was very important to him.

Before opening new leek fields, he wanted to check the situation of the old one.

Bennett nodded and explained the current situation of Planet Aquamarine in detail.

Thanks to the Black Star Army, Planet Aquamarine was now shifting from a planet surface civilization to a galactic civilization and had been trying to colonize the nearby uninhabited planets.

A large number of new players had started in Version 3.0 on Planet Aquamarine and were recruited by the Black Star Army subdivision.

Overall, the situation was great.

Han Xiao was quite satisfied. "You've done a great job. You don't have to worry about Planet Aquamarine anymore. Do you want to come to the galaxy?"

If he remembered correctly, Bennett had some longing for the universe, so Han Xiao proposed to invite him.

However, to his surprise, Bennett shook his head and rejected him.

"I have decided to stay in the Aquamarine Federation. The galaxy… I don't want to go there anymore."

"Why? I remember you were…"

"I have new wishes now. The Aquamarine Federation is still small. I hope to help it grow and devote the rest of my life to it." Bennett smiled with deep wrinkles. "I'm old and have a family and a kid now. I don't want to fight and kill anymore. I'm very satisfied with my current life."

Upon hearing what Bennett said, Han Xiao did not want to persuade him anymore.

Everyone had different goals. Bennett had spent the first half of his life in wars and chaos, so now that he had found somewhere he belonged, he had a home where he could feel at peace. Han Xiao chose to respect that.

"Understood."

"Actually, I have one more thing to ask from you," Bennett said.

"What is it?"

"I'm still very worried about Nero. He has a very bright future and shouldn't be staying here with me. After I pass away, I hope you can bring him along your side, take care of him, and raise him." Bennett's eyes were filled with fatherly love.

"What? Why are you planning these things out of nowhere‽" Han Xiao felt numbness on his scalp.

"After all, I'm different from you. My life span is finite, and I don't know when I will die. So, I wanted to tell you this as early as possible." Bennett smiled wholeheartedly. "Can you promise me that?"

"No problem, I have enough money to raise one person." Han Xiao raised his brows and made a joke to ease the atmosphere. "After you die, do you want me to 'take care' of your widow as well?"

Bennett's mouth twitched. "No need to trouble you for that."

…

After chatting casually for more than half an hour, only then did Han Xiao end the call. His smile dissipated, and he sighed.

Not everyone had a long life span like him.

Getting old and dying was the common fate of normal people.

Bennett was getting older. Sooner or later, he would pass away.

No matter what, he did feel quite sorrowful.

Nonetheless, even if he passed away one day, the cause that he loved and had devoted his life to would remain.

"The Aquamarine Federation…"

Han Xiao nodded.

With his protection, the Planet Aquamarine Civilization would go much, much farther than it did in his previous life…

…

With the popularity of the previous two versions, Version 3.0 became an exploding period for new players. According to statistics, there were more than ten million new players entering the game currently, and it was still growing.

Due to the fact that China had won the championship of the previous Pro League, the Shattered Star Ring attracted the most players. In just three months after Version 3.0 was released, there were already close to two million new players.

Half a month later, in the Gelock Star Cluster, Planet Deirdre…

The public airport hall had become a square for the players. Some opened stores, some asked to team up, and some provided boosting services. All sorts of players were gathered there.

It was noisy and crowded. The wall was transparent. The entire Planet Deirdre surface could be seen from there as well as the beautiful sky filled with stars.

As a galactic transit station, there were a lot of job opportunities on Planet Deirdre. Over the three months, the million or so new players had leveled up extremely quickly because of the Version 3.0 mission reward standard. Their level average was now above level 30, and some had already reached more than level 40.

Unlike the Version 1.0 Planet Aquamarine players, the players on Planet Deirdre became galactic residents as soon as they were born. Their information channels were rich, and they could search for galactic information easily.

After exploring for three months, the Planet Deirdre players found many ways to develop themselves.

At this time, among the boisterous public airport hall, there was one team that was discussing their future direction.

"We should join the Odegen Financial Group and help them fight the nearby galactic pirate groups. This is a planet's main storyline. It's definitely the best choice."

"What kind of future can joining a financial group give? It's better to become freelance mercenaries. Those senior player guides on the forums all say that becoming a mercenary is the best."

"I've done the research. The biggest mercenary group in the Shattered Star Ring now is the Mercenary League. I heard some people triggered new main storylines there. If we're going to be mercenaries, we have to join this organization."

"Then we might as well go to Colton and join the Black Star Army to participate in the secret war main storyline."

"The Black Star Army is good indeed, but flights between Star Clusters are rather expensive."

"I don't think we should go there. We have new main storyline missions here. There's no reason to travel there."

"How about we do something challenging? Killing and crimes are always profitable. Let's become galactic pirates…"

"Hehe, you think we can afford a spaceship?"

"Are you stupid? Since we're going to become galactic pirates, we can rob one if we can't afford it."

This player team discussed the matter for some time when they suddenly realized that the noisy environment around them had suddenly become quiet.

They turned around with shock.

In the entire hall, be it players or NPCs, everyone was looking up with their mouths wide open and their faces filled with shock.

What's going on?

This player team looked up as well. When they saw what was outside the transparent ceiling, their eyes widened immediately.

An enormous armed satellite fortress appeared out of nowhere and filled the entire field outside the transparent ceiling. The size of this public airport was not even one twentieth of this armed satellite fortress!

Thousands of battleships guarded the satellite as it slowly approached, stopping in the outer orbit of Planet Deirdre.

The armor of these battleships all had the same symbol. For those players that often visited the forums, they recognized the symbol immediately.

It was the insignia of the Black Star Army!

The Black Star Army had moved an entire satellite subdivision there!

The million or so new players in the airport were in disbelief and at a loss.

Isn't the Black Star Army fighting a war in another Star Cluster? Why are they here‽

Chapter 738: Purple Crystal's Thoughts

The Black Star Army was already a famous organization in the Shattered Star Ring, and the sudden appearance of a satellite base caused a huge commotion on Planet Deirdre.

The Gelock Star Cluster had nothing to do with the secret war. The various financial groups located on Planet Deirdre and new players were extremely puzzled about the intentions of the Black Star Army.

A couple of battleships then left the dock and welcomed the arrival of the Black Star Army satellite base with caution.

The various financial groups immediately sent out a communication request, and they all wanted to talk to the commander of the fleet.

Very quickly, their requests were approved, and all the financial groups were pulled into a conference chat. Sylvia's appearance then appeared on all their communicators.

It's her! Black Star's Chief Administrative Official!

As one of the important officers of the Black Star Army, Sylvia's fame was not low, and many financial groups recognized her. Seeing such an important figure leading the group, they could not help but feel uneasy and felt that the Black Star Army was scheming in some way.

"I am Sylvia, the commander of this fleet." Sylvia nodded and introduced herself.

"Why did you descend without informing us? Are you planning to go against the rules of the merchant world and snatch the business on Planet Deirdre?" one of the financial groups who seemed to be the leader of the group asked with an unfriendly tone.

The Odegen Financial Group was one of the largest financial groups on Planet Deirdre, and the one speaking was the person in charge, Carver.

The others shared the same thoughts as Carver. Planet Deirdre was like a treasure bowl to them, and they did not wish for others to snatch a piece of the pie from them.

Sylvia smiled and said, "Please do not misunderstand anything. Although our Black Star Army is an armed organization, we will not use force to coerce any legal financial groups. Furthermore, your operations on Planet Deirdre do not attract us in the slightest. All of you can be at ease."

Hearing that, the faces of Carver and the others became unnatural. They treated Planet Deirdre as a treasure bowl, but the benefits from the planet were no more than peanuts to the Black Star Army. Sylvia had very obviously stated that they were not even interested in the little benefits of the planet, and this made Carver slightly embarrassed.

"Then, what is the purpose of your visit?" Carver asked with doubt. "You've even shifted an entire satellite base over. If I don't remember incorrectly, the Gelock Star Cluster isn't part of the secret war."

Sylvia cleared her throat and said in a loud voice, "As an important member of the Mercenary League, our Black Star Army has decided to expand our mercenary operations toward the Gelock Star Cluster. Planet Deirdre is the planet that we have chosen to set up a branch on. We will take over the mercenary operations in this entire region, and all of you can treat us as an agency for the Mercenary League. If any of you need manpower in the future, you can make an application with us."

The eyes of Carver and the others lit up. If the Black Star Army did not interfere in their operations on Planet Deirdre and only expanded their mercenary operations, there would only be benefits for them.

If a reliable mercenary group was set up on Planet Deirdre, the security of the region would be improved, and more people would be attracted to the planet.

Furthermore, with the Black Star Army around, they would not have to find other insignificant mercenary groups, and their safety would be ensured.

Currently, the Mercenary League was on their way to monopolizing the entire mercenary world in the Shattered Star Ring, and Carver felt that the Black Star Army was only expanding the operations of the Mercenary League as one of their members.

"We understand. We don't have any opinions." Carver was no longer as wary as before.

Sylvia then continued. "Very good. I have something to request. I hope that all those present here will make use of your influence to announce the news of our Black Star Army setting up a branch in this place. We will be able to open up this market very quickly with all of your help."

As an organization that came from the outside, even if the Black Star Army was a huge conglomerate, Sylvia would still ease up their relationship with the local organizations. This would help to make their operations more efficient.

Carver began to hesitate upon hearing that.

At this moment, Sylvia added, "Of course, we will provide all of you with a discount should any of you need mercenaries in the future."

"Don't worry. We will definitely help you with the announcement." Carver immediately agreed without hesitation.

Everyone on Planet Deirdre could see the gigantic satellite fortress floating outside the atmosphere of their planet whenever they lifted their head.

Just as everyone was filled with fear over the appearance of the satellite fortress, the financial groups made a public announcement that the Black Star Army had gone to Planet Deirdre with friendly intentions and had a cooperative relationship with the different financial groups.

The moment the announcement was made, everyone heaved a sigh of relief and was overjoyed.

The security situation in the galactic transit station was truly a problem, and the Black Star Army might be able to improve this situation.

Of course, not everyone welcomed the Black Star Army. For example, some small mercenary groups on Planet Deirdre felt immense pressure.

They all knew that their lives in the future would not be good, and all the mercenary missions would be snatched up by the Black Star Army.

However, the Black Star Army quickly released news that they were recruiting manpower and gave priority to the local mercenaries.

An endless stream of individuals immediately responded, especially the players located on Planet Deirdre.

The Black Star Army was a hot topic of discussion on the forums, and even the new players had a certain degree of understanding toward the benefits, storyline, and events of the Black Star Army.

The Black Star Army had already accompanied the players for two whole versions. With the players adding on their imagination and the legends of the Black Star Army becoming a part of the Galaxy Chronicles, many of the new players naturally felt a sense of belonging toward the Black Star Army.

In the eyes of many new players, the Black Star Army was like a player army in the Shattered Star Ring.

Because of their location, many of them did not wish to travel all the way to the Colton Star Cluster. Since the Black Star Army had expanded to the Gelock Star Cluster, most of the players no longer hesitated and joined.

The players who were hesitating were mainly concerned about the Main Storyline mission. The way they saw it, they would have to participate in the secret war storyline if they chose to join the Black Star Army. However, they did not wish to give up the freedom to explore other storylines.

However, after listening to the explanation of the other players who had joined the army, they realized that they were completely wrong. They needed to file for an application if they wanted to join the secret war. If they were not willing to join the secret war, the army would not force them, and they could choose not to trigger that storyline.

The players who did not join the war would be ordinary mercenaries in the Black Star Army, and they can choose the missions that they wanted to do while enjoying the benefits of the army.

Furthermore, they were surprised to realize that the Black Star Army was an upper echelon of the Mercenary League. They would be able to trigger the Main Storyline mission of the Mercenary League as well, so joining the Black Star Army was akin to giving them the choice between two Main Storyline missions.

There were some other players who wanted to participate in the Main Storyline mission on Planet Deirdre—helping the Odegen Financial Group chase away galactic pirates in the vicinity.

However, they were shocked to realize that the Odegen Financial Group had actually cancelled this mission. The Main Storyline mission of Planet Deirdre had mysteriously disappeared!

After asking around, the players finally understood what had happened. After all the galactic pirates in the vicinity of Planet Deirdre caught wind of the Black Star Army's arrival, they immediately abandoned all their bases and escaped.

These galactic pirates were all frightened away by the Black Star Army!

There was not a need to even hesitate.

In just three days, over ninety percent of the players on Planet Deirdre had chosen to join the Black Star Army.

The benefits of the Black Star Army were truly too alluring to the new players. Not only was there a large amount of equipment and tools, they also had a full set of basic and advanced knowledge. There was no need for them to farm for NPC favorability all around to learn that knowledge.

The current level and needs of the players were akin to the players in Version 1.0, but they could enjoy the benefits of Version 3.0. This was an irresistible temptation that the players could not reject.

As Sylvia recruited the players on Planet Deirdre, Han Xiao's interface received all the benefits.

The first thing all those new players did was learn knowledge.

He had the reward from the [Bloodline] mission, a Political Asset, and received a thirty percent bonus for experience. His experience pool, which had dried up, was very quickly replenished, and he had sufficient experience to level up once again.

After expanding his crops, the speed of harvesting experience had increased greatly. According to this efficiency, level 240 was not too far away.

The players in the army could be split into two different groups. The first were those who had reached Grade B and the second were the new players who had an average level of 20 to 30.

While the spending power of the new players could not match the old players, they had a huge hidden demand. Han Xiao decided to allow them to remain on Planet Deirdre and not force them to participate in the secret war. With their current strength, completing recruitment missions might be more efficient than participating in the secret war.

The Mercenary League's Main Storyline mission would be more suitable for those newbies.

Han Xiao then thought to himself, The player market has doubled, and all these new players will have to learn all the various knowledge from scratch. However, their levels are still low, so I must groom them slowly.

Class Knowledge was a necessity, and the new players would have to learn them eventually. He was not in a rush at all.

Ring ring!

His communicator suddenly rang; it was Ralph.

"Black Star, I heard that you set up a branch in the Gelock Star Cluster," Ralph inquired.

"You sure receive news very quickly. Do you have any issues?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Cough cough, I am only asking out of curiosity." Ralph coughed dryly.

In truth, Purple Crystal hoped that the Black Star Army would always remain in Colton and did not wish for them to expand outward. However, this was not the time to talk about this.

Han Xiao then asked, "Why have you called?"

Ralph's expression then turned solemn, and he said, "It's like this. We received news that the Crimson Dynasty and Federation of Light have come to an initial agreement. We do not have much time left and must speed up our progress."

The negotiations are about to be over?

The secret war would be over when the Crimson Dynasty and Federation of Light completed their negotiations. It was no wonder that Purple Crystal was feeling anxious.

"What is the reaction of Bloodshed Land?"

"They have become more active and sent out all their high-level combatants," Ralph said. "Without your presence to suppress them, we have suffered quite a huge loss."

Han Xiao immediately understood what was going on. Jorde had been misled by him, resulting in such a situation.

"We urgently need you to return to the battlefield. We are planning to launch another large-scale mission. Black Star, we need you to…"

At this moment, Han Xiao interrupted him. "I am sorry. I do not wish to participate in the upcoming mission."

Ralph was stunned. Black Star was an important part of their strategy. If Han Xiao did not want to go, would that not disrupt their entire strategy?

"Why?"

Han Xiao thought for a moment and said, "You should know that regardless of the outcome, Heber definitely won't let me off."

Ralph fell silent. Purple Crystal did indeed know about this but did not inform Han Xiao about it. It was not that they did not care about Han Xiao's life and death. However, the upper echelons were extremely pragmatic and would make use of Han Xiao as much as they could.

Seven years ago, Purple Crystal had recognized Han Xiao's potential and begun to invest in him. However, seven years had gone by, and the upper echelons of Purple Crystal no longer thought that much of his potential after witnessing his growth stagnate.

Although they still placed great importance on him, the thoughts of the upper echelons had changed, and they no longer felt that Han Xiao would become a Beyond Grade A Super.

Purple Crystal would not allow the Tyrant to take revenge on one of their meritorious subjects, but the upper echelons had their own considerations. Although the chances of Black Star becoming a Beyond Grade A Super had been lowered, he was still a peak Calamity Grade Super, and there was still value in roping him in. Thus, they wished for Black Star to seek protection from them when the Tyrant took action. This would improve the relationship between both parties and would be extremely beneficial to the upper echelons.

As for the safety of Black Star, Purple Crystal was not too worried. Black Star had the Dragon Emperor behind him, and their presence was like the icing on the cake. They might also have a chance to form a relationship with Ames because of it.

Han Xiao was not too bothered by this. Both parties were only working together for their respective benefits, and Purple Crystal did not owe him anything. He slowly said, "Thus, I have to think of a way to break past the Calamity Grade bottleneck in this remaining time."

"I understand."

Since Han Xiao had laid his cards out openly, Ralph did not force the matter.

As for the situation in the secret war, Ralph understood it extremely clearly. Purple Crystal knew that they would not be able to chase out all the enemies and would probably lose a portion of their territory near the border. Their retaliation was only an attempt to reduce their losses.

Under such circumstances, Han Xiao's refusal to participate in the war was something that Purple Crystal could accept.

Black Star probably knows this as well and thus made such a request… Ralph thought to himself and felt that Black Star was only finding an excuse.

After remaining stagnant for a full seven years, he did not think that Han Xiao would be able to make a breakthrough in the near future.

However, there was no need for him to spell things out so clearly.

"I will convey your message to the upper echelons," Ralph said. "However, you can choose to be absent, but your Black Star Army must still participate."

"Naturally."

Han Xiao then heaved a sigh of relief after hanging up.

Purple Crystal and Bloodshed Land temporarily would not bother him, and he would be able to pull out of the secret war and find some talents to prepare for Beyond Grade A.

Chapter 739: Guests

Molding Talents were something that could not be obtained easily, and Han Xiao had obtained all his Molding Talents through abnormal means.

Although the [Prey] mission was a good chance to obtain a talent, he had not triggered the next phase of the mission after such a long time. He almost thought that Thousand Shadows had given up on him. However, the mission had not ended, so Han Xiao did not know what was going on. Thus, he naturally could not count on it.

There were many different missions for him to obtain talents in his memories, but the rewards were usually ordinary talents. There were not many rare talents, and Han Xiao had to consider which missions he should do.

He first struck out all the missions outside of the Shattered Star Ring.

Some talents did not really increase his combat capabilities and would only waste his time. He also eliminated those.

After striking out all the missions that he deemed unsuitable, Han Xiao picked a few more valuable missions.

Although the talents from those missions would not be able to cause his combat capability to have an earth-shattering change, it would still increase his combat capability to a certain extent.

I will probably need a few months to complete these missions… The war won't be over so soon, so I should have enough time…

He was currently level 221 and would need to complete a Class Advancement at level 225. He had saved a few Mission Completion Cards during the version update period, and he still had a few leftovers after using one at level 220. Thus, he was only lacking experience points.

The amount of experience needed after level 220 increased exponentially, but with his two plots of crops, he would only need a few months to accumulate enough experience.

He could complete some missions while waiting for his experience to accumulate.

Han Xiao then called Hila, Aurora, and Feidin over to explain his plans to them.

"Right." Han Xiao suddenly thought about something and said to Aurora, "Help me create some recovery medicine. I want to give them to the high-level officers of the army. It should be able to save their lives during a critical moment."

The Bloodshed Land had begun to go all out. In order to prevent the upper echelons of the army from getting injured, he wanted to provide them with some protection. Aurora's life force medicine had a divine effect and was akin to a second life.

Aurora was able to freely control her Esper abilities already, and creating medicine would not cause too much exhaustion.

"No problem!"

Aurora was extremely excited. I can finally be of some help!

Hila originally wanted to persuade her otherwise, but upon seeing Aurora's excited appearance, she chose to remain silent.

Since it was Han Xiao's request and was not too difficult, she decided to just let Aurora do as she wished. She had personally witnessed Aurora's growth, and she was no longer as overprotective as before.

Han Xiao spent a day settling all that he needed to before taking the three on his journey to farm for talents.

…

Three black, curved spaceships exited the desolate universe belt and entered the Shattered Star Ring from some deserted region.

In the cabin of the leading spaceship, Colin looked out of the window and spat out a rotten fruit from his mouth. His mouth was filled with purple juice from the fruit.

"After almost six years of flying, we are finally here."

As he said that, he slapped the defrost button on the spaceship.

Psh…

A few dozen low temperature life sustaining chambers began to defrost, and the doors to those chambers opened. Cold air filled the entire spaceship, and many people of different heights and races walked out of the chambers.

"We slept for three years?"

"Is it time to change shift, or have we reached?"

Those fellows who had just woken up from their sleep put on their clothes and walked toward the cockpit.

Upon hearing the sound of footsteps, Colin pointed to the star map without turning back. "We have arrived in the Shattered Star Ring. All of you adjust your bodies quickly so that we don't delay the mission of our boss."

"Don't worry, I just need to suck some blood to recover," a tall, skinny man said while licking his lips.

"Baron Orozen, don't blame me for throwing you out of the spaceship if you dare touch my subordinates."

"Why should I listen to you?" the pale-faced Orozen sneered coldly.

"Because I am the captain His Excellency EsGod appointed. Or do you want to fight?" Colin glared ferociously.

Orozen chuckled eerily before shrugging his shoulders to show that he would submit.

Colin then snorted and said, "You'd better behave in a low-profile manner. I remember that you were a fugitive who escaped from the Shattered Star Ring. I don't what your stupidity from the past to expose our location before the completion of the mission."

"That bounty was over sixty years ago. It may have been removed already," Orozen replied indifferently.

Everyone present on those three spaceships were members of Fallen Ark and were wanted criminals from different Star Fields. They had all been sent out to complete a mission in the Shattered Star Ring.

Colin had the nickname 'Corrosive Poison' and was the captain of this team. He had once spread a plaque in many different colonial planets in the Ancient Star Desert, which had resulted in the death of over three billion people. He was a wanted criminal of twenty-three Star System civilizations and two Star Cluster civilizations. He had then joined Fallen Ark and followed EsGod.

Orozen had the nickname 'Baron' and belonged to the blood race. He was another Grade A Super in the team and had hunted in many different Star Fields. He was an extremely ferocious character and was a wanted criminal in five different Star Fields.

Especially the Shattered Star Ring.

He had once eaten a high-level official during the ceremony of a Star System civilization in front of the entire Star System. That incident had caused a huge commotion, and he had joined EsGod after escaping from the Shattered Star Ring.

This group of individuals had set off six years ago and had only just reached the Shattered Star Ring. As wanted criminals, they would not dare to openly use stargates and spent most of their time in the desolate universe belt.

These three 'Light Marten' spaceships were equipped with top grade hyperdrive engines and were created specifically for travel between Star Fields. The ship's highest speed was level 17.89 warp speed. If it travelled within a Star Field at top speed, it would be able to travel from one Star System to another within minutes.

Although the lowest grade among the group was a Grade B Super, they needed to rest in a life sustaining chamber in order to endure the load from travelling at warp speed.

This small team was only able to travel through various Star Fields to arrive at the Shattered Star Ring by relying on a warp speed engine.

One of his subordinates then asked, "Captain, which mission shall we complete first?"

They had two different missions in the Shattered Star Ring.

"Are you an idiot? Of course we'll take care of the easier one first!" Colin replied impatiently. He then opened a file on the holographic screen.

There was information about two individuals in the file, Harrofal and Han Xiao.

They were the two of joint hands to deal with EsGod.

"Harrofal, Grade A Super in the Tyla Civilization, vice principal of the Tyla Mechanic School. He is a researcher.

"Black Star, Han Xiao. The leader of the Black Star Army and ally of Purple Crystal. A Beyond Grade A seed… Eh? This fellow's battle record had been updated again. He is a powerful individual and is said to be one of the top fighters among the Calamity Grade Supers in the Shattered Star Ring."

Orozen smiled calmly upon hearing those words. "Black Star? I never heard of such a character when I was in the Shattered Star Ring. He is no more than a newbie who only appeared recently.

"The Shattered Star Ring is only a remote Star Field," Colin said emotionlessly. "The strength of the Supers in this place cannot be compared to the three Star Fields in the Central Galaxy."

Colin and the others who usually spent their time in the Central Galaxy looked down on the Supers from a remote Star Field like the Shattered Star Ring. As the most ferocious criminals in the galaxy, they were all used to being arrogant, and they did not even place some Beyond Grade A Supers in their sights.

Since seven years ago, EsGod had been muttering about trees every day. They all felt that EsGod's mental illness must have become worse for him to send them to the Shattered Star Ring to find the coordinates of some wormhole.

"Harrofal will have the data that we want, so he is the key target," Colin said. "If we can get the data successfully, we won't have to find Black Star. After all, Harrofal is much easier to deal with than Black Star."

Everyone nodded.

"We can then steal the Evolution Cube after completing our first mission."

Chapter 740: Swaggering through the Novice Village

After a few days of travelling, the Blacklight Stealth arrived at the spot reserved for it at their destination.

The view from inside the porthole showed a planet with green vegetation and yellow earth. Blue oceans could be seen on the planet's surface, but the yellow earth made up the majority.

Aurora stared at the planet curiously.

"Phillip, what sort of planet is this?"

"Database search, hum… Search complete.

"Planet Nalun, sitting in the Star Zone 6 of the Colton Star Cluster in the Shattered Star Ring, the planet's number is S-0706812. It was discovered and recorded by the Galute Civilization. There are signs of civilization within, but they are considered fairly backward, yet to have developed interstellar technology. Observation priority is rated as four, hum…"

Planet Nalun consisted of an indigenous civilization, but their level of science and technology was still quite ancient, without aircraft mounted nuclear cannons, far from the stage of space exploration.

"Why did Han Xiao bring us here then?" Aurora wondered.

"He definitely has his reasons. Just ask him when you see him." Feidin smiled.

At this moment, Han Xiao was not aboard the ship. While the trio were seated in the spaceship, he was streaking through the universe with just his flesh in order to be exposed to the cosmic radiation. This was to obtain attributes through the Void Star Pursuer's talent [Radiation Absorption]. As a result, his travelling speed was slower than theirs.

The spaceship was suspended above Planet Nalun, and before long, the void beside it started to twist and warp. Han Xiao jumped out from the void dimension. He yawned and quickly opened the hatch to fly into the cabin.

Whoosh!

Jumping into the cabin, Han Xiao exhaled a stream of hot air.

The moment he got out of the vacuum environment, his body started to emit white smoke as though he was being cooked.

Because the cells in his body were continuously digesting the cosmic radiation from the universe, his body was like a burning furnace. The surface of his skin was hot enough to even fry eggs.

Opening his interface to take a look, Han Xiao was pretty satisfied.

This is indeed a mid to high levelled evolutionary species. Its talent shows good growth, and as long as enough time is accumulated, the bonus will be considerable.

After some practical tests, Han Xiao understood how the mechanism of [Radiation Absorption] worked.

After evolving into a Void Star Pursuer, his body cells had transformed, and now he possessed the ability to absorb cosmic radiation. If his physical body was exposed to outer space for a period of time, it would trigger [Radiation Absorption], which would permanently increase his Strength, Agility, or Endurance by one to three points or increase his energy capacity by five to ten points.

If [Radiation Absorption] was used continuously, the effect would be weakened, and one would need to expose themselves in outer space for a longer period of time before they received the increased attributes.

However, if it was not triggered for a day, the time needed to expose oneself to trigger the effect would also return to the initial state.

This absorption process could be dismantled into three steps—absorption, storage, and digestion. Since cells are not bottomless and only had limited storage and digestion capabilities, this situation occurred.

This was a racial talent that would allow one to obtain considerable benefits just through the accumulation of time. It could be strengthened on the go and would definitely be worth the time. [Radiation Absorption] was the talent that Han Xiao was the most satisfied with at this time.

At this point, the total bonus attributes accumulated by the talent consisted of sixteen Strength, thirteen Dexterity, twenty-one Endurance, and sixty-eight Energy, as well as a huge boost to his attack.

Returning to the cockpit, Han Xiao greeted the three of them.

"You guys have waited a long time. We can start now."

"Why did we come over to this planet?" Aurora asked.

"To be Samaritans."

Han Xiao only smiled and switched to manual mode, turning the spaceship into stealth mode as they entered the atmosphere of Planet Nalun and slowly descended.

This was the first stop that he had chosen. Planet Nalun had three huge continental land plates, but only one of them hosted a civilization. The other two continents had yet to be discovered by the locals. Even their maritime era had not yet started, let alone venturing into the universe.

Other than the Galute Civilization, which discovered Planet Nalun, he should be the second visitor to grace this planet.

This civilization pursued the path of magic, with several kingdoms ruling over the continent. They followed the old aristocratic method of kings and lords, conquering other kingdoms for land. One of the biggest kingdoms was the Ocean Boundary Kingdom.

In his previous life, the players had discovered a profession mission, which could benefit Han Xiao.

The spaceship descended to an altitude of around one kilometer above sea level in its stealth mode, sweeping across the ground under the control of Han Xiao. From their point, towns built out of stones and bricks flashed by.

The Planet Nalun's local civilization did not possess the ability to discover interstellar spaceships.

Very quickly, the spaceship circled the entire planet once, completing its scan. Phillip created a map of the entire planet.

Hu!

The trees swayed as the spaceship landed amid a dense forest within a mountain range.

The four of them disembarked while keeping the spaceship in a stealth state, in case it was spotted by the locals.

Taking out his newly created map, Han Xiao swept his eyes over it before explaining,

"Our destination is nearby. This area belongs to the Ocean Boundary Kingdom. We're heading to an area called Stone Heart City. Let me see… oh, it's that city."

Pointing into the distance, Hila, Aurora, and Feidin looked to where Han Xiao had pointed.

They saw that, on the edge of the mountain, was a city built on one of the hills, with the gray stone of the surroundings as the main color of the city.

"Follow by my side and keep a low profile. None of you shall make a move," Han Xiao instructed.

Because Grade A Supers were a top tier combat power in the universe, they had a crushing power when facing a surface civilization. None of them could be defeated on Planet Nalun, and if they were not careful, an entire city could be wiped out instead.

In order to perform his mission, Han Xiao required everyone to stay low-profile, at least on the surface to integrate into this segment.

While they did not understand the intentions of Han Xiao, Hila and the rest nodded in response.

"Phillip, imitate the appearance of the Naluners."

A few mechanical orbs rose up, directing blue rays of light toward the four of them.

A matrix of data flashed across, and a simple simulated illusion was quickly generated on the four humans, turning them into Naluners. The body structure of the locals was similar to that of a human, albeit with darker, rougher skin and a lot of wrinkles.

After adjusting the translator channel, Han Xiao took the three alongside the mountain path toward Stone Heart City.

The afternoon sun shone lazily down.

The four of them moved extremely quickly and soon came to the scattered villages and towns outside the city. The area was undergoing plowing, and farmers were in twos or threes, working hard in the field. The air was filled with the stink of some sort of monster feces.

Having gotten used to the magnificent scenery of the universe, the group of them rather appreciated the primitive scenery of this surface civilization. It had a different flavor to it, as every Universal Civilization had once experienced such a period. The fires of civilization were weak at the beginning, and it was because they were cared for generation after generation that they finally blazed up to the universe level.

Being involved in war within the universe daily, only seeing battleships and armor, it was refreshing to suddenly come over to such a backward civilization to roam around.

There was no need to care about any enemies there. They could walk as they liked.

"The environment here is not bad. There's no air pollution." Han Xiao took a deep breath before shaking his head. "Even the smell of sh*t here is so fresh…"

"I'm getting the feeling that you're becoming more perverted," Feidin said honestly.

"No, no, in this regard, you're still much better."

The few of them idly chatted all the way to the entrance of Stone Heart City. The guards could not see through the camouflage of interstellar technology, which allowed Han Xiao to blend into the crowd and enter the city.

With a muggy wind blowing at them and noisy chatter in their ears, the group faced a messy stone street full of natives, which showcased backward town planning.

"What are we here for?" Aurora whispered in a small voice.

"You're the only one that keeps asking. Just follow me. We'll get the job done."

Using two fingers, Han Xiao pinched at the supple cheeks of Aurora's face, pulling it a little before letting go. Aurora cradled her reddened cheek with teary eyes.

"Sis, he bullied me!" Aurora immediately turned her head to complain.

Unfortunately, Hila's eyes remained straight ahead, as though she did not witness anything.

The few of them walked toward the notice board in town. Phillip translated the Nalunese for them into their language, and Han Xiao approached an old notice that had been left for many years.

As per the notice, a manor in Stone Heart City was believed to be haunted, and there were ghosts within. The owner of the manor hoped that someone would be able to go and solve it.

This notice had been placed here for a long time.

The location of the mission was a small manor. After Han Xiao and the rest expressed their intentions, they were quickly welcomed by the owner of the manor and seated in the main hall.

The moment they sat down, the owner could not wait and began speaking.

"This is great. Finally, there are people who are willing to help once again. This notice has already been up there for a good few years, and I've received at least a hundred people who have applied for this role, with five wizards among them, but no one has been able to solve this problem."

"Relax, we're different from them," Han Xiao said, and the translator immediately changed his words into Nalunese.

"Then, are you… are you guys wizards?" The manor owner looked hopefully at them.

"We could be counted as such. Tell me the specific situation first."

"O—Okay."

On Planet Nalun, there was a lifeform that resembled something like a ghost or a spirit, which the indigenous people named a 'demonic spirit'. A few years ago, a demonic spirit had appeared in the manor and would occasionally go out at night to haunt.

Planet Nalun's professions lay in the Mage system, which they termed as 'Poposot'. When translated to the universe language, it meant 'Wizard'. This Super system was very weak, with the wizards mainly utilizing potions or materials to cast spells. They were probably only at the Grade D level, but they appeared mysterious and powerful in the eyes of the indigenous people.

Exorcising the demonic spirits was the job of wizards. A few decades ago, the majority of wizards had mysteriously disappeared, causing them to be rarely seen and their heritage to thus be lost. Their Super system was cut off and could only be explored through obscure magic books.

Luckily, the demonic spirit in this manor was relatively weak, thus the owner and his family could still live here for several years.

The moment the owner finished speaking, Han Xiao's interface pinged.

You have triggered a Chain Mission: [Planet Nalun's Devil King]!

Mission Introduction: You have heard from the people that the wizards of Planet Nalun have mysteriously disappeared. There should be more than meets the eye.

First Chain Mission Requirements: Extinguish the demonic spirit in the manor.

Reward: 200,000 Experience

Because this was a chain mission, the initial rewards were very low. In his previous life, the players also only found out about this mission during free exploration in Version 3.0.

Each civilization would have a great number of trivial tasks. This mission was also very hidden; it was only discovered when a player who loved to perform storyline missions happened to discover this mission by chance. It was discovered that the reward of this was a talent that could boost one's psychological resistance. While the strength of Planet Nalun was akin to a weak chicken, the talent reward was pretty good.

At this moment, because the new version had just been opened, Black Star Army had been continuously farming the players like leeks, and thus, no one had gone to explore Planet Nalun.

Because of the soul embryo in his mental territory, Han Xiao decided to get another talent toward psychological resistance and thus went there, where the power level was not even at the level of a novice village.

He was clear about the flow of tasks and would be able to omit a lot of exploration time needed.

"Leave the demonic spirit to us. We'll resolve it tonight," Han Xiao said while glancing at the corner of the room, where a transparent magic eyeball was suspended, watching the conversation of several people talking.

Only the manor owner was unaware of the existence of the magic eyeball. The moment they stepped into the room, Han Xiao and company had immediately seen it.

At their level, such a clumsy, low-levelled magic eyeball was just like a living man squatting in the corner and murmuring, "You can't see me."

They could only lie to themselves.

"Leave it alone." Han Xiao waved a hand to stop Feidin. He knew who was paying attention to the manor, and attracting their attention was a key step in this mission.

At the same time, within a hidden meeting area deep beneath Stone Heart City…

The room did not have any windows, only a few kerosene lamps providing a faint light. From the darkness, a husky voice spoke.

"The sentry on number thirteen reacted. Someone has accepted the reward from the manor and wants to deal with the demonic spirit."

"Most likely, they're people who have picked up a few wizard books and think themselves actual wizards," a youthful voice helplessly replied. "Alas, there's no way they can handle the demonic spirit."

"They said they would move at night. Tomar, you shall follow after them."

"I got it. I'll protect them, lest they mess up and anger the demonic spirit, ending up hurt."

The conversation came to an end, and the sound of gears rang in the room for a while before stopping.

Deep at night, Han Xiao made the manor owner and his family leave before they went to the back garden of the manor.

This was an abandoned area surrounded by stone walls and fences, and the door was locked with several padlocks.

Using the keys given to open the door, Han Xiao strolled in. Inside was an abandoned warehouse area with several barns.

There was a cold, viscous atmosphere floating in the air, as though there was an airflow constantly brushing past their skin.

If it was a normal person, they would start to get nervous for no reason, as though they had entered a haunted place.

However, toward Han Xiao and the rest, it was useless.

"There are faint abnormal mental signals coming from here. I spotted them during the daytime," Feidin whispered. "Should I get rid of them?"

In front of this great Psychic master, the demonic spirit paled in comparison. Let alone getting rid of one, getting rid of a thousand was just a thought away for him.

"Wait for it to appear." Han Xiao shook his head, glancing vaguely in the direction of a barn. He had perceived a living person squatting there. This was his true goal.

"Alright, we'll follow your lead."

Feidin was helpless.

While he had his doubts, his role currently was a bodyguard, and his job was just to follow Han Xiao everywhere.

At this moment, Tomar stood near the barn, leaning against the wall as he watched the four of them 'secretly'.

He was a youth dressed in a black, hooded suit, which covered his face with shadows. He looked like an assassin, just that there were many small bags hanging around his waist, which contained spellcasting materials.

Upon seeing Han Xiao and the rest looking around as though they were on an outing, Tomar could not resist rolling his eyes, showing disdain.

Too unprofessional. They don't even know to arrange the Spiritual Light Powder in advance. Where did they get the idea to come and help someone exorcise the demonic spirit? It seems like they're going to suffer today…

As he thought, there was suddenly a gale of cold wind. The dust rolled up like a tornado, and a pale blue phantom emerged, roaring toward the air.

"Dammit, only a few years and the blue shadow demonic spirit has mutated!" Tomar exclaimed, and he began to get worried.

He had only studied witchcraft for five years and could not guarantee that he could protect himself in the hands of this demon, let alone those four laymen.

Upon seeing the indifference on their faces, Tomar angrily cursed before reaching for his casting kit. Regardless of his hidden identity, he was about to rush out and help.

"Plop…"

At this moment, Feidin carelessly sent out a mental wave, hitting the demonic spirit.

The blue phantom-like spirit body was akin to a broken mirror, shattering and collapsing into pieces like blue snowflakes, disappearing without a trace.

Tomar, who had just dashed out, was stunned rigid at this scene.

What just happened? Was the demonic spirit destroyed in one go?

Aren't wizards supposed to fight with potions and materials? What is this situation? The books never mentioned such a thing!

Tomar looked blank.

Chapter 741: Hidden Talent

Han Xiao looked at Tomar and greeted him with a smile.

"Hello to my friend who suddenly appeared."

"H-hello." Tomar snapped back to reality and stammered slightly. He then sized up the four individuals before him and asked with uncertainty, "Are all of you real wizards?"

The moment he said those words, Tomar immediately felt that he had asked an unnecessary question.

What's the point of asking such a question? Only a wizard can get rid of a demonic spirit…

The four individuals before his eyes had to be powerful wizards. If not, it would be impossible for them to kill a mutated blue shadow demonic spirit with a single strike.

I thought that the ones I'm protecting are novices. Who would have thought that they are in the same field as me?

Tomar's eyes widened with shock.

All of a sudden, Tomar seemed to have thought about something, and his expression changed greatly. He then took out a packet of white dust from his back and scattered it in midair before asking Han Xiao and the others to follow him.

"I used a bag of aura erasing dust to wipe out traces of magic in this place, so we shouldn't be spotted. Hurry up and follow me. I will bring all of you to the gathering place in Stone Heart City.

As he said that, Tomar leapt across the wall of the garden nimbly and sprinted away. Han Xiao took his three confused comrades and followed behind Tomar. They then arrived at an old house in the corner of Stone Heart City. A simple concealment array was laid in this place. In the eyes of Han Xiao and his three comrades, the array was naturally extremely clumsy, and nothing could be hidden from them. However, it was more than enough to bluff the natives of the planet.

Tomar entered through the chimney and took out a corner of the floorboard to reveal an underground passage.

"The gathering point is below. Follow me."

A hanging basket floated in the opening of the cave, and people were transported through gears and chains. It was like a prehistoric lift.

They stepped onto the lift, and after a short period of descending, the hanging basket touched the ground.

They were greeted with a gray space which was like an underground base. There were many cartons of supplies and over ten rooms in the place. The burning lamp was the only light source in this place.

Being extremely used to the technological advancements of the galaxy, this backward place gave Hila, Aurora, and Feidin an extremely fresh experience. It was as though they had gone back in time.

"This is the gathering place of Stone Heart City. I will take you to meet the person in charge, Mister Lanley."

Tomar took them to one of the rooms that was filled with bookshelves and old books.

A bearded old man was currently reading in front of an oil lamp that gave out a faint glow. Upon hearing some sound, he turned around with a face full of surprise.

Tomar gave a brief explanation, and the old man called Lanley lowered his guard. He then said with a hoarse voice, "It turns out that all of you are also wizards. Feel free to use anything in this place. Stone Heart City welcomes your arrival."

"I have been extremely curious along the way here. All of you did not use any magical elixirs. How did you get rid of the demonic spirit?" Tomar asked curiously.

"It is actually very simple. It is a technique of using magic." Feidin had received Han Xiao's instructions and could only follow them helplessly.

"Really? Why haven't I read it in the books?" Tomar rubbed his head.

As Lanley heard those words, he stood up abruptly and said with shock, "Only the legendary great wizard can cast a spell without using magical elixirs. Could it be that you are a great wizard‽ I thought that all the great wizards were killed by that devil fifty years ago!"

"What devil? What is going on?"

Lanley was stunned for a moment. "You guys don't know?"

"We don't…" Han Xiao revealed a puzzled look. Actually, I do know. However, I can only trigger the mission if it comes out from your mouth…

"I understand now. All of you are the legendary reclusive wizards and didn't participate in the battle fifty years ago."

Lanley grew excited and began explaining what had happened.

Fifty years ago, when there were plenty of wizards who roamed the streets, a wizard called Vosumede created a 'Divine Weapon'. It was able to create and control demonic spirits, and he could use the strength of the demonic spirits to increase his own magical strength. In order to increase his strength, he released a large number of frightening demonic spirits in multiple cities and used ordinary individuals to increase the strength of his demonic spirits. In the end, he became a great wizard by using such a method.

At that time, many wizards united together and wanted to kill Vosumede. However, Vosumede made use of the 'Divine Weapon' and killed all the wizards who surrounded him. He then chased after all the remaining wizards in the world and ended the legacies of many wizards.

After this, Vosumede became the Great Palace Wizard of the Ocean Boundary Kingdom and was known as the Demon King by the wizarding world. He groomed a large number of demonic spirits within the territory of the kingdom and became slightly more restrained because of his many different identities. The demonic spirit army under his army became more and more powerful and caused chaos everywhere.

A small portion of the wizards submitted to Vosumede and became his lackeys while the other surviving wizards had no choice but to hide. They set up various gathering points and helped each other.

Vosumede continued to chase after the surviving wizards, and thus, all the wizards hid themselves and no longer appeared in public. The outside world had lost all traces of the wizards, and the legacies of the wizards were in the hands of Vosumede or the gathering points. The gathering points would only pass on their techniques if they met a reliable youngster, bringing new blood into the world of the wizards and barely being able to survive.

This Vosumede is also a farmer in the same line as me… Han Xiao thought to himself.

After living in the universe for such a long time, Han Xiao had heard of plenty of similar incidents. It was basically the appearance of a powerful boss without anyone in the civilization being a match for him. Thus, a new dark era was born.

Planet Nalun did not know that there were other living beings in the universe and were not even clear about the meaning of the universe. Thus, they naturally did not have the ability to seek help from mercenaries.

Vosumede was the final target of this Chain Mission. Although Vosumede was a powerful existence who could do as he wished on Planet Nalun, he was no more than a little boy who Han Xiao could take care of with a wave of his arm. However, he might not necessarily obtain the Talent reward from the final phase of the mission if he got rid of Vosumede directly and had thus chosen to follow the mission step by step.

In any case, it was akin to him returning to a novice village to bully the noobs. There was not the slightest bit of pressure, and he just treated it as a vacation.

Lanley paced around excitedly before saying with a respectful tone, "Great wizards, we need your help."

"Speak." Han Xiao nodded.

"The wizarding world will always be under Vosumede's control as long as he doesn't die…"

"So, you want us to kill him?" Feidin interrupted.

Lanley shook his head and said with a bitter laughter, "We have tried to do so for fifty years, but Vosumede is too powerful. He was able to kill multiple great wizards at once a few decades ago, and he is probably even more powerful now. Even if all four of you are great wizards, you may not be a match for him. We cannot send all of you to your deaths."

Hila curled her lips up with dissatisfaction. She would be able to roam unhindered anywhere on Planet Nalun alone. However, she could only remain silent since Han Xiao did not say anything.

"Then, what do you need us to do?" Han Xiao asked patiently.

"It's like this. Vosumede's greatest helper is his demonic spirit army. He created the most powerful demonic spirit to lead his army, and we call it the Demonic Spirit King. If we want to deal with Vosumede, we will have to get rid of his helper first. However, the Demonic Spirit King is extremely powerful, and even a great wizard may not be a match for him. However, we have investigated his weakness.

"The Demonic Spirit King is a man-made item, and its strength is sustained by three magical altars. Every time an altar is destroyed, his strength is weakened. We have already located the locations of the three altars. There is one near Stone Heart City, but a demonic spirit army is guarding the altar. With the addition of the four of you, we will have the strength to destroy the altar."

As he spoke, the next phase of the mission appeared on Han Xiao's interface. It described the existence of the altar near Stone Heart City, and he could gain the trust of the gathering point by destroying the altar.

"Alright, I accept."

Lanley was overjoyed and said, "Then we will rely on all of you. The manpower that we can mobilize is limited, so we will only be able to provide eight wizards…"

"No need, he is enough." Han Xiao pointed at Tomar, who was by the side.

Tomar, who was listening by the side silently, was slightly surprised by those words. He then nodded resolutely. "I will try my best."

Han Xiao nodded silently. Obtaining the Talent was one of his objectives. Han Xiao's second objective of this trip was Tomar. This fellow had a low-grade Luck Glow and was a main character level NPC on Planet Nalun.

Most missions would have some residual influence after the completion of the mission, and the players who completed this mission in his previous life went back to Planet Nalun a few years after completing the mission. They had then discovered the achievements of Tomar.

After Vosumede's death, the wizards on Planet Nalun had attained their freedom, and Tomar had become a famous wizard. He spent his life researching magic and achieved a groundbreaking discovery. He left behind a lot of knowledge for the later generation and single handedly raised the Super standard on Planet Nalun to a whole new level.

This was no simple matter. This was akin to someone who had only received high school level mathematics education coming up with university level mathematics proofs.

In truth, many of the heroes of the civilizations were talents who were buried because of the generation that they were born in.

Tomar was such a character as well. His magical talent was extremely outstanding, and he was a rare talent who could only be found once every thousand years. However, he could not grow properly in a backward location, and his talent was wasted as a result.

Thus, Han Xiao's other objective was to bring Tomar into the army to groom.

Talents were precious, and the more main character level NPCs the better. Regardless of how worthless they were, they could increase the luck of the army.

…

The location that Lanley gave was a cave hidden in the mountains. One of the altars was located in this location.

The next morning, Han Xiao and the gang set off together with Tomar. In order to match Tomar's speed, it took them half a day to reach the cave. The sky was already dark by then.

They stood outside the cave, and a chilly wind blew out from within the dark cave as though it was breathing.

Tomar shivered and said, "The demonic spirits will come out at night as their strength increases at night. We should set up camp outside and rest for the night before entering the cave tomorrow at noon."

"That isn't necessary." Han Xiao shook his head. This mission did not pose any difficulty to him, and he walked into the cave with Hila, Aurora, and Feidin. Tomar hesitated for a while before gritting his teeth and following them.

The cave was filled with many winding tunnels with cold winds blowing from within. The deeper they went into the cave, the more obvious the cold aura being emanated from the cave. When they reached the depths of the cave, the demonic spirit aura was not covered in the slightest, and some faint muttering could be heard from time to time in the cave.

Tomar's head was covered in sweat, and he looked around nervously, afraid that a demonic spirit would jump out and scare him at any moment. He held on tightly to the magical elixir on his waist and was ready to throw it out at any moment. His appearance was completely different from Han Xiao's group.

"Wh-why don't we return?" Tomar stammered with his voice trembling. "Although all of you are great wizards, we shouldn't underestimate our enemy. There are three hundred demonic spirits in this place at the very least, and it would be extremely difficult for you to deal with them…"

Right after he said those words, a strange stone altar appeared in front of him. A few hundred candles were lined up by the altar and burnt with a green flame that seemed inextinguishable.

"This is the place. Let's quickly destroy the altar and make our retreat!" Tomar said anxiously and was about to throw out his magical elixir.

Right at that moment, a bone piercing chill blew over, and a few hundred figures appeared in the surroundings, glaring at Han Xiao's group coldly.

"They are all demonic spirits…" Tomar's eyes widened with shock, and his heart skipped a beat.

However, before the fear in his heart could explode, the cold aura in the cave melted away like snow in the sun.

The few hundred demonic spirits were all destroyed without even making a sound. They were all defeated in one hit by Feidin.

Their illusory bodies disappeared, and Tomar's scream was stuck in his throat.

The scene before him had completely changed his worldview.

Just what happened just now? How did all the demonic spirits disappear?

Is a great wizard really so powerful‽

"We just need to destroy this altar, right?" Hila waved her arm, and the altar turned to dust.

A notification of the second phase being completed popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

The instant that the altar was destroyed, the cave began to tremble.

Boom!

Black fog floated up from the destroyed altar and formed a black whirlpool in midair. A wave of pressure was then emanated from the whirlpool as though a being was about to descend.

Tomar's hair stood up on end, and he felt as though a ferocious animal was glaring at him. An instinctive feeling of fear rose in his heart.

"It's the Demonic Spirit King…" Tomar's voice became hoarse, and he was frightened to the point that he could not move.

The next second, an eerie voice sounded from within the whirlpool and echoed in the cave.

"A few bugs actually dared to destroy my altar‽ You will pay the price for this!"

Han Xiao and the others watched the Demonic Spirit King's performance emotionlessly.

"Humph, it is too late to regret. I will eat all your souls and transform all of you into a part of me. All of you shall fall into the depths of… argh!"

Before the Demonic Spirit King could even finish his act, Feidin snorted and shot out his Psychic energy. Like an inflated balloon being punctured, the Demonic Spirit King let out a miserable groan and disappeared.

The black whirlpool floating in midair had disappeared and the shaking of the cave had also become silent. It was as though nothing had happened at all.

"Hey, you didn't end up killing it, right?" Han Xiao became worried. Would the mission be stopped midway if the Demonic Spirit King died?

"I could have killed it, but it wasn't necessary." Feidin rolled his eyes.

"You are the one who knows me best." Han Xiao laughed and slapped Feidin on the back.

Following which, Han Xiao then waved at Tomar, who was rooted to the spot in shock.

"The altar is destroyed. Let's return."

Tomar had spent a great amount of effort to shut his opened mouth before jumping back to look at Han Xiao with caution.

"Who exactly are all of you‽"

Han Xiao frowned and said, "I said before. We are wizards."

Tomar had a look of disbelief on his face.

Don't think you can bluff me because I am uneducated. You lot are definitely not wizards.

Because wizards cannot be so powerful!

He then praised his own wisdom silently.

"Alright then, since we have been discovered, I shall tell you the truth…"

Han Xiao's eyes spun around, and a teasing look could be seen in his eyes.

"We are actually deities."

Hila, Aurora, and Feidin almost choked.

Woah, you're truly shameless!

Tomar had a look of disbelief upon hearing that.

There are actually deities in the world? Could those religions be real? I thought that it was only a scam.

However, it seems like only deities would be able to kill a few hundred demonic spirits in a second.

Tomar could not think of any other explanation. In the face of a 'deity', he was completely helpless and did not know what to say.

Han Xiao giggled in his heart while pretending to be solemn on the surface. "I have come for Vosumede. His actions have gone against the laws of nature, and he will be punished."

Planet Nalun was a backward planet, and it was extremely easy to fool them. It was not the first time that he had tried to act as a deity. He had tried once in front of the Black Spirit Race before. When facing the natives of a backward planet, saying that he was a deity might be more convincing than saying that he was from the universe.

Tomar's eyes lit up upon hearing those words, and an agitated look could be seen on his face.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao placed his finger on his lips and said with a smile, "But I hope that you can help keep this secret. It is best that only you know the truth that I am a deity."

It will be time to kidnap you when the mission is complete.

"Okay, okay." Tomar nodded like an obedient child.

He originally wanted to inform everyone at the gathering point about the truth, but since the 'deity' had personally requested for him to keep silent about it, he must have his reasons. Thus, he decided to hide this truth in his heart.

Upon thinking about the fact that he was the only one who knew that the four individuals before him were deities, Tomar felt extremely agitated.

Chapter 742: One Cannon Is Enough

After getting rid of the first altar, they spent a night outside before returning to the gathering point in Stone Heart City.

After finding out about the successful mission, Lanley was extremely surprised.

"All of you succeeded so quickly?"

He has been leading the gathering point in Stone Heart City for many years already and had always been wary of the demonic spirit army near the altar. Due to the lack of manpower, he did not dare act too rashly. He had originally thought that Han Xiao and his group would need eight to ten days to slowly clear up the demonic spirits near the altar. However, Han Xiao's efficiency had truly surprised him.

That was especially so after realizing that there were no injuries in the group, and only Tomar looked as though he did not have a good sleep. Lanley was extremely curious about the details of their operation.

"I remember that there should be a few hundred demonic spirits. How did all of you accomplish this?"

"It's like this…" Tomar swallowed a mouthful of saliva and began to explain.

When they set up camp outside last night, Feidin had given Tomar a subtle mental hint together with the 'divine miracles' that Han Xiao had gotten Aurora to perform. Tomar had completely believed that Han Xiao's group of four were deities.

He was the only one who knew the truth about the 'deities', and Tomar was agitated to the point he could not sleep. In order to hide the identity of the 'deities', he had spent a full night thinking of an appropriate excuse to report to Lanley today.

As he gave his 'explanation', Tomar was extremely anxious that Lanley would spot a flaw.

He did not understand why the 'deities' wanted to hide their identities, but he did not dare gamble. He was afraid that the 'deities' would choose to leave if their identities were exposed. This would result in the gathering point losing such great support.

Upon seeing the broken fragments of the altar, Lanley did not have any other doubts, and after expressing his gratitude to Han Xiao, he left hastily to contact the leaders of the other gathering points.

"I managed to hide it…" Tomar heaved a sigh of relief.

"Good job." Han Xiao nodded.

Tomar was extremely reserved in front of Han Xiao. Although Han Xiao's group of four seemed extremely approachable and were not aloof like in the religious records, Tomar still felt immense pressure. He then said, "Your Excellencies, I have a question that I don't know if I should ask."

"Speak."

"Actually, I have been curious since last night…" Tomar stammered. "The deities in the religious records all have their own names and authority. I wonder if… cough cough, I don't know if it is rude for me to ask this. If it is, I hope that you can accept my apology…"

In truth, he wanted to ask if Han Xiao's group of four were the deities in the legends that he had heard.

"Names…" Han Xiao stroked his chin before saying with a smile, "This isn't a secret. My divine name is Black Star."

Black Star?

Tomar had a look of confusion. He had never heard of such a deity in all the stories he heard.

Han Xiao then pointed at Hila and Aurora. "They are the deities of death and life."

Hila had a speechless look on her face and could only allow Han Xiao to joke as he wished.

"As for him…" Han Xiao turned around and looked at Feidin who had an expectant look on his face. After letting out a light cough, he joked, "He is the deity of luck. Let me remind you about something, he is both male and female in one body and doesn't have a gender."

Must you really emphasize my gender… Feidin had a look of resignation on his face.

Tomar engraved the names into his heart and immediately expressed his loyalty. "I will spread all of your names and allow the world to know who the real deities are. I will spread your glory in this land."

"We can talk about this in the future."

Han Xiao tried his best to stifle his laughter. When Tomar entered the universe, this would definitely be his dark past.

…

After completing the second phase of the mission and gaining the trust of the gathering point, the gathering point began to treat the four 'great wizards' with much importance. In the following days, the gathering point gave many tasks to the four of them as part of the mission.

With his overwhelming strength and galactic technology, Han Xiao completed the missions with incredible efficiency. Some of the missions included destroying the other two altars, clearing up demonic spirits in many different cities, killing some of Vosumede's henchmen, collecting rare materials, and so on.

The use of a spaceship greatly reduced their travelling time, and Han Xiao was able to easily find the rare materials by scanning the entire continent with his devices. He only needed half a month to solve the problem that had been troubling the gathering point for fifty years.

The entire gathering point was shocked by Han Xiao's divine efficiency, which was almost like a miracle. Tomar bitterly tried to hide the 'truth' and did not expose the identities of the 'deities'.

However, the result of Han Xiao's efficiency was the suspicion of the upper echelons in the gathering point. There were some who felt that the four of them were far too successful and might be spies sent by Vosumede. Vosumede might intend to lure them all out to catch them in one fell swoop.

Wulis was the current leader of all the gathering points, and he was the one who suspected Han Xiao's group of four the most. However, he did not reveal his suspicion, instead keeping some secrets from the four.

His plan was to create a 'divine weapon' to fight with Vosumede, and the rare materials that Han Xiao had gathered were the materials for the 'divine weapon'. However, he did not reveal anything to Han Xiao's group of four.

This way, even if Han Xiao's group of four were spies for Vosumede, they would not know his true plan. At the same time, he would be able to borrow their strength to gather the materials for the 'divine weapon'.

…

In some secret location, all the gathered materials were sent over. Wulis and a few other wizards of the upper echelons were crafting this 'divine weapon' secretly.

The flames of the furnace lit up the dark room, and the 'divine weapon' was beginning to take shape.

Clank!

As the iron hammer came into contact with the red-hot ores, sparks flew in all directions, and the ores gradually began to change shape.

Wulis and the others released their magical elixirs by the side, chanted incantations, and engraved formations to complete the process.

The last step was soon reached, and the blacksmith quenched the completed 'divine weapon' in ice-cold water.

Whoosh!

A large amount of water was immediately evaporated, and after a long wait, the blacksmith removed a metallic staff from the cold water. It looked like black vines with many curses being engraved on it.

"It is finally completed! The White Sorcerer Wand!"

Wulis picked up the staff excitedly. This was the 'divine weapon' that their gathering point had always wanted to forge. It was able to greatly increase the strength of their magical powers and restrict the demonic spirit army. This was the nemesis of Vosumede's Demonic Spirit Necklace.

All the wizards present had looks of joy on their faces.

"With the White Sorcerer Wand in our hands, we have the strength to face Vosumede head on!"

Wulis held on to the staff tightly and spoke in a bright voice.

"Everyone, we must keep the existence of this staff a secret. We must not let Vosumede and the four wizards of dubious origin know about it.

"This is our strongest trump card, and we will have to rely on it to kill Vosumede! It has been a full fifty years, and it is time for the final battle!

"Inform the wizards in all the gathering points. It is time to launch an all-out attack!"

Wulis burnt with battle intent.

…

The Chain Mission was at its second last phase, and its mission requirement was to head to the capital of the Ocean Boundary Kingdom to meet up with the wizards of the other gathering points. The next phase of the mission would be to defeat the final boss, Vosumede, in the palace of the Ocean Boundary Kingdom.

In some secret courtyard, all the wizards of the gathering points were gathered with Wulis as the leader. There were about 230 wizards present.

It was evening, and Wulis was giving a speech in front of the others.

"Tonight is the final battle, and we are going to sneak past the defense line of the palace to ambush the Great Palace Wizard. We will gather the strength of our gathering points to kill him. This is the moment when Vosumede is the weakest, and all of our success is thanks to our four new reclusive wizards."

Wulis then nodded toward Han Xiao's group of four, who were seated at the front, with a look of caution hidden in his eyes.

The way he saw it, if the four of them were spies, they would definitely expose themselves that night.

Wulis had already made preparations and got his trusted aids to keep an eye on the four of them.

Han Xiao smiled without replying.

The mission would be at its final phase during the battle, and he would be able to reap the harvest from his half a month of hard work.

Tomar was within the crowd, and his fists were clenched with agitation.

I am the only one here who knows that they are deities…

…

Night descended after a long wait, and darkness enveloped the entire city.

Wulis no longer hesitated and announced the start of the mission.

Their large gang of more than two hundred wizards then approached the palace and suppressed their auras with magical powder. They snuck into the palace and did not disturb the guards.

Han Xiao's group of four hid among the group and waited for the mission to enter the final phase.

The journey was extremely smooth, and the wizards very quickly gathered outside the palace of the Great Palace Wizard.

Wu!

Right at this moment, a military horn sounded from within the palace.

The palace doors swung open, and a few dozen wizards charged out from the palace. At the front of the group, an old man stood. He was Vosumede.

"Humph, a bunch of sneaky rats. I have been waiting for all of you for a long time," Vosumede said proudly. "I have long found out about all of your little schemes over the past half a month and couldn't be bothered with all of you. Do all of you really think that I was unaware of you sneaking into the capital?

"I have already been operating in the Ocean Boundary Kingdom for fifty years, and my demonic spirit army is hidden all around. I found out the moment you stepped into this city!

"The guards of the palace have already cut off your escape route and are on the way here. It will be impossible for you to escape!"

The moment these words were said, the wizards of the gathering point became jittery.

Wulis stood out from the crowd and said with a deep voice, "Don't be anxious. The number of wizards in the palace is less than a quarter of ours. We will be able to kill them all before the guards arrive!"

Vosumede suddenly burst out into laughter. "Wulis, is your brain rotten? Have you forgotten about my strongest trump card?"

Vosumede grabbed the necklace on his neck as he said that, and the temperature in the surroundings fell immediately. A cold gust of wind blew over, and more than a thousand demonic spirits appeared.

A gigantic demonic spirit appeared beside Vosumede; it was the Demonic Spirit King.

The two hundred or so wizards of the gathering points took a step back subconsciously and looked at the demonic spirit army nervously.

This was what Vosumede had relied on to rule the wizard world for fifty years. His Demonic Spirit Necklace was able to create and control demonic spirits.

Compared to the anxiousness of the others, Wulis was extremely confident. He held onto the White Sorcerer Wand in his hands. This was the nemesis of the demonic spirit army and also the reason he had dared to challenge Vosumede.

You have a divine weapon, but I do too… Wulis sneered coldly in his heart.

Right at this moment, Wulis suddenly thought about Han Xiao's group of four. His eyes narrowed, and he decided against using the White Sorcerer Wand.

The divine weapon had to be used at the most appropriate moment. Wulis was extremely wary of Han Xiao's group of four, and he glanced at them carefully before making a decision.

If four of them are Vosumede's accomplices and make any moves, I can use the White Sorcerer Wand to kill them!

On the other side, Vosumede stroked his beard and looked extremely calm as though the entire situation was within his grasp.

"Do you know, I have never concerned myself with you? If all of you chose to hide properly, I may have been willing to give you a path of survival. However, you chose to come out and create trouble for me time and time again, even wanting to kill me.

"Ah, your imaginations are as distant as the stars in the skies, and all of you are like a bunch of annoying flies.

"You hid yourselves for fifty years like rats. Do you think that it is possible to overthrow me? How ridiculous!"

As he said that, the luxurious robe on Vosumede's body began fluttering despite the lack of wind. His powerful magical force burst forth from his body. In the eyes of Wulis and the other wizards of the gathering points, Vosumede's aura seemed to have become like a towering building, suppressing their very souls.

"What is this‽" Wulis and the others were shocked, and their faces turned pale.

"Humph! There is an even more powerful level above the great wizard realm. I made use of fifty years to take this last step…"

Vosumede stretched out his arms and let out arrogant laughter.

"I am now a god!"

The two hundred or so wizards were all dumbfounded, and even Wulis felt his heart falling into despair.

No! The situation has changed, and I cannot save my trump card to deal with a spy that may not even exist.

I must make use of the White Sorcerer Wand to severely wound Vosumede if not the others will die!

Wulis held onto the White Sorcerer Wand tightly and began chanting a series of mnemonics, ready to activate the 'divine weapon'.

Vosumede obviously did not understand the logic of a bad guy dying because he talked too much. He was still intoxicated with the feeling of the entire situation being in his grasp. He raised his hand and pointed at the crowd as though he was looking down on a bunch of ants.

"You do not understand anything about true strength!"

As those words sounded, Wulis completed his preparations, and his eyes narrowed. He was about to use the White Sorcerer Wand to launch his strongest attack on Vosumede.

Right at this moment, a psionic cannon shot out from within the crowd and smashed onto Vosumede's arrogant face before anyone could even react.

The speed of the attack was one that did not even allow him to dodge.

Bang!

The flash of light came and went quickly, and Vosumede's head disappeared without a trace.

His headless body then shook for a while before collapsing on the ground.

Everyone present was stunned silly.

Everyone looked at Vosumede's headless body, and they could not believe what had happened.

Wait, Vosumede was… dead?

He died like that‽

Wulis' eyes bulged out to the point that they almost fell out.

Was I the one who killed him?

That's not right… I didn't even use the divine weapon…

Everyone then thought about the direction from which the ball of light was shot out from. They turned their heads and looked at Han Xiao's group of four. The wizards of the gathering point then inched away from the four subconsciously.

"Mission complete." Han Xiao then lowered his palm and opened his interface with satisfaction.

Just a moment ago, the mission had entered the final phase, and Han Xiao had blasted Vosumede's head off without any hesitation. Despite this fellow looking as though he was extremely powerful, he was no more than a Grade C Super. A single cannon was enough to blow his head.

All the wizards present looked at Han Xiao's group of four, and before they could even react, a huge change occurred.

Hu!

The moment Vosumede died, all the demonic spirits present lost control and charged out in all directions toward any living being around them.

The two hundred or so wizards immediately snapped back to reality and prepared to face the enemy.

Right at this moment, everyone could clearly see Feidin, who was beside Han Xiao, tapping his forehead and releasing a formless white light to cover the entire region. All the demonic spirits who touched the white light immediately disintegrated.

In the blink of an eye, all the demonic spirits including the Demonic Spirit King were wiped out.

This time, everyone clearly saw what had happened. Their bodies were rooted to the ground, and a look of disbelief could be seen on their faces.

This… What kind of strength was this?

Was Vosumede really killed by these four? With a single hit‽

Pa!

The staff in Wulis' hands dropped on the ground, and his lips began to tremble.

He had tried to make various predictions about what might happen, but never had he expected such a scenario.

To think that the four people who he thought could be spies for the enemy actually had such frightening strength and killed the enemy leader with a single attack.

The White Sorcerer Wand that he had spent so much effort to create was actually completely useless.

"You… who exactly are all of you?"

Wulis looked at Han Xiao's group of four with bloodshot eyes.

This was also the question in the hearts of everyone present.

Vosumede had been ruling over the wizard world for fifty years and was actually easily killed by four reclusive wizards of dubious origins.

This made all the wizards present feel a sense of defeat.

Wulis was the one who was most affected by the scene before him. He felt as though his insistence over the last fifty years was completely meaningless.

Han Xiao frowned and did not reply. He turned around to look at Tomar instead.

Tomar was excited to the point he almost exploded. From beginning to end, his eyes had been fixed on Han Xiao's group of four. Upon seeing Han Xiao looking at him, Tomar immediately understood the hint.

The next moment, he walked out from the crowd with agitation and spoke loudly to attract everyone's attention.

"There isn't a need for me to hide anything anymore! I have always known their identities. They are deities, true deities! Only deities have such strength!"

Upon hearing that, everyone fell into a daze.

De—deities‽

This answer was completely out of their imagination.

Everyone felt as though their world view had been lifted before being slammed back onto the ground.

Chapter 743: News from Harrofal

After seeing the performance of the four, the audience somewhat believed that they were deities. This seemed to be the only explanation for their unprecedented power.

Ta, ta, ta!

As everyone started to rave about the deities, the royal guards of the Ocean Boundary Kingdom slowly arrived. They had originally heeded the order of Vosumede to surround the wizards, but upon learning that Vosumede had suddenly died, even the court mages were too afraid of the so-called four 'deities' and lost the ability to resist.

The subordinate wizards of Vosumede surrendered one after another. Upon learning that Vosumede had been killed, the head of the Royal Guards Corps could not believe it. Once he had confirmed his death, he was overjoyed.

Vosumede was not supported by the majority of people, and they hoped for him to die an early death. However, no one had the ability to kill him, so his death came as good news to a lot of people.

The head of the Royal Guard Corps initially thought that Vosumede had been killed by the head of the wizard assembly points, but the truth from the wizard's mouth frightened him. He could not help but glance over at the four 'deities' before hurriedly dispatching an escort to notify the king.

While it was already late into the night, the atmosphere surrounding the area was weird. Practically everyone around was wide awake and scrutinizing the four of them. Han Xiao did not bother with their reactions and turned his attention to the Mission Completion notification on his user interface.

Having completed the chain mission [Planet Nalun's Demon King], the talent that he was supposed to obtain as a reward finally arrived.

Talent [Soul Lock]: +20% Psychological Resistance.

Duration of all negative spiritual effects is reduced by 10%.

When you suffer a spiritual attack, you have a 18% – 34% chance to negate the damage.

If damage is negated, there is a cooldown time of 30 minutes.

Adding this to my [Advanced Mental Toughness], my spiritual resistance should be at fifty-five percent. However, compared to the addition of resistance, the effect of this damage negation could result in some miracles…

While the cooldown time was pretty long, probably allowing it to only be triggered once in battle, and was uncontrollable, it was still an extremely useful ability. If he had possessed such a talent when he was facing Psyker, he would have had a chance to completely negate this effect.

The chance of triggering the damage negation was only at eighteen percent. Even if he was not too lucky, the chance was still manageable. Han Xiao had long gotten used to looking only at the lower limit of his odds.

At this time, Tomar had already started to popularize the divine names of the four of them among the crowd. Wulis brought a group of people to approach Han Xiao, displaying a cramped expression. He did not seem to know how to properly communicate with the deities, and to come into contact with someone whose life level far exceeded theirs, he was full of awe and anxiety.

"Four Majesties… oh no, Deities. On behalf of all the wizards, I thank you for getting rid of this devil Vosumede. If there are any requests, I'll try my best to fulfil them…"

Han Xiao kept his interface, looking at the anxious group of people before smiling. "I do have a request, and that is for Tomar to be my emissary. I'll bring him up to the kingdom of God."

The emissary of a Deity‽

Everyone's head swiveled toward Tomar, full of envy, surprise, shock, and so on.

Tomar gaped in shock, his brain an absolute blank. He did not believe that Han Xiao was pointing at himself. "This… what is the meaning of this…"

"The meaning is, I'll take you to the world that the deities live in." Han Xiao pulled out all the stops in his acting. "Are you willing to?"

Tomar was rendered utterly incoherent by the surprise, and the few words that managed to escape his mouth were gibberish that even the translator could not handle. He frantically nodded, as though he was testing if he could snap his spine by doing so.

Wulis gulped. While he was full of curiosity about deities and their kingdom, he did not know their character and hence did not dare to ask further.

At this moment, the soldier who went to notify the king finally returned, reporting the situation to the head of the Royal Guard Corps.

Immediately, the head walked over to where Han Xiao and the rest were, with a respectful expression.

"Four Deities, Your Excellency Wulis, Your Excellency Tomar, His Majesty hopes that you will grace him with your presence."

Wulis did not reply but rather turned his head to look at Han Xiao. He understood that the person whom the king wished to see were the deities.

Han Xiao thought about it before nodding and accepting the invite.

Seeing the king of this current regime would not take much time, and it could also help to dispel any worries the new leek Tomar would have.

Seeing this, both Wulis and Tomar quickly agreed as well.

"Please follow me."

The head guard was overjoyed and quickly escorted them to the main hall.

The king of Ocean Boundary Kingdom had urgently dressed up just to meet them.

When faced with the creatures suspected to be deities, the Ocean Boundary King tried to make himself look dignified. Since it was the first time that he had come in contact with deities, he did not wish to destroy the glory of his kingdom. Unfortunately, his protruding belly had defeated all his attempts.

Upon seeing Han Xiao and the rest in the appearance of the Naluners, his internal nervousness dissipated a lot. At least the appearance of the deities was familiar to him.

"Distinguished Deities, I hereby represent Ocean Boundary Kingdom to welcome you. Forgive me, but please allow me to ask, what exactly is a deity and for what purpose have you all come?"

"Even if I were to tell you, you would not be able to understand the difference in our life levels." Han Xiao raised a brow, behaving pretentiously. "As for our objective, it was first to get rid of Vosumede, which has been completed. The second objective is to choose an emissary, and I have chosen Tomar."

The Ocean Boundary King glanced at Tomar, burning his face into his heart. He then jolted before asking, "In that case, does it mean that deities are willing to pass down your teachings?"

"Oh, you can put it that way." Han Xiao nodded. This reasoning was more convenient for him as well.

The eyes of the Ocean Boundary King lit up, and he thought that he had grasped the needs of the deities.

"Since that's the case, if the four of your Deities are able to perform a miracle and bless the kingdom, I'm willing to create a religion that belongs to you, mobilizing the people of the kingdom to become your believers."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, unsurprised. For a backward civilization, the knowledge of deities existing was equivalent to an opportunity for them to reshape their social structure. In their eyes, the help of deities was more important than the development of science and technology.

He could predict that, with his influence, the trajectory of the development of the Planet Nalun civilization would change. Religion would soon begin to intervene in politics, and there was a great chance of forming a political system that combined both politics and religion.

This time, a new mission suddenly popped up on the interface.

[Display Miracles]

Mission Introduction: The indigenous regime of Planet Nalun treats you as a God and wishes for you to show your 'miracles'. Maybe you'll leave a mark on the history of this civilization.

Mission Requirements: Present a 'miracle' to the Ocean Boundary King (Requires a subversion of the target's cognition).

Reward: 3,000,000 experience, 1 Planet Legendary Point.

"Oho, there's even a branch task." Han Xiao was overjoyed.

In his previous life, during the mid to late versions of the game, players would occasionally visit backwater civilizations to gain Legendary Points. They would pull all sorts of tricks to leave their names in the history of that civilization. This was also a way to gain Legendary Points.

Since he could obtain a Legendary Point, there was no need to reject this task.

Sweeping a glance at the expectant looks of the Ocean Boundary King, Tomar, and Wulis, Han Xiao breathed in deeply before raising his hands. The nanoparticles transformed into countless carving knives, drawing out a map on one of the palace walls.

"What are you doing?" The Ocean Boundary King was shocked. He had thought that a divine miracle would be a big event and did not expect for it to be so simple.

"This is the original appearance of the world you're in and also the map of the entire world." Han Xiao slowly spoke.

On the wall was a map of Planet Nalun, generated by Phillip.

The Ocean Boundary King jerked in shock. He immediately scrutinized the map before suddenly exclaiming, "The world is round?"

Even Wulis and Tomar had looks of disbelief.

The civilization on Planet Nalun had only occupied a continent and had not even explored the entire world. They did not even know that their planet was in the shape of a sphere.

"Wait, other than this continent, there are still two more‽" The Ocean Boundary King saw the main point and almost had a cardiac arrest.

The Ocean Boundary Kingdom was only one of the few kingdoms on the continent, and they still had to fight for domination against the other kingdoms. If there were really two other unoccupied continents, if their kingdom could take the lead to occupy them, they would gain an advantage in expansion.

Upon thinking of the possibilities of opening new territories, the Ocean Boundary King was so excited that he could hear the rapid pounding of his heart.

Suddenly, he came to his senses. He felt that all of this might not be true. Since he had no way of knowing the true appearance of the world, even if the deities decided to lie, he would not be able to unravel it.

Unable to suppress his suspicion, the Ocean Boundary King softly coughed before saying, "Respectful Deities, may I ask how to confirm the authenticity of this map. As you know, we're all mortals, and without your powers, we have no way to cross the ocean in this continent to explore the world."

The mission is not yet complete… Han Xiao was frowning but quickly smoothed his face as he said, "That's right. In that case, I'll let you see it for yourself."

"See it for myself?" The Ocean Boundary King jerked.

Before he could react, Han Xiao grabbed him by his shoulder and formed a shield out of his nanoparticles.

Bang!

The next second, Han Xiao burst out toward the sky, smashing through the roof of the palace.

Flying up high, they quickly reached the atmospheric level, where one could barely overlook half of the entire planet.

"Look, can you see it now? The world is round, and there are two continents over there…"

Han Xiao casually spoke before turning to look at the king. He only found that the king had turned pale white, his eyes rolling around while his whole body was frozen stuff, as though he had lost the ability to react.

"It seems like the stimulus was too much for him…"

Helplessly shaking his head, Han Xiao then descended and returned to the palace. The entire process did not even take a minute.

The moment Han Xiao took off, Wulis and Tomar had been stunned speechless. At this time, they saw the two of them return, and only then did they realize that they had still underestimated the powers of the deities. Their abilities were incomprehensible.

Han Xiao injected a shot of adrenaline into the Ocean Boundary King, and after he recovered, he shivered, his legs turning soft as he slumped to the ground. He could no longer maintain his proud front and only stared at Han Xiao in horror, speechless.

Before this, he had some doubts about the identity of the four 'deities', but he no longer dared to hold any. His bladder that almost leaked had completely replaced whatever he had for a brain, allowing his body to remember the reality that 'deities' could do anything.

"Do you believe it now?" Han Xiao smiled.

"Believe, I believe…" The Ocean Boundary King nodded, and besides respect, there was a fanaticism and piety within his eyes.

This was a miracle!

At this moment, he felt that he had finally found his calling.

Han Xiao's interface was updated, and it showed that his task of showing miracles had been completed. He had obtained 1 Legendary Point.

Legendary Point (Planet Nalun): The God of the Mortal World

The miracle you have shown today will change the development trajectory of Planet Nalun to a certain extent. Your existence will seep into the history of this planet, and people will treat you as a religion and spread your divine light. Your influence will accompany this civilization for a long time.

Another Legendary Point obtained… Han Xiao grinned to himself.

…

After the Ocean Boundary King promised to establish a religion for the four of them, Han Xiao and his party left, disappearing in front of everyone's eyes.

Tomar also became a member of the team. He had already agreed to follow Han Xiao to his 'Divine Kingdom'. Because he was a standard orphan-type protagonist template, he had no strings attached and could roam freely.

Han Xiao felt that taking Tomar away was also a good thing for Planet Nalun. Tomar would be the first Naluner to enter the universe, just like him.

Because Tomar was a native of the planet, he had to open his eyes to the world and understand the true meaning of the universe.

After he had been systematically trained to maximize his talents and developed a stronger power, he could then use the resources obtained in the universe to feed Planet Nalun. This would bring more benefits to his motherland compared to him staying within.

Since the mission had already ended, Han Xiao did not tarry much longer on Planet Nalun and quickly took his group to board the spaceship, leaving the planet.

Tomar was extremely curious about everything on the spaceship, but he was also a little dazed, as the deities' image in his mind differed from reality.

Han Xiao just threw him to Feidin, allowing him to complete Tomar's enlightenment education.

As for himself, he returned to his room, looking through the news obtained this past half month.

The daily news of the Black Star Army was scanned, and Han Xiao flipped through his communicator before finding a message from Harrofal.

After seven years of no contact, Han Xiao was a little curious about what Harrofal wanted him to do.

With one glance, however, his facial expression changed.

The news was short, but the content gave him a headache. There was only a sentence written without any context.

"It's EsGod!"

Chapter 744: EsGod's Intention

Why mention EsGod suddenly?

Han Xiao frowned. Back when he was attacked by EsGod's doppelganger, Harrofal had fought alongside him. After seven years, Harrofal had suddenly brought it up again, so something must have happened.

Without hesitation, Han Xiao sent a message to Harrofal directly to ask him what he meant.

However, after waiting for quite some time, Harrofal still did not reply.

Han Xiao suddenly had a bad feeling. He summoned Phillip and said with a deep voice, "Search keyword 'Harrofal' and show me the abnormal results."

Phillip hummed and quickly completed the search.

"Master, hum… A few days ago, various news channels in the Tyla Civilization reported Harrofal's death."

He died a few days ago‽

Han Xiao knew that something was wrong.

"Bring it up."

Phillip played the related reports. After watching them, Han Xiao then figured out what had happened.

Just a few days ago, Harrofal was attacked in the government school of the Tyla Civilization. He was kidnapped in front of the public. Even the three Calamity Grades working in the school could not stop the kidnappers.

One day after the kidnappers left, Harrofal's body was discovered. The message that Han Xiao had just received was sent by Harrofal before his death.

The news stated that the Tyla Civilization had confirmed one of the kidnappers' identities through the traces left behind, and a bounty had been issued.

Han Xiao opened the bounty information, and the image showed a pale male.

"Orozen, Blood Race… a wanted criminal from sixty years ago," Han Xiao murmured.

He did not recognize this man.

However, after linking it with Harrofal's message, the answer was clear—this Orozen was most likely a subordinate sent by EsGod.

"Why did they attack Harrofal?" Han Xiao frowned.

From what he knew, the only link that they had with EsGod was from the battle that happened seven years ago. Could it be that EsGod was so petty that because his doppelganger was tricked, he sent subordinates for revenge?

He felt that this was the only logical reason.

However, EsGod was maniac, and maniacs were not associated with logic.

Han Xiao had no idea if EsGod knew his current strength. If he had only sent Calamity Grade subordinates, it would basically be feeding him kills. Since even his doppelganger had failed, EsGod would definitely not be expecting his Calamity Grade subordinates to succeed.

After some thought, Han Xiao's eyes became firm.

"This means that these people are very likely to be able to summon EsGod's doppelganger like the DarkStar leader did!"

If this was really the case, it would be quite a tough situation.

Back then, he had been able to exile EsGod's doppelganger because of the terrain advantage and Harrofal's help, which he did not have now.

"I'm much stronger than before. After completing the Promotion after level 220, my health is almost double that of seven years ago. Plus, I have the Void Star Pursuer talent [Cosmic Environmental Adaptation], which greatly increases my defense. Even if I must face an EsGod doppelganger directly, I won't be in as much of a disadvantageous position as I was seven years ago… Hmm, if it's just a doppelganger, EsGod might not be able to threaten my life. Aurora's potions also give me the equivalent of many lives…"

Han Xiao quickly analyzed the situation. As he realized that the situation was not that horrible, he was slightly relieved.

Fortunately, Version 3.0 had begun, and he had already gained enough experience from it to become stronger once again. If he had been the same as seven years ago, EsGod's revenge would indeed have been very threatening to him.

After looking at news of Harrofal's death carefully again, Han Xiao sighed and could only mourn for this old friend of his that had once fought alongside him.

This time, a new mission suddenly popped up on the interface.

_____________________

You have triggered Grade A Bounty Mission [Harrofal's Revenge].

Mission Introduction: Harrofal is an important member of the Tyla Civilization. He was murdered, and the killer has caused an extremely horrible impact. The Tyla Civilization has issued a bounty. Anyone that avenges Harrofal will receive a huge amount of reward.

Mission Requirements: Kill or capture the bounty target—Orozen.

Reward: 236,000,000 Experience, 8,000,000 Enas bounty, +1,800 Tyla Civilization Favorability.

_____________________

To a Version 3.0 player, the difficulty of this mission is way above their abilities. No wonder the rewards are so good… Han Xiao tutted.

No players in Version 3.0 would be able to complete this mission. Missions with this kind of difficulty would only appear in at least two more versions.

However, Bounty Missions were not restricted by versions. Many people were wanted by civilizations or black markets. Even the players now would be able to accept Bounty Missions for Calamity Grades or even Beyond Grade As, just that they would certainly not be able to complete them.

For example, many Shattered Star Ring organizations had secretly issued bounties for Han Xiao on the black market, which totaled about ninety-two million Enas. This was an outrageous bounty for even major galactic pirates. However, most bounty hunters knew the limit of their capabilities, so no one would accept this kind suicide mission.

"The requirement is to avenge Harrofal…" Han Xiao murmured. "There's no need to waste energy tracking the culprit; that is Tyla Civilization's job. A Star Cluster civilization has more resources to track the culprit. It would be like searching for a needle in a haystack for me. If EsGod's subordinates are looking for revenge, they will most likely come for me. I will just have to wait."

After contemplating for a while, Han Xiao made up his mind. He was not planning to break his tempo of farming talents because of this mission.

If EsGod's subordinates were not coming, it would save him some trouble, but if they were indeed after him, he did not mind getting rid of the mission target. He was rather confident in this. After all, the outside world did not know that he had made another breakthrough in terms of strength.

According to the combat experience from seven years ago, he would just about be able to endure the pressure from an EsGod doppelganger.

Of course, being confident was one thing. The Great Mechanic Han would not be less alert because of it.

"I still have to be cautious…"

…

At the same time in a certain area in the Shattered Star Ring, three curved spaceships slowly flew between an asteroid belt in stealth mode. There were signs of a battle on these ships. Nano Robots were repairing their armor.

Inside the main ship, Colin, Orozen, and the rest were looking at the data records of a wormhole detector. This was a device that they had received from Harrofal. Inside was the many years of data of studying the wormholes, among which was the data of the time when an EsGod doppelganger fell into the wormhole.

"Hmm… the dates align. This is the data that His Excellency EsGod wants." Orozen grinned, showing a few fangs. "The memories I read are indeed correct."

Orozen's Esper ability was the rare 'Race Strengthening', which enhanced his Racial Talents as a member of the Blood Race. He had the ability to read the memories of the target whose blood he consumed. These people did not kidnap Harrofal to interrogate and torture him but to let Orozen suck his blood and get the intelligence they wanted. Harrofal's cause of death was his blood being drained dry completely while he was still alive.

"But due to your stupidity, the Tyla Civilization discovered your identity," Colin said coldly. "The entire Star Cluster civilization is now searching for us. Maybe they will be able to discover that we're members of the Fallen Ark. If not because you're still a little useful, I would've killed you."

Orozen did not care at all. He leaned back on the sofa, crossed his legs, and said lazily, "So what? The Tyla Civilization won't be able to catch up to our spaceships. Plus, this is the Shattered Star Ring, not the Central Galaxy ruled by the three Universal Civilizations.

"Is it necessary to be this careful? Might as well have some fun. So what if an organization in this remote Star Field discovers who we are? Can they go to the Central Galaxy to fight Fallen Ark?

"Plus, even if they really dare to go there, they will only end up being demolished by His Excellency EsGod."

Colin snorted. "If any accidents happen during the operation, I will make you pay."

"Instead of worrying about something so unimportant, how about sending the data back first?" Orozen shrugged and snickered.

Colin did not continue hanging onto the fact that their identities had been partially exposed. Through the super-long-range quantum communication device, he sent the wormhole data back to the Fallen Ark.

This way, the first mission given by His Excellency EsGod was complete.

Colin was rather satisfied with their efficiency. After planning for more than half a month, they had successfully kidnapped Harrofal and retrieved the data right away. The mission was going smoothly.

Since they had obtained the data, there was no need for them to find Black Star.

This team had three EsGod doppelgangers in their hands, which were all given different abilities. Colin did not want to waste any of them on Black Star—these were all important trump cards that EsGod had given them to steal the Evolution Cube.

Stealing the Evolution Cube from Psyker was the most important mission of this trip. Comparatively, kidnapping Harrofal was a walk in the park.

Colin clapped his hands and said with a deep voice, "The data has been sent. It's time to get down to business. Psyker is a Beyond Grade A, so we need a detailed plan and a suitable opening."

The three spaceships changed direction and headed to the Star System where Psyker resided.

…

In a desolate universe belt outside the Central Galaxy, the main army of the Fallen Ark was resting in their secret stronghold.

In the main ship, an officer woke EsGod up from his sleep.

"Your Excellency EsGod, the team we sent to the Shattered Star Ring had sent back the data you wanted."

Upon hearing the officer's report, EsGod woke up. The black vortex under his hood turned into a face. He then smiled strangely and said with a husky voice, "Good… good. Have the research team analyze this wormhole data and find the place that the other side of the wormhole was connected to at that time. I want to know the coordinates of that place in the universe."

"Understood."

"Hmm… let me think. Right, I told them to bring the Evolution Cube back. Have they succeeded?"

"They have yet to send any information related to that. They should still be on the task."

EsGod slowly nodded and mumbled, "I have finally discovered where the Evolution Cube is. The Arcane Church has been looking for it for so long. They have no idea that the leftover records of the Evolutionary Civilization have always been in my head. I'm the rightful heir of the Evolution Cube. It can help me achieve a higher level of evolution. Psyker has no right to such a treasure…"

Chapter 745: Tomar

"My name is Tomar Tykin.

"I was born in Yellow Leaf Town of the Ocean Boundary Kingdom. I was adopted by the only orphanage in the town before I could remember, where I spent my childhood.

"I can still remember when I was six years old, I saw a few slightly older children from the town doing weird things to older sister Shanna in an alley two streets away from the orphanage.

"Sister Shanna was the oldest child in the orphanage. She always took care of everyone, and we all saw her as our older sister. She had freckles on her face. I think that she looked very pretty and gentle when she smiled with the dimples on her cheeks. I always dreamed of her when I was little.

"I thought that they were bullying older sister Shanna, so I picked up a stone and threw it at the forehead of one of them. Then, they beat me up. After growing up, only then did I know what they were doing to Shanna back then.

"After that, older sister Shanna left the town without saying goodbye. I don't know where she went.

"Then, the guy whose forehead I hit went to the orphanage to complain. The head of the orphanage scolded me. I asked him why my parents didn't have my back. He said that my parents died long ago. They went into the mountains to harvest things and met demonic spirits.

"Only then did I know that I had no one to rely on in this world.

"When I was ten, I left the orphanage and became an apprentice at the carpenters' workshop in town.

"When I was fifteen, my teacher got a job that needed him to go to Stone Heart City, which was nearby. He brought us there, and after working there for half a month, we finally finished the job. On that night, Pilly cheekily said that he was going to take me to a good place. Pilly was the senior apprentice of the carpenter workshop, a few years older than me. Then, we went to a pub in Stone Heart City called 'Honey'. That was the first time I ever drank. In that place, I saw Sister Shanna, whom I had not seen for many years.

"She was working in the pub. She had thick makeup on her face, and she smiled more than before. But her smile looked fake to me. It reminded me of the smiley-faced dolls I carved hundreds of times.

"Her job was to take food to the guests. When she passed by, there were always people who placed their hands on her body. Every time that happened, she smiled more clearly and even faker. I remember that she was still very young, but I noticed that she already had wrinkles at the edges of her eyes.

"Pilly said that I was an adult now. He had already paid, so Sister Shanna would take me to the second floor and help me to become an adult. Only then did I realize that she had become a prostitute, and her business was quite good. Many people paid for her.

"I remember how my mind became blank. I fought with Pilly but lost. He was taller and tougher than me. I was pressed on the floor and beaten up badly. Sister Shanna did not come to help. I don't know if she recognized me.

"After that, I was thrown out of the pub. My eyes swollen, and my body hurt, but I did not want to return to the hotel and wandered around the streets.

"On that night, I met a wizard.

"Sometimes, I can't help but admit how unpredictable life can be. When I was a kid, I never thought that I would become a wizard in the future.

"Over the next five years, I learned all kinds of spells and ways to make magic potions in Stone Heart City. Mister Lanley always praised me, saying that I'm talented. I don't know if he meant it… Anyhow, I stepped into another hidden world. My old life became distant and unreachable.

"The others set a goal for me—to beat a person called Vosumede. Although I didn't know him, everyone said that he's my enemy.

"When I was twenty, I met four people who called themselves deities. I never thought that this would be the turning point of my life.

"Their appearance changed everything. They easily completed the goal that us wizards in the gathering point had spent fifty years fighting for. I saw my enemy, Vosumede, for the first time, and then he was casually killed by the deities.

"The deities chose me and brought me to the Kingdom of Deities. I thought I would then become a faithful believer, but everything that happened after overthrew my knowledge of everything.

"We boarded a huge metal box, and this box could actually fly. When we entered the sky, I realized that my world was actually a ball!

"Why is it a ball‽ I don't understand!

"The God of Luck told me that the world I was in is called Nalun. It's something called a planet. Outside the planet is a place called the universe. In the universe, there are countless planets like Planet Nalun.

"I was really shocked, more shocked than when I realized the existence of deities. I never could have thought of something like this even in my wildest imaginations.

"However, the God of Luck then told me that them being so called deities was just a joke. They were just visitors from the universe, and I'm the only one from Planet Nalun to enter the galaxy. I could not believe that this had happened to me!

"He said that his name was Feidin, and he told me what the real world was like. This completely shattered my past world view.

"Feidin said that they were all members of the Black Star Army. That guy who tricked me is the leader of the army. I have never seen someone this shameless before…

"Nonetheless, I felt gratitude toward him. If he had not chosen me, I would have forever been an ignorant native like Feidin said, never getting to know the truth of the universe. His Excellency Black Star changed my entire life.

"The Black Star Army seems to be a very strong organization in the universe, and I became a member of the Black Star Army… Alright, I'm used to things like this. Just like back in the gathering point, I once again joined an organization out of nowhere.

"For many days, I was confused and lost. While Feidin taught me the general knowledge of the world, he told me that if I don't know what to do, I should take helping my mother planet as my life goal—this is the destiny of a pioneer of a civilization.

"Honestly, I like this destiny.

"Mister Feidin helped me a lot. I think he's a good man. He looks nice when he smiles, like Sister Shanna in the past.

"After a few days, I was sent up to another spaceship. They were sending me to the Black Star Army headquarters to learn magic. They said that I'm talented. Sigh, why does everyone think I'm a magic genius? Isn't magic very simple?

"I was handed over to a person that looked miserable and depressed. He said that he would be my teacher from now on.

"Honestly, I don't think he's a suitable teacher. He told me, 'Magic is actually not that useful. Just learn something so that I can say I've done my part.'"

…

Three months later, on Planet Macipher…

This was a well known, neutral planet in the Shattered Star Ring, located at the edge of the Star Field and not ruled by any civilization.

At this moment, Han Xiao's spaceship was hovering above Planet Macipher.

Three months had passed since his trip to Planet Nalun.

In those three months, the biggest battle up till now had erupted in the secret war. As the Crimson Dynasty leaked rumors about the negotiation starting to come to an end, Section Zero and the Bloodshed Land began an all-out war to delay the time. The two sides gave up all conservative strategies and fought head-on.

The warfare was tragic. In just the short three months, the Calamity Grades that died on both sides added up to close to a hundred.

Han Xiao did not participate, and Purple Crystal allowed that, but the Black Star Army had to fight given how many resources they had consumed.

The army was led by Lagi and Herlous. The players were given suicidal missions, so the number of casualties of lower-middle combatants was kept to an acceptable range. As for the high-level combatants, without their leader, Black Star, many Calamity Grades were injured. However, Han Xiao told Aurora to make some super strong recovery potions that saved lives in crucial times. Thanks to that, none of the high-level combatants of the army died.

During all that, Han Xiao took Hila, Aurora, and Feidin to travel all around the Star Field to do side missions. Tomar was the only protagonist character that he had been able to woo. This leek was given to Lagi to slowly cultivate. Han Xiao had obtained five new talents in the past three months.

Three of them were common talents, and two were rare talents. All of them were useful in some way. His actual combat capability increased to a certain extent. However, the most important thing that he received was not those talents but the Experience that he had been hoarding throughout the three months.

The senior players and new players of the army provided him with plenty of Experience. According to his calculation, that Experience was more than enough for him to level up to above level 235. He was getting closer to level 240.

The speed of getting Experience is faster than I expected. It seems to be because these new players are starting to learn Advanced Knowledges as well. At this rate, in about half a month, my Experience would be enough for me to reach level 240…

Inside the spaceship, Han Xiao was rather excited.

He had yet to use the Experience on leveling up—this was mainly because he wanted to use the Experience as a trump card for dealing with the possible revenge of EsGod's subordinates.

However, after waiting for three months, EsGod's subordinates had yet to appear.

Since the enemies did not appear, he was in no hurry to level up. After all, the Experience was not going anywhere.

Thus, Han Xiao continued to farm talents. Planet Macipher was his next stop.

This neutral planet was known for two things—their enormous black market that consisted of countless products and their developed galactic shipyard industry.

There were a ton of mechanical and magic based shipyards there. A large number of spaceship models could be ordered there. Many galactic travelers went to Planet Macipher to build ships.

As it was a neutral planet, Planet Macipher was filled with all kinds of people. The shipyards did not care about the guests' identity; anyone could make an order as long as they paid for it. Quite a number of galactic pirates or wanted criminals would put on a disguise and go there to purchase and resupply their spaceships.

Neutral planets always had a powerful ruler, and Planet Macipher was no exception. The owner of this planet was called Sardeem, nicknamed 'Giant Soldier Architect', a powerful Grade A+ Mechanic.

However, Han Xiao's goal for this trip was not him.

Through the spaceship porthole, Han Xiao looked down on the metal planet surface of Planet Macipher. He then turned around to the others and said, "Let's put on a disguise. We're not using our real faces here."

As he spoke, Han Xiao placed a transparent membrane on his face. Electrical circuits flashed on the membrane surface and turned into the face of another person.

This was a mask that he had learned to make a long time ago. The technology used in it had been updated dozens of times, and it was much more undetectable.

Hila and the others did not ask why and wore the membranes to disguise themselves—they had become used to Han Xiao's strange actions in the past three months.

There was an obtainable Mechanic class talent on Planet Macipher. Its effect was to enhance the ability to build machines.

This was a mission exclusive to Mechanics. He had to apply for employment in a certain shipyard and become a shipbuilder. Of course, with Black Star's identity, there was no doubt that he would not become a shipbuilder of a shipyard. Thus, Han Xiao had to disguise himself, cover up his handsome face, and be an ordinary man temporarily. Only then would he be able to trigger the mission.

After I'm done with this mission, I should have around enough Experience to reach level 240…

Han Xiao took a deep breath, clenched his fists, and gave the order to Phillip.

"Descend."

Chapter 746: Planet Macipher and the Cornerstone Summit Corporation

As Planet Macipher was not a colonial planet but an industrial neutral planet that would naturally attract people, there were only five cities on the planet's surface—one main city and four sub cities. Han Xiao landed in the main city, which was the biggest.

Looking down from above, Planet Macipher had a very strong industrial theme. It was mainly made up of large spaceship yards. Some were even assembling large spaceships in the open, and the skeletons of these spaceships could be seen from above. There were no actual residences on the planet, only the hostels for the Mechanic workers and entertainment facilities, as well as all sorts of hotels for the galactic travelers.

At the heart of the city was a conch-shaped mechanical hovering city—this was the base of 'Giant Soldier Architect' Sardeem. It was wide at the bottom and narrow at the top. Sixteen two-hundred-and-forty-meter-tall sentry-type mechanical Giant Soldiers were mounted at the base of the hovering city, which were all in standby mode and would automatically be activated when attacked. They were very powerful.

The three branches of the Mechanic class all had their specialties. Sardeem was clearly an Armed Branch Grade A+ Mechanic that mastered building powerful mechanical Giant Soldiers.

Planet Macipher had eight planet surface ports. Han Xiao's spaceship followed the instructions from the surface and landed in Surface Port 3 before entering the hangar. After Han Xiao went through the simple procedures, he led the disguised Hila and the others out of the port, mixing into the crowd and entering the city.

There were beings from all kinds of races on the streets—human-like beings and even some pedipalp beings—all galactic residents from different Star Clusters. The universal translator allowed them to communicate with each other at ease.

"It's so boisterous here. Both are neutral planets. Why is Floating Dragon so quiet?" Aurora looked around curiously.

"Well, that's because Floating Dragon doesn't have a specialty, and it's not friendly to foreign financial groups."

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled. Places with Beyond Grade As in them were always popular. The reason that Floating Dragon did not prosper was completely due to their strategy—Ames did not want to develop Floating Dragon at all.

Furthermore, from the aspect of the territory type, Planet Macipher was a pure industrial planet while Floating Dragon was Ames' home. The management mode and openness of the two were different.

Sardeem had enough strength to be the boss of an organization. He was also a Mechanic who was good at attracting investments and businesses. Thus, it was easy for him to make a place popular.

Hu!

This time, the sound of energy spraying flashed past the sky. They looked up, and a team of mechanical soldiers happened to pass by. They were the armed forces that Sardeem used to maintain the law. They were also his own mechanical troops.

Opening a neutral planet is quite profitable. Hmm, although my Black Star Army is at a higher level, making a neutral industrial planet seems to be quite a good idea. It can gather more leeks… Hmm, but that's a matter to think about after the secret war ends…

Han Xiao caressed his chin and pondered about the business expansion of the army.

Black Star's name was quite well known in the Shattered Star Ring. Fortunately, they had put on a disguise, so no one recognized him. The group boarded ground vehicles and went to a shipyard at the center area of the main city.

This shipyard was extremely large and grand. Han Xiao and the rest stopped outside the gate and looked up at the colorful floating virtual signboard. On it were the words 'Cornerstone Summit Corporation' written in Universal Language.

This was one of the most credible and reputable shipyards on Planet Macipher.

"This is the right place." Han Xiao nodded. He opened the communicator. On it was the hiring notice of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation.

This kind of large shipyards recruited Mechanics constantly. The minimum requirement was Grade Cs or owners of a Mechanic Technician Work Permit distributed by a Star System civilization—just like companies in the real world that required minimum education qualifications.

Han Xiao did not have a Machinery Technician Work Permit. This was something that only those Supers focusing on researching and life skills needed. Its main purpose was to make things more convenient for research personnel and technicians that did not like fighting. Han Xiao had never had a need for this. Plus, with his Grade, he would get it easily without any tests if he wanted to.

Supers had extraordinary powers. Some used this power for violence—such as the galactic pirates, mercenaries, and bounty hunters. Some used this power to produce and manufacture things. Supers were also important labor and production forces in the galactic society.

Among which, the business of Mechanics and Mages was the most popular. Some Espers with special Esper abilities also had quite good business, and Psychics were suitable for therapy, reconnaissance, and the like. Pugilists were the only ones that had very worrying futures in the business world. After all, Pugilists were the best in manual labor jobs, which was something even robots could do but for a much cheaper price. After all, who would hire Pugilists just to carry things around the site‽

Han Xiao and the rest walked into the shipyard. There were many guests in the reception hall who were all there to order spaceships. They were using the self-service screens to browse through the spaceship models available and make orders.

Han Xiao went to an unoccupied self-service screen and pressed on manual service instantly. The next moment, the image on the screen changed into a pretty lady receptionist of the Galaxy Human Race.

"Hello, welcome to the Cornerstone Summit Corporation. How may I help you?"

"I'm a Mechanic here to look for employment." Han Xiao expressed his intentions. The disguise was effective, and he would not be recognized.

"Okay, please follow the reception robot. You will be led to an interviewer.

A palm-sized, spherical robot wearing a mini receptionist uniform flew over. It was really adorable. It bowed and led the way.

They left the reception hall, passed by the exterior factories, and entered a huge workshop. Han Xiao immediately saw quite a few low-level Mechanics working on the various workbenches, assembling parts.

This time, an old man approached. His white hair was tied into a braid behind his head, and he was smiling. He looked rather amiable.

"Hi, I'm a Senior Machinery Engineer of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, Luke."

Right, I need an alias as well… Han Xiao smiled and said, "I'm Barne."

Luke paused and said with a deep voice, "Cornerstone Summit Corporation is constantly recruiting Mechanics. You should've seen the requirements. Which kind of test would you like to take? Showing your permit or testing your Grade?"

"Testing my Grade."

Luke nodded. He raised his hand and released a wave of Mechanical Force. He then grabbed the reception robot in his hand. The energy that he emitted had reached the Grade B standard.

He secretly sized Han Xiao up. Seeing that Han Xiao's expression did not change, he then pressed a few more times on the reception robot. A probe popped out from the head of the robot. This was a device used to detect a person's Energy Rank.

"I assume you know how to use this thing. Just release your Mechanical Force toward the probe," Luke said.

Han Xiao exhaled deeply and carefully controlled the Mechanical Force inside his body. He worried that he might release too much of it and expose his Grade A identity.

A stream of Mechanical Force shot out from his fingertips. As Luke saw the results, his expression changed immediately, and his tone suddenly became enthusiastic.

"You're a Grade B+ Mechanic‽"

That was still too much… Han Xiao thought in resignation.

Grade B+ was basically the top talent that a shipyard could employ. Although Calamity Grades were common in the secret war, they were exceedingly rare in normal galactic life. There was no way a Grade A would look for a job in a normal shipyard like this.

"Are there any other tests?"

"No, no, we will immediately give you the Senior Engineer position and salary. This is what someone at your Grade deserves."

Luke was very enthusiastic. In the corporation, being Grade B was the basic requirement of becoming a Senior Engineer, but one still had to accumulate contributions before becoming one. Anyone at Grade B+, however, could become a Senior Engineer immediately.

"Please wait a moment. I will tell my superiors to discuss with you directly."

Then, he turned around and instantly reported the situation to his higher ups before passionately escorting Han Xiao around to tour the various areas of the shipyard.

Not long after, a few Cornerstone Summit Corporation managers arrived and sincerely discussed the terms with Han Xiao. Han Xiao came just for the talent, so the two-year contract was very quickly agreed and signed by both parties, which included the usual terms such as not allowing Han Xiao to leak some blueprints and such.

Of course, Han Xiao was not planning to comply with the contract. He signed the contract as 'Barne' and planned to leave as soon as he received the talent. Even if his real identity was exposed someday, with his position in the galaxy, would this shipyard dare to go after him for breaching the contract?

Furthermore, he was not planning on hurting their profit.

I, a peak Calamity Grade, am working for you. What else do you want?

As the contract was signed, Luke smiled and shook hands with Han Xiao.

"The Cornerstone Summit Corporation welcomes you."

Han Xiao nodded. "What project do I need to be responsible for?"

"Hmm, well, the corporation recently accepted a high-level order from one of our big customers. They provided the blueprint and asked us to mass produce a rather rare battleship model. Our assembly lines are unable to build some parts of it that require very advanced technology. Only Grade B Mechanics and above are able to learn and build these extremely complicated blueprints. Therefore, we used many of our Senior Engineers, but the progress is not optimal at the moment…"

"Understood, so my job is to build some of these parts." Han Xiao nodded.

"Yes. I shall first arrange your accommodation, then I will give a part of the blueprint to you. You have five days to learn the blueprint before borrowing the corporation's factory to build it. Every Senior Engineer has a quota to meet. You're new, so your schedule might be a little packed," Luke explained.

Five days is completely unnecessary. Just give me the blueprint and I will learn it within a second… Han Xiao laughed in his mind. Plus, with the manufacturing ability of a Calamity Grade, mass building spaceship parts was a piece of cake.

Finally, a mission popped up on the interface.

[Engineer]

Mission Introduction: First line in the Mechanic Code of Conduct—A Mechanic's career is incomplete without the experience of using others' resources to train oneself!

Mission Requirements: Using the Cornerstone Summit Corporation's resources, build 1,500 products of any type (must be for the corporation).

Current Progress: 0/1,500

Reward: 6,500,000 Experience, [Proficient Technician] talent.

It finally triggered. Han Xiao was joyous.

Although the name of this talent was a little boring, its effects were rather good. Talents that could strengthen the main class were always valuable.

He now had a total of twelve Mechanic type talents—[Energy Modification], [Machinery Analytical Comprehension], [Virtual Technology Essence], [Machinery Theory Summary], [Military Machinery Enlightenment], [Flexible Weapon Usage], [Super Electromagnetic Sense], [Elementary Grade Mechanical Sense], [Assembly Line Professional], [High Level Mechanical Suit Pilot], [Machinery Truth Knowledge], and [Mechanical Force Ascension—Apostle Body]. Most of them came from the Class Advancement of his main class.

The bonuses from these Mechanic type talents added up to a considerable amount.

…

For the rest of the day, Luke accompanied Han Xiao to know more about the areas within the shipyard. When night arrived, his accommodation was finally arranged. He would be staying in the high-level hostel at the internal area of the corporation. The other three had been acting as his bodyguards, so they moved in as well.

After they finished unpacking, Aurora could not help but ask, "Uncle, do you have some other motive for working here?"

"Oh?" Han Xiao wondered.

"You actually want to steal their blueprints, right?" Aurora said with an excited tone and a smug expression.

"You're overthinking this. I don't need to do such low standard things." Han Xiao's mouth twitched. "If I wanted a blueprint, I can just buy it. I'm not poor."

"Black Star, we're not really going to stay here for two years, are we?" Feidin suddenly asked.

"Of course not, what are you thinking?"

Feidin sighed. "We've followed you around for three months. You said this was to experience different lives and see more things, but I really can't figure out how this will help you to break through and reach Beyond Grade A."

Han Xiao had no choice but to create an excuse. "I fought a seven-year-long war and did not improve much if at all. Maybe relaxing will give me something different."

"Anyway," Feidin said with resignation, "you have to know that you really don't have much time left. If you aren't able to break through, it's best to make plans. Be it asking for the Dragon Emperor's help or escaping the Shattered Star Ring, you have to at least have a plan."

You're saying it in a way as if I'm near my doom… It would be great if you're Lagi…

This time, someone rang the doorbell. Luke walked in carrying a thick stack of blueprints, placed them on the table, and chatted for a while before leaving.

These were the blueprints for three parts—to prevent the technology of the entire spaceship being leaked, every Senior Engineer received blueprints of different parts and was responsible for the production of those parts.

Han Xiao quickly browsed through the blueprints in less than a minute. The blueprints of these three parts were recognized by the interface and quickly turned into abilities, fully learned by Han Xiao.

"The technology level of these three parts is a little high. Usual spaceships won't need to use these three parts. Only super large spaceships do…"

Han Xiao was stunned.

If he was not wrong, only spaceships using Star Cluster level technology would need these three parts…

Linking these factors together… could the order that the Cornerstone Summit Corporation had received be to build a Star Cluster grade flagship? Like the Star Diamond Grade Flagship of the Purple Crystal Civilization‽

That would be a secret manufacturing process even for Star Cluster civilizations!

Han Xiao was tempted. He was not an Armed Branch Mechanic and always had a shortage of blueprints for large machines. All he had that was considerably impactful was the armed satellite fortress. If he could obtain the blueprint of a Star Cluster grade flagship, it would be an amazing surprise.

Chapter 747: Eternal Light and Sardeem's Attention

The next day, Han Xiao arrived at the shipyard early in the morning and was ready to craft the spaceship parts assigned to him.

For the sake of secrecy, the blueprint of the spaceship would be split into different groups and given to different Senior Engineers to complete. The core components of the spaceship would be crafted by the direct subordinates of the organization. New engineers like him usually would not be involved in such a large order.

The Cornerstone Summit Corporation considered the problem of the deadline and also the Grade B+ strength that Han Xiao had displayed. Thus, they had pulled him into their plans. However, they would never pass the core portions of the blueprint to him.

The three components that Han Xiao was in charge of had a high technical requirement but were not core components. Because it was a high-grade made-to-order component, the corporation did not have a corresponding assembly line. As such, the high-grade engineers were put to use.

He originally did not plan to steal the blueprint, but if it was a Star Cluster grade flagship… cough cough… since it was the job of a Mechanic, could it be considered stealing?

He planned to make use of his Virtual Technology skill to infiltrate the database of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation. He should be able to steal the basic framework of the Star Cluster grade flagship. The virtual engineer that the Cornerstone Summit Corporation had hired to guard their database was no more than a little brother in front of him. He could easily take a stroll in the other party's backyard without anyone noticing.

Most important blueprints were still being kept in hardcopy format. Although such a method was pretty prehistoric, it would never become outdated. After all, Virtual Mechanics were infamous all around the world, and no one wanted their own database to be eyed up by others every day.

The Cornerstone Summit Corporation was currently rushing to complete an order, and his construction speed was his advantage. As long as he could complete the quota on his hands, the corporation would probably give him the blueprints of a few more parts for him to construct. He could then farm for progress points for his mission.

As long as he found a way to steal the remaining parts of the blueprint, he would be able to complete the blueprints of the entire flagship.

Upon arriving at the work region for high grade engineers, Han Xiao immediately saw Luke and greeted him.

"Barne, why are you here?" Luke was a little surprised.

"Why do you look so surprised?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"I thought that you would spend the entire day learning the blueprints. If you want to view your workbench, I will get someone to show you around. The deadline is coming up, and I am extremely busy. I will not have time for anything else."

Luke thought that Han Xiao was there to familiarize himself with his workplace.

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "You misunderstand. I'm here to start work."

Luke's eyes widened upon hearing that. "You only needed a single night to learn the blueprints I gave you‽"

This efficiency was way too high, right?

He was truly in disbelief. The parts of these high-grade spaceships were extremely complicated, and he had needed a full three days to grasp them. The way he saw it, Han Xiao should have needed a day or two to learn it at the very least. However, to think that he was actually able to learn them in a single night!

Han Xiao looked at Luke, who was in a daze, and said, "I shall get to work if there isn't anything else."

Luke snapped out of his daze and hurriedly said, "Alright, alright, I won't disturb you anymore."

Han Xiao nodded and entered his workshop.

Luke only retracted his gaze when he saw Han Xiao close the door. This new colleague Barne was even more amazing than he had thought.

The access card of a Senior Engineer could gain access to a high-grade workshop of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation. The facilities of the workshop were extremely complete, and although it could not be compared to his personal workshop in the Black Star Army, it was still extremely valuable.

Closing the door, Han Xiao was the only one left in the workshop. He then looked around at the workshop and nodded.

"They gave me a deadline of half a month to complete my parts, but I will only need half a day to complete them. Hmm, I think this is a little too exaggerated. I should slow down a bit and drag it out for three days…"

Clank!

Han Xiao then flicked out a series of compressed orbs to form various different assistants. These were specially modified machines that he had constructed personally and were peak Grade A+ machines. These machines could not be bought on the market and were his personal equipment.

Buzz!

Mechanical Force shot out from his arms, and his assistants all began to spring into action. They then made use of all the various materials and began their construction.

His large pool of experience was the reason behind why he was not afraid of the Soul Embryo. As he constructed the parts, he used his [Quantum Network Matrix] to connect to the network of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation and infiltrated their database.

Han Xiao's Virtual Technology skill was more than sufficient to deal with the firewall of an ordinary shipyard corporation. He easily hid his tracks and went past the firewall and alarm of the database. He then got Phillip to make a copy of all their information.

"Let me see what kind of good stuff there is…" Han Xiao was in a good mood.

An endless stream of information appeared in his mind, including records of all the Cornerstone Summit Corporation's past transactions. After eliminating all the useless information from his mind, Han Xiao dug out a bunch of useful information.

Blueprints of high-grade spaceships would not be kept in the database, and a special safe would have been constructed to store it. However, the location of the safe was not located on the map, so he did not know the location of the blueprints.

The blueprints kept within the database were those of ordinary spaceships, but Han Xiao would not reject any freebies and accepted them all. Even the meat of a mosquito was considered meat. Furthermore, he had the talent [Research Theory] and would gain one Intelligence point for every three skills. It would only benefit him to learn more blueprint skills.

After searching for a while, Han Xiao finally found information about what he was looking for—the recent large order for the Cornerstone Summit Corporation.

"Eternal Light fortress‽" Han Xiao was stunned.

This flagship model was truly too famous. It was not the product of any Star Cluster civilization within the Shattered Star Ring but one of the flagship models of the Federation of Light!

Although the Eternal Light was not the trump card flagship of a Universal Civilization, it was still a top model. In ordinary galactic wars, this was one of the main flagships of the Federation of Light. The combat capability of the Eternal Light was comparable to Star Cluster level flagships and was even stronger in terms of energy. Furthermore, the cost to construct it was also cheaper, and it was one of the flagships within the Federation of Light that had a lower technical requirement.

Battleship blueprints of the Federation of Light could not even be found on the black market. To think that an ordinary shipyard in the Shattered Star Ring was actually able to construct the high-grade battleship of a Universal Civilization.

Is there a reason behind this?

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he could not help but think about various possibilities.

For the Federation of Light to secretly employ local workshops in the Shattered Star Ring to construct battleships, are they actually trying to build up their forces in this Star Field? Could it be that they're about to make a big move? If that's the case, the Cornerstone Summit Corporation shouldn't be the only corporation constructing Federation of Light battleships.

Eh, that's not right. The Federation of Light should have their own secret warehouses in the Shattered Star Ring, so there's no need for them to outsource production. Furthermore, the only reason for them to build up their forces in the Shattered Star Ring would be to fight against the Crimson Dynasty… Could it be that their negotiations with the Crimson Dynasty are no more than a farce and they wish to occupy the Flickering World with force?

That doesn't seem too likely. Not to mention the fact that there wasn't such a storyline in my previous life, if the Federation of Light wanted to do so, they would have sent an army already…

After exploring the different options, Han Xiao had a more reliable guess.

This matter should not be related to the Federation of Light. Perhaps an individual got the blueprints from some unknown channel and placed an order with the Cornerstone Summit Corporation for them to aid with the construction.

If that was the case, this large customer would either have extremely close ties with the Cornerstone Summit Corporation or was an existence that the corporation could not afford to offend. If not, they would not dare to casually provide such a valuable blueprint.

If this is the case, stealing the blueprint will be even more difficult than I imagined. I may even offend a powerful organization in the process…

Han Xiao frowned slightly.

I am 'Barne' now and not 'Black Star' anyway. What has Barne stealing blueprints got to do with Black Star?

He can just steal the blueprints and run away.

However, the basic framework of the Eternal Light fortress was stored within the database. The framework of the spaceship referred to the outer armor and components of the spaceship and formed the outer shell of the spaceship. It was akin to the skeleton and skin of a spaceship and did not have any core technical skills involved. Because the external frame of such a large flagship would usually be constructed outside the atmosphere, the technical skills involved were extremely high and required the aid of an artificial intelligence. Thus, the blueprints of the framework were entered into the database.

The core components of a spaceship included the energy furnace, shield generator, hyperdrive engine, and many more. All those components formed the organs of the spaceship and were much more important than the outer frame.

As Han Xiao viewed the framework of the Eternal Light fortress, a notification popped up on his interface.

You have received [Battleship Blueprint: Eternal Light (Incomplete)!

It's fine even if it's incomplete. I'd better get the other parts of the blueprint… Han Xiao thought to himself.

Over the next ten or so days, Han Xiao hid himself within the shipyard to construct components, and the progress of his [Engineer] mission shot up.

He completed the first target in three days, and the upper echelons of the corporation were stunned.

After checking to ensure that there were no problems with the quality of the components, the upper echelons all felt that they had truly picked up a treasure. They then passed the blueprints of a few more parts to Han Xiao, and he completed them in less than two days.

The upper echelons of the corporation then gave Han Xiao a few more blueprints, which were completed extremely quickly. However, the upper echelons immediately fell into a conundrum. Han Xiao's efficiency had far exceeded their expectations, and they were faced with a problem. If things continued as such, this new recruit 'Barne' would learn of many more blueprints. If this continued, it would go against their initial plans of splitting up the blueprint into parts to lower their risk.

Just when the upper echelons were hesitating, the big boss behind the corporation came to inspect their progress.

In the conference room, Sardeem flipped through the latest report of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, and his gaze swept over the managers who were by the side.

"I am disappointed in your efficiency. Why isn't the Eternal Light constructed yet?"

"Your Excellency Sardeem, this is the flagship model of a Universal Civilization. We can't construct it quickly with our technical skills. Furthermore, our corporation only has one Grade B+ engineer at the very most, and the production capability of those high-grade components is too low…"

"Oh?" Sardeem narrowed his eyes. "I truly wonder if all of your attention is only on the sales figures of the shipyard. All of you only want to increase your sales figures for the outside world and don't want to do your jobs?"

"You… you misunderstood us. We do not have such thoughts!" The expressions of the upper echelons changed greatly, and they hurriedly defended themselves.

Although they were the upper echelons of the corporation, Sardeem was the true boss, and the Cornerstone Summit Corporation was actually Sardeem's property. Apart from accepting the orders of the outside world, their other responsibility was to produce machines for Sardeem.

If Sardeem was the ruler of Planet Macipher, then the Cornerstone Summit Corporation was a state enterprise. As long as Sardeem was willing, he would be able to easily take back the authority of those managers.

Constructing the Eternal Light fortress was a mission that Sardeem had given the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, and the blueprint belonged to him.

"Don't forget whose subordinates all of you are," Sardeem warned. "I will give you four more months. If all of you still cannot complete the Eternal Light…"

The upper echelons hurriedly expressed their loyalty. "Don't worry, we will definitely construct it."

Sardeem then nodded and suddenly asked after reading the report, "You hired a new Senior Engineer?"

"Yes, he is called Barne."

Sardeem then pointed at the data displayed on the report. "Even if he is a Grade B+ Mechanic, his efficiency is extremely rare. Hmm, there are two possibilities. He may be an extremely talented Mechanic with the potential to become a Calamity Grade Super, or… he hid his strength because of some motive."

The upper echelons were stunned. "What should we do?"

"You do not need to bother about this."

Sardeem waved his arms and revealed an excited look.

"If it is the former, it wouldn't be a bad idea for me to take in a disciple with potential. If it is the latter, it may be even better."

All the upper echelons then looked at each other.

"Then how should we arrange his job? Do we continue to let him construct the Eternal Light? With his efficiency, he will probably learn a large number of blueprints."

Sardeem's mouth curled up, and he said, "We just need to protect the blueprints of the core components. There's no need to be worried about the other parts being leaked."

"Alright." No one dared to rebut.

Sardeem then stood up and had a teasing look in his eyes. "Observe him for a while. I will find the time to come into contact with him. I think that he will be an interesting fellow."

The sea of stars was boundless, and the universe was endless.

The Shattered Star Ring was at the edge of the explored universe. This Star Field was split into more than ten Star Clusters and at least a thousand Star Systems.

Among all these Star Systems, the Eternal Night Star System was one of the most special ones.

Because a new Star Cluster Civilization was being born in this Star System.

Under the lead of their leader, their civilization rose at an unprecedented speed. Their race evolved at an unbelievable rate, and their race would forever remember the glory that their leader brought them. They changed the name of their race and were called the Star Pupil Holy Race.

Psyker was the leader of this civilization.

Today, the Star Pupil Holy Race welcomed an uninvited guest.

Chapter 748: Target: Evolution Cube!

Planet Avitan of the Eternal Night Star System was not the Star Pupil Holy Race's mother planet. It was a highly developed administrative planet. Its location was optimal, and it was an important financial center. There were more than twelve billion residents on this planet.

In a certain main city on Planet Avitan, hovering carriers flitted between the tall buildings. The Star Pupil Holy Race people who were born with the ability to fly were travelling in the sky following the traffic rules. The city was peaceful and prosperous.

However, on this day, the peace on Planet Avitan was shattered.

A crimson meteor suddenly appeared and started descending extremely quickly from outer space. The radars did not detect the movement of this meteor before this at all, as if it had appeared out of nowhere.

The meteor descended at an extremely high speed, right toward this main city. The time in which the fleet stationed at Planet Avitan could react was very little.

Countless fully automatic planetary defense formations deployed outside the planet's atmosphere quickly responded, releasing an enormous amount of dark energy and forming a net that extended more than a hundred miles, standing in the path of the meteor's descent.

Such devices were usually used to stop meteor showers. The dark energy was close to materializing. It had extremely strong elasticity, toughness, and extensibility. The net could make use of the tens of thousands of meters between the atmosphere and the ground as the buffer zone to shroud the meteor and stop it.

However, the meteor penetrated this dark energy net instantly like a knife cutting through silk.

The automatic defense formation immediately started executing the second plan. It launched countless homing annihilation beams, attempting to turn the meteor into dust midair, but to no avail. It was as if the meteor was indestructible while at the same time having some kind of anti-lock on ability, causing the majority of the beams to miss.

Looking down from above, the blocks of strange black marks caused by the annihilation beams could clearly be seen.

Woo!

At the same time, an air strike alarm rang throughout the city that the meteor was falling toward. Countless entrances of underground shelters appeared on the city surface. Most of the citizens quickly hid in the underground shelters nearby. Very soon, the streets became empty.

They activated a gigantic protective shield, which shrouded the entire city, in an attempt to stop the impact of the meteor head-on. Thousands of antiaircraft cannons extended from below the ground of the edges of the city and fired simultaneously at the meteor in the sky.

Outside the city's protective shield, the Calamity Grade Star Pupil Holy Race Super protecting the city floated in midair.

The black-red meteor covered in burning flames enlarged quickly in his blue eyes.

"The flames are too thick. I can't see the exact shape of this meteor. It's almost reached the ground. I have to stop it now!"

The protector was a Calamity Grade Psychic. He looked up at the accelerating meteor and released all his psychic energy, hoping to stop the meteor or at least alter its course.

However, to his absolute shock, he realized that his psychic energy disappeared as soon as it touched the meteor. He could not do anything to it at all.

"What the hell is this thin…"

The next moment, the speed of the meteor suddenly increased again as it strongly penetrated the protective shield and landing right in the city.

Bang!

A several-hundred-meter-wide crater appeared on the ground. The tornado-like flames quickly dissipated, showing the true identity of this 'meteor'. It was a completely black human-shaped being, like a cluster of fog, emitting black smoke from all over its body. It had no face, only a vortex on its head with a red dot of light in the middle, as if that was its core.

It was an EsGod doppelganger!

The observation satellite of Planet Avitan recorded this and broadcasted it live to the other cities on the planet. The EsGod doppelganger was being watched by more than ten billion people.

The garrison on Planet Avitan had already noticed this. The protector of the city and the guards were trying to surround the EsGod doppelganger. The fleet stationed there started moving as well. Spaceships quickly gathered in the area, and more than half of the military forces on the entire planet were hurrying toward this city.

However, the next moment, what the EsGod doppelganger did terrified the entire planet.

As he opened his arms wide, his energy level increased at an extremely high speed. Horrifying energy gathered like a supernova that was about to explode!

Hum!

The next instant, the blinding light made all the people of Planet Avitan watching the broadcast close their eyes. Then, the exploding radiation forcefully cut off the broadcast.

However, even without the broadcast, everyone on the Planet Avitan felt it.

The ground beneath their feet trembled!

With the EsGod doppelganger as the center, a black and red energy sphere quickly expanded into an enormous size, devouring the entire city. It could even be seen from outer space.

The energy sphere expanded over the entire city, seemingly having reached its limit.

This time, the energy sphere suddenly split into two layers of energy. The outer layer became weaker, and its color became lighter, still maintaining its original size. The inner layer quickly constricted.

When the inner layer was half of the size of the outer layer, the entire energy sphere seemed to lose its balance. Be it the inner or the outer layer, they both exploded violently, turning into a radioactive impact wave, sweeping across everything in its path!

Boom!

Great rifts were created right in this city. Be it the city protector, the ground troops, or the citizens in the underground shelters, they all turned into ash in the explosion.

It was like doomsday!

When the aftershock of the explosion finally ended, this main city was wiped off the surface of the planet, erased of its existence.

All the tall buildings disappeared, only the enormous crater and great rifts were left.

Not a single soul survived.

The EsGod doppelganger slowly flew up from the bottom of the enormous crater, out of the dust that covered the sky, and exposed himself in the satellite image.

He paused for a short moment in midair before suddenly flying in another direction—toward another city.

As the satellite broadcast recovered, everyone on Planet Avitan saw this, and everyone seemed to have forgotten how to breath.

Endless fear grasped everyone's heart.

A few minutes after the 'gigantic explosion', every galactic news channel of the Star Pupil Holy Race reported the news, broadcasting what was happening on Planet Avitan to the entire civilization.

…

At the same time, a fleet with Psyker's ship in the middle took off from the Star Pupil Holy Race mother planet and headed to help Planet Avitan.

Three 'Light Fox' spaceships in stealth mode slowly parked in an area not far from the Star Pupil Holy Race mother planet.

"Psyker's made his move. The first step is a success!"

Colin smiled ferociously and clenched his fists in excitement.

Psyker guarded his mother planet all the time, and the Evolution Cube was on his mother planet. They would only have a chance to steal the Evolution Cube if they could lure Psyker away.

Psyker's weakness was how important his race was to him. All they had to do was place an EsGod doppelganger with Beyond Grade A strength on an important colonial planet and let the EsGod doppelganger massacre the Star Pupil Holy Race people. Psyker would undoubtedly leave his mother planet to provide aid.

Unless Psyker chose not to care about the lives of his people on that planet, he did not have a choice.

For this first doppelganger, EsGod had gifted it Esper abilities with very strong destructive powers.

EsGod could create many doppelgangers but not infinite. Although he possessed countless Esper abilities, his doppelgangers could not use all of them. Only after his original body gifted Esper abilities to his doppelgangers would the doppelgangers be able to use those abilities. His original body would not be able to use the Esper abilities that were given to the doppelgangers until the doppelgangers were dead or if he actively made them disappear.

For example, if he gave ten Esper abilities to his doppelgangers, he would then not be able to use those ten Esper abilities, nor would he be able to give those ten Esper abilities to another doppelganger.

Therefore, EsGod kept collecting Esper abilities, even duplicates. Fusing the Super High Risk Esper Ability List was not the only reason.

"Once Psyker arrives at Planet Avitan, it'll be the time for us to move." Orozen smiled.

Colin nodded, looked at the second EsGod doppelganger beside him, and said, "Your Excellency EsGod, please wait awhile. We will move when the time is right."

"Hmm." The second EsGod doppelganger nodded.

This doppelganger was controlled by the original. Colin and the others were communicating directly with EsGod, who was far away in the Central Galaxy.

This second doppelganger was gifted stealth, teleportation, anti-detection, and various Esper abilities related to espionage.

He had been hiding this team as well as blocking Psyker's large area Psychic senses with his Esper abilities. This was why they could hide right under Psyker's nose and remain undetected near his mother planet.

The main force of stealing the Evolution Cube was also this second EsGod doppelganger—he was the only one that could send Colin and the others to where the Evolution Cube was stored unnoticed.

As for the third doppelganger, he had hidden on Planet Avitan long ago. His plan was to work together with the first doppelganger to stall Psyker.

The third doppelganger had mostly control-type Esper abilities.

Although his doppelgangers all had Beyond Grade A level strength, they were still just doppelgangers, and they would not be able to match Psyker. One doppelganger would not be able to last long; only two doppelgangers working together would be able to stall Psyker long enough to keep him from his mother planet.

As for why EsGod was confident in stealing the Evolution Cube, it was because he had the only detailed information about the Evolution Cube.

The Evolution Cube was no small item.

Without the instruction manual, no one knew how to carry the Evolution Cube around!

Chapter 749: It Will Not Be So Easy!

When the reinforcements led by Psyker arrived on Planet Avitan, the first EsGod doppelganger had already destroyed more than twenty cities, causing heavy casualties, and was still remolding the surface of Planet Avitan.

The fleet stopped in the orbit of Planet Avitan. Psyker flew out of his spaceship and floated at the front of the fleet. He looked down at the planet surface filled with wreckages, and an immense amount of rage appeared in his eyes.

Normally, those of the Star Pupil Holy Race had four arms, three eyes, and smooth azure skin. Their organs were also different from the human race. They had two brains and five hearts, and they had no totally lethal weaknesses. Under the influence of the Evolution Cube, their genes were outstanding. Their bone structure, muscles, and blood vessels were all enhanced. Although they were not at the level of rare Universe Species yet, even the normal members of the Star Pupil Holy Race could survive in space with just their body.

Psyker's appearance, however, was very different from his people. He had awoken the ancestor genes in his body, so he looked more ferocious. He had seven eyes on his face, among which six formed a diamond shape surrounding his main eye. His eye was like a black gem, flickering with infinite stars as if it had a galaxy in it.

He had long, white hair, but it was not actually his hair but countless tentacles as thin as hairs that could sense things. A pair of straight, snow-white horns with jade texture extended from his forehead. His shoulders, chest, wrist, knees, back, and several other places were covered by a naturally grown white exoskeleton, like he was wearing skeleton armor. His azure skin was filled with dark purple patterns. Three pairs of pipeline-looking bone limbs grew from his back, looking like the skeleton of wings when they were opened.

Of course, as the leader of a civilization, Psyker was not naked. He wore a gorgeous, tailored robe.

The next moment, Psyker dived right toward the planet's surface. The first EsGod doppelganger noticed and stopped on a wasteland. He then looked up and looked at Psyker as he landed in front of him.

"EsGod, I know you can hear me. You threw your doppelganger to my territory. Do you want to be my enemy?" Psyker demanded in a cold tone.

He had once travelled to other Star Fields and had knowledge of all the Beyond Grade As in the Galaxy, so he had recognized this as EsGod's doppelganger long ago.

The red dot on the doppelganger's face flickered as EsGod took control of him. Through the doppelganger, EsGod smiled and said, "You know why I've come."

"You think that as long as you lure me out, you will definitely be able to snatch away my treasure?" Psyker sneered and instantly pointed out EsGod's intentions.

He was the leader of a civilization, so he was clearly not stupid. For a notorious Beyond Grade A brute of the Central Galaxy to suddenly appear in the Shattered Star Ring and cause destruction in his territory, it was not because EsGod just wanted to have fun. His Evolution Cube was desired by tons of people. As soon as Psyker saw the news on the mother planet, he had known what EsGod's goal was—it could only be the Evolution Cube.

However, even though he clearly knew that leaving his mother planet would mean he was completely following EsGod's plan, he had no other choices. No one would be able to stop the EsGod doppelganger from destroying Planet Avitan if he did not come.

"No matter how strong someone is, as long as he cares for something, he will forever have weaknesses." The EsGod doppelganger smiled faintly.

"What's the point of being strong if one has no goal to stand by?"

Psyker's seven eyes narrowed simultaneously. An enormous amount of psychic energy shot up the sky. His voice suddenly became solemn and holy, as if it filled the entire sky.

"I indeed have no way to ignore your trap, but as long as I kill you quickly, luring me away will be meaningless!"

Boom!

As soon as his sentence ended, EsGod doppelganger No.1 punched forward with both fists. A maroon energy wave ejected from his fists. The ground cracked open, and the already heavily damaged lands started to vibrate violently, gradually shattering.

Esper Ability—Destructive Dark Energy!

Psyker completely ignored the approaching tsunami-like energy wave. A light shot out from his seven eyes at the same time. Invisible psychic energy turned into countless needles and shot right toward the energy wave.

Boom!

Like fireworks, the energy wave exploded. Though colorful and dazzling, it was extremely dangerous. The energy emitted dug out one rift after another from the ground. Everywhere they passed, even the mud turned to ash.

Psh!

The psychic energy penetrated the explosion and landed on the EsGod doppelganger. His body violently exploded and turned into a cluster of black fog in an instant. In the black fog, a red dot of light flickered—this was the core of the EsGod doppelganger.

The next moment, all the black fog condensed around the red dot and turned back into the doppelganger but thinner.

Psyker's psychic energy happened to be able to deal the most damage to the core of the EsGod doppelganger. Even the EsGod doppelganger would not be able to endure attacks from Beyond Grade As with ease, not to mention the fact that the EsGod doppelganger had already used quite a lot of its energy.

Bang bang bang!

The battle between Beyond Grade As shattered the sky and the earth, mainly because the EsGod doppelganger did not care about the damage caused at all and released his energy without holding back.

On the other side, Psyker's ability would not cause too much impact. It looked like the EsGod doppelganger's attacks were much more horrifying, but in reality, he was no match for Psyker.

After all, he was just a doppelganger. There was no way he would be able to beat a true Beyond Grade A Super in his full form.

Bang!

For the next few minutes, they fought intensely. The EsGod doppelganger was turned into a cluster of black fog time after time and barely reformed his body afterward. The red dot of light flickered constantly as if it would disappear at any moment.

As Psyker was about to maintain his momentum and completely destroy this doppelganger, he suddenly sensed a new Beyond Grade A energy source, and he instantly looked up at the sky.

The other EsGod doppelganger that had been hiding for a very long time on Planet Avitan finally appeared. He was now attacking the fleet in the orbit of the planet.

"You're right, I won't be able to stop you with just one of my doppelgangers," EsGod said through the doppelganger, "but if it's two of them, stalling you for a short period won't be a problem. After I destroy your fleet and your spaceship, you won't be able to rush back to your mother planet."

"You talk too much!" Psyker's eyes became firm. He did not want to waste time by speaking and immediately overwhelmed the first EsGod doppelganger with his psychic energy.

Psyker did not panic. He was not worried about the Evolution Cube being stolen at all. He felt that EsGod only knew that the Evolution Cube was a Universal Treasure but most likely had no idea what the Evolution Cube really was.

The Evolution Cube was very strange, and it was enormous. He was not able to carry it along even after studying it for so long. Unless it was directly snatched away from him, the possibility of it being stolen was next to nothing. This was also why he was confident enough to leave his mother planet and go there.

Of course, Psyker did not know about EsGod's true trump card.

…

On the Star Pupil Holy Race Mother Planet, while Psyker was being stalled by two doppelgangers, the remaining EsGod doppelganger acted. Using its teleportation Esper ability, it teleported Colin, Orozen, and the others to where the Evolution Cube was stored.

An extremely strong, blinding light!

When they finally adapted to the blinding light around them, they finally looked around.

This was a strange area. They were shrouded by a light green protective shield released by the EsGod doppelganger, and everywhere outside of it was filled with a hot, viscous liquid.

"What is this place?" Orozen wondered.

"The outer core of the Star Pupil Holy Race Mother Planet," the EsGod doppelganger said with a calm tone.

Psyker had hidden the Evolution Cube in the inner core of his mother planet and covered it with his psychic barrier, blocking the majority of detection abilities. If not because the Evolutionary Civilization recorded the method to locate the Evolution Cube, the EsGod doppelganger would not have been able to directly teleport there.

After confirming the location, the EsGod doppelganger used his psychic Esper ability to melt the barrier left by Psyker.

The next moment, a gigantic metallic object appeared before everyone's eyes out of nowhere.

They did not know how huge this object was. All they knew was that they could only see one side of the Evolution Cube, and they could not even see the end of it.

"This is way too huge." Colin's pupils constricted.

Curious, Orozen reached out and touched the Evolution Cube, but his hand entered the Evolution Cube unobstructed, as if the Evolution Cube was just a projection with no physical form.

The physical state of the Evolution Cube was very strange. It was between material and energy. It could not be touched by usual means.

"The information says as long as someone's entire body enters the Evolution Cube, they will evolve inside. That's the simplest way to use it." Orozen was tempted.

Colin was a little tempted, but he still remembered the mission. "Stop wasting time. Quickly contain it with the device."

One of the people quickly took out a silver, palm-sized cube and passed it to Colin.

This was a device that EsGod had built following the information left behind by the Evolutionary Civilization. Like a container to store water, its only use was to carry the enormous Evolution Cube and make it portable.

This was special technology possessed by the Evolutionary Civilization that had been lost for a long time. EsGod, who possessed information of this civilization, was the only one that could build this device!

Without this device, stealing the Evolution Cube would be an almost impossible mission.

Colin raised up the silver cube and activated it.

Ding!

The silver cube suddenly emitted a gentle light.

The enormous Evolution Cube seemed to have sensed something. It suddenly shook, and the next moment, a black beam suddenly shot out from the side that was facing them, like it was a pipe.

The Evolution Cube started to turn itself into pure energy. Through this pipe, it slowly 'squeezed' itself into the silver cube, as if it had finally found a home.

The Evolution Cube in the outside world started to shrink. It was as if the silver cube was slowly drinking the Evolution Cube from a straw.

Seeing that the device worked, Colin felt relieved. "The process should take a few minutes. We have more than enough time."

As soon as his sentence ended, a ton of pale white light clusters appeared in their peripheral vision and quickly headed toward them. If not because they were all Supers, they would not have even noticed these inconspicuous light clusters among all this blinding light.

"What are those?" Colin's expression changed drastically, and he was instantly alarmed.

"As expected," the EsGod doppelganger said, "Psyker has a backup plan. These clusters are all his psychic energy. Every one of them is equivalent to one Beyond Grade A psychic attack. This is to protect the Evolution Cube and will attack all intruders. You guys focus on the Evolution Cube; I will stop these things!"

Every one of these psychic energy clusters had strength equal to the one-time psychic weapon that had been used on Han Xiao. At this moment, more and more energy clusters appeared continuously and swamped toward them.

The EsGod doppelganger opened an invisible psychic shield that shrouded everyone.

Boom boom boom!

The psychic energy clusters landed on the shield one after another like pouring rain landing on a lake, causing countless ripples on the surface of the psychic shield.

The EsGod doppelganger's red dot core dimmed at a visible rate. His energy was being consumed extremely quickly while enduring so many Beyond Grade A psychic attacks.

"Quickly… quickly…"

Everyone was anxious as they stared at the silver cube slowly absorbing the Evolution Cube.

They knew that once the EsGod doppelganger was destroyed, they would certainly die.

Seconds felt like years while they waited. Fortunately, although the Evolution Cube's physical state was weird. It was still a whole object. When the silver cube absorbed a large enough portion of the Evolution Cube, it started absorbing the rest at a much quicker rate.

Finally, the last bit of the Evolution Cube turned into energy and entered the silver cube. The absorption was complete, and the cube turned from silver to black.

This was the Evolution Cube in its complete form!

"It's done!" Colin hastily shouted.

"Go!" The EsGod doppelganger could not hold on anymore. Using the last bits of his energy, he sent everyone else back to the spaceship and immediately cut off the teleportation gate.

The next moment, this doppelganger could no longer maintain the shield and was devoured by the energy clusters, disappearing instantly.

Nonetheless, he had completed his mission of protecting his subordinates till they stole the Evolution Cube.

Doppelgangers had limited energy. Only those subordinates of his could cross the desolate universe belt and take the item back to the Fallen Ark. EsGod's original did not dare leave the Central Galaxy casually. The three Universal Civilizations had their eyes on him at all times. If his original made a move, he would not have been able to hide this mission, and things would have been much more difficult.

…

With a flash before their eyes, Colin and the others were teleported back to the spaceships. Before they could speak, their attention was attracted by the loud alarm inside the spaceship.

"Sh*t, our spaceships have been discovered. The Star Pupil Holy Race has sent a fleet to attack us!"

The expression on their faces became worse instantly.

Three 'Light Fox' spaceships were surrounded by a large number of Star Pupil Holy Race battleships. Their shields were swamped with attacks.

When they were stealing the Evolution Cube, Psyker had sensed it. He had quickly ordered the military stationed on his mother planet to do a thorough search of the universe space around. When the EsGod doppelganger was eliminated, the three spaceships lost their stealth barrier and were finally discovered by the Star Pupil Holy Race. They were instantly besieged by the fleet.

"Quickly, leave!"

Colin had no time to observe the Evolution Cube and quickly piloted the spaceship to dodge the attacks.

The three spaceships parted ways, and one spaceship was soon destroyed.

Relying on the spaceships' powerful engines, the two remaining spaceships entered high-speed hyperdrive and escaped. The armor of the spaceships was covered in damages.

Colin gasped for air. When they entered hyperdrive, his tense body finally relaxed.

"We escaped. With our speed, the enemies won't be able to catch up," Colin said with a low voice. "Activate spaceship diagnostics, calculate damages."

The artificial intelligence of the spaceship replied with stutter, "Tsss… self-diagnosing… Ship body damage at sixty-three percent. Shield generator close to broken. Energy furnace damaged moderately. Power output decreased by forty-two percent… Tsss… Thruster damage at thirty-eight percent. Engines No.4 and No.6 are close to broken. Self-repair device malfunctioning… Immediate repair of the spaceship is suggested. With the current state of the spaceship, it can't stay in hyperdrive much longer."

Orozen grinned and said, "Stealing something from a Beyond Grade A was so exciting."

"No matter what, we have what we came for." Colin glanced at the Evolution Cube that was now palm sized. "The spaceship can't travel across Star Fields in its current state. We just have to find a safe place to repair the spaceship, and we will be able to return."

"Hmm, I know a planet that can repair spaceships and is not controlled by any civilization," Orozen said. "It's very safe and is located at the edge of the Shattered Star Ring. We just have to fix our spaceship there, then we can leave this Star Field. I escaped from the Shattered Star Ring from there sixty years ago."

Hearing the name of that planet, Colin checked the star map and nodded.

"Okay. It's very far from the Star Pupil Holy Race. We can use our speed to earn enough buffer time for us to repair the spaceships."

They would only dare travel across Star Fields after they fixed their spaceships. Otherwise, if the spaceships malfunctioned in the middle of a desolate universe belt, they could be stuck there forever.

The 'Light Fox' spaceships immediately changed direction, turned into a stream of light, and disappeared.

…

On Planet Avitan, the last EsGod doppelganger was destroyed, turning into a cluster of black fog and dissipated.

Psyker patted away the dust on his clothes and looked up at the sky with a grave expression.

"The Evolution Cube has really been stolen. I didn't expect EsGod to have the detailed information on the Evolution Cube. This was a miscalculation…"

Three EsGod doppelgangers were equivalent to three Beyond Grade As. They were working together while he was alone, so EsGod succeeding was not completely illogical. Psyker felt resigned.

This was also why EsGod was very difficult to deal with.

However, Psyker was still calm and did not panic. He narrowed his eyes and murmured, "You did succeed, but don't ever think you'll take the Evolution Cube away from me this easily."

Although Psyker did not have the instruction manual of the Evolution Cube, after having the Evolution Cube for so long, he had gained some knowledge of it. Like how Austin owned the Palace of Hidden Spells, after Psyker had the Evolution Cube in his hands for so many years, he had almost made the Evolution Cube his own treasure.

He had built a spiritual connection with the Evolution Cube. Even if the Evolution Cube was not beside him, he could still remotely use the Evolution Cube to improve his psychic abilities.

At the same time, he had left a mark on the Evolution Cube. No matter where it was, he could sense the location of the Evolution Cube.

He could sense the coordinates of the Evolution Cube moving extremely quickly, marking where Colin and the rest were.

Fleeing right after you stole from me?

It won't be so easy!

Psyker pressed a finger on his forehead and communicated with his subordinates through his psychic abilities.

"Prepare the fastest spaceship for me. I'm going after those thieves!"

Chapter 750: Unexpected Invitation

Planet Macipher, the Cornerstone Summit Corporation.

Han Xiao had been working here for more than twenty days. His name had already spread widely among the Senior Engineers. The entire corporation knew that a highly skilled Mechanic had joined them and that he had completed more than ten times the workload of a normal Senior Engineer in less than a month.

As the boss behind them had already spoken, the upper echelons of the corporation did not worry about the confidentiality of the blueprint anymore and daringly used Barne. They gave him extra quotas to hit, which led to Han Xiao getting more and more parts of the Eternal Light blueprint.

The [Engineer] mission was already completed, and he had obtained the [Proficient Technician] talent. Its effect was a slight increase in the attributes of the machinery he built of eight to fourteen percent, twenty-two percent quicker building speed, and six percent reduced cost. This scaled well given how much machinery he would be building, so it was quite a good talent.

As Han Xiao obtained the talent, he had only had one goal left in the Cornerstone Summit Corporation—to steal... no, learn the blueprint of Eternal Light.

Due to how many responsibilities were given to him, Han Xiao learned quite a lot of the blueprints. As for the blueprints given to the other Senior Engineers, he used Virtual Technology to hack into the artificial intelligence assistants of those Grade B Mechanics and monitored them in various ways. When the Senior Engineers looked at their blueprints, Phillip would then capture the image and duplicate the blueprint.

As for some blueprints that he was unable to see with this method, Han Xiao just visited those Senior Engineers with various excuses. All he had to do was look at the blueprint for a short while, and he would be able to obtain the blueprint through the interface.

Sadly, after a past Race Evolution, he had lost the Observer's Mark ability, otherwise secretly learning the blueprint would be much easier.

In more than half a month, Han Xiao was able to obtain the majority of the Eternal Light's blueprint. All that was left were the core blueprints. These were all tightly stored by the core engineers of the corporation, and Han Xiao had no chance to see them. He had been pondering how to obtain these blueprints for quite some time.

During this time, as players were learning more Knowledges from the faction store, his Experience increased once again.

Inside the workshop, Han Xiao was doing his job while looking at the Experience he had on his interface, calculating.

With the current amount of Experience I have, I should be able to reach about level 238 or 239. I'm just one step away from Lv240, which will be filled up in three or four more days...

Han Xiao was secretly excited. Beyond Grade As were on a completely different level to Calamity Grades. They were important people throughout the entire Galaxy, and even Universal Civilizations had to take them seriously.

Once he succeeded, he would get a seat on the highest table of the Star Field, and the Black Star Army would become a real Beyond Grade A organization.

After looking forward to it for a while, Han Xiao looked at the time. It was time for his lunch break. He stopped working, retracted all the building assistants, and planned to go for lunch.

As soon as he walked out of the workshop, Han Xiao noticed that Luke was standing outside the door.

"Barne, I was looking for you."

"What is it? You want to have lunch with me?" Han Xiao stopped and looked at this old gentleman curiously.

Luke smiled and shook his head. "I'd be glad to do so, but this is not why I've come. The real owner of the corporation wants to see you."

The real owner? Han Xiao raised his brows. "Sure, lead the way then."

Luke gestured for Han Xiao to follow him and led him to the core area of the corporation.

After walking for more than ten minutes, the two of them arrived at the top floor of a tall building and entered a wide office.

In the room, a person sat in a chair with the chair's back facing the door. Han Xiao could only see the back of his head.

Luke stepped back and closed the door, leaving Han Xiao and this so-called 'real owner of the corporation' in the room.

This time, this person spoke with his back still facing Han Xiao.

"Barne, this isn't your real name, right?"

Then, this person turned around to face Han Xiao.

Seeing his appearance, Han Xiao was stunned for a moment before understanding.

It was Sardeem. Of course, that made sense. As the owner of Planet Macipher, Sardeem controlled many of its industries. The Cornerstone Summit Corporation belonging to him was not much of a surprise.

In his previous life, the players only knew that a talent would be rewarded if they worked in the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, and any Mechanics could do this mission. However, with the strength of the players at that stage, they did not come into contact with the corporation's core. In the players' eyes, the Cornerstone Summit Corporation was just a small unimportant side mission. Therefore, the players did not know that the owner of this shipyard turned out to be Sardeem. Nonetheless, this was not difficult to guess.

This means that the Eternal Light blueprint belongs to Sardeem... Why did he suddenly call me here? Did he find out who I am?

Han Xiao's mind was racing.

Of course, he was not afraid at all. Although Sardeem was a Grade A+ Mechanic as well, he would be no match for him. However, he just wanted to secretly learn the Eternal Light blueprint. If his identity was exposed, he would have no choice but to snatch it... Still, Han Xiao did not like making enemies.

Seeing that Han Xiao did not speak, Sardeem gave a knowing smile.

"I've been observing you for quite some time. You've actually been hiding your strength. You're not a Grade B+ Mechanic but a Calamity Grade Mechanic, am I right?"

Without waiting for Han Xiao to reply, Sardeem sized Han Xiao up and continued.

"A Calamity Grade willing to work in my company as a normal engineer makes me doubt your true intentions. Through my observations, you seem to be interested in the Eternal Light blueprint, right?"

After hearing what Sardeem said, Han Xiao felt relieved instead.

Whew, luckily, this guy only noticed that I'm Grade A and did not find out my real identity. He just thinks I'm a normal Calamity Grade Mechanic.

Seeing how confident Sardeem looked, Han Xiao could guess that Sardeem was certain that he had the upper hand.

Indeed, Sardeem was Grade A+ and had the entire planet as his base. This was his territory, so normal Calamity Grades were indeed no match for him in this situation.

Figuring out Sardeem's confidence, Han Xiao calmed down. Without correcting Sardeem's misunderstanding, he acted alert as if he really was a normal Calamity Grade.

"What do you want?"

Seeing this, Sardeem smiled with satisfaction. 'Barne' becoming nervous was exactly what he wanted to see.

"I don't know where you got the information about Eternal Light from, nor do I know which organization you belong to. But don't worry, I did not call you here today to hold you accountable. Instead, I'm giving you an invitation."

"Invitation?" Han Xiao raised his brow.

Sardeem stood up, smiled, and said, "Become my subordinate. I can guarantee that this will be the wisest decision you ever make."

"You're recruiting me?" Han Xiao said with a strange tone.

Isn't that too careless? You don't even know my identity.

Is this because you're absolutely confident I won't be a problem for you?

Pal, that's a little arrogant of you. Even someone as outstanding as me is not this arrogant!

"I have a lot of companies and a lot of troops, but I'm short of a capable assistant. You have the ability to be one. Us together will be an amazing combo," Sardeem said in a calm tone.

Han Xiao shook his head with resignation. "I'm not inter..."

This time, Sardeem shook his hand and interrupted Han Xiao. "If you're willing to become my subordinate, not just Eternal Light, I can let you learn all the blueprints I know."

"Hmm, I will have to consider..." Han Xiao immediately changed what he was about to say. As the leader of a faction, of course, he was not going to be a subordinate of a Calamity Grade. However, scamming some blueprints from him seemed to be quite tempting.

After all, whatever Barne does has nothing to do with Black Star... ahem.

Han Xiao suddenly asked, "Are you forcing me? If I don't join you, will you use force on me?"

Sardeem shook his head and laughed.

"Don't worry, I don't like making enemies. If I was hostile toward everyone like you that visited Planet Macipher, I wouldn't have been able to last till now. You can reject me, and I won't chase you away. I won't even force you to reveal your true identity. You can still stay in the Cornerstone Summit Corporation as 'Barne'. I have no need to reject a Grade A Mechanic from working in my company. However, I will always keep an eye on you, and I won't let you take part in any important projects."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "You're quite generous."

"It's very tough for someone petty to achieve great things in life. I've managed Planet Macipher for close to a hundred and thirty years," Sardeem said calmly. "What situation have I not seen before? Hmm?"

Han Xiao contemplated for a while and still shook his head.

As an almost Beyond Grade A faction leader, it would be too shameless for him to become a subordinate of a Calamity Grade just because of a blueprint.

Although he did put on a disguise, if he accidentally exposed his true identity one day, it would be a mark on his history he would not be able to wipe off. It would damage his high reputation in the eyes of the players and would not be beneficial for building a sense of belonging for the faction, as well as the cultivation of leeks. In conclusion, the cons outweighed the pros.

The Eternal Light blueprint was indeed a good item, but it was not something that he had to obtain no matter what.

Also, you think that I won't be able to get the blueprint without joining you?

You're dreaming!

Seeing that Han Xiao had rejected him, Sardeem narrowed his eyes.

"Hehe, I know you have the pride of a Calamity Grade, but I'm worth following. Do you think that normal people would be able to get the flagship blueprint of the Federation of Light?"

Han Xiao was slightly moved.

Indeed, even he could not buy a blueprint as rare as the Eternal Light blueprint. How did Sardeem get it?

Sardeem put his hands behind his back and looked at Han Xiao. "You might think that as a Calamity Grade, you don't have to become a subordinate of another Calamity Grade, so you rejected me... But what if I told you that I'm not just representing myself and there's a Beyond Grade A behind this?"

"Hmm?" Han Xiao noticed something.

Now that he thought about it carefully, there should be some unknown reasons that brought about Planet Macipher's prosperity other than Sardeem's personal strength. He might indeed be a secret officer of a certain Beyond Grade A.

However, there were only four Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring. Who did this guy work for?

Tyrant? Possible, but not likely. After all, Sardeem was not a buffed and muscular dude.

Magus? That did not feel right either. Sardeem was not a mage...

Star Pupil? Not likely given how rarely that guy left his own territory.

Could it be the Dragon Emperor? Laughable.

Seeing that Han Xiao was confused, Sardeem shook his head and smiled.

"You have definitely heard of him before."

Pride appeared on Sardeem's face, together with a sense of superiority.

"Do you know about... the Mechanic Empire?"

Han Xiao was completely shocked and almost wanted to leave right away.

Mechanic Empire Manison?

Don't know, never heard before, bye!

Chapter 751: Arrival

Sardeem being Manison's subordinate was a piece of intelligence that Han Xiao did not expect to obtain. In his previous life, Sardeem had not been considered a known NPC to the players and had no mission to trigger. He did not think that Sardeem was hiding this much.

Manison was an extremely strong guy. As a member of The Ancient Ones, he created his own faction in the Calamity of the Supers version.

Han Xiao was very sensitive to anything related to Manison and did not want to have anything to do with him. This was because of Aroshia.

She was a survivor of an artificial intelligence civilization conquered by Manison, and Risda was still hoping that Han Xiao could avenge them. Han Xiao still had the [Reboot] mission on his interface.

However, he was not willing to mess with this ancient and powerful being. The Mechanic Empire had no conflict of interest with him. It would be too big a loss for Han Xiao to become his enemy for just a normal mission. He actually did not want to do this mission, so he had been delaying it. Risda also knew that this was impossible without the help of a Beyond Grade A Super, so he had waited patiently and did not hurry Han Xiao.

Manison was mainly in the Central Galaxy and the Primeval Star River, but his organization had fangs secretly distributed among many Star Fields. His 'Mechanic Empire' was not just a reference to his Mechanical Army but also signified that the number of Mechanics under his command could form an entire empire.

Manison likes to recruit Mechanics. This is probably also the reason his subordinate in the Shattered Star Ring, Sardeem, is suddenly recruiting me. No wonder this guy is so arrogant.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

However, although he was shocked by Sardeem's background, he quickly calmed down.

No matter what, Manison did not even know that he existed. They had no conflict with each other, so he did not have to fear him.

Manison not knowing of Han Xiao's existence was his biggest advantage. Furthermore, he had surprisingly discovered that Sardeem was secretly under the Mechanic Empire, which was a huge gain.

After purposely acting like he was hesitating for a while, Han Xiao shook his head. "Of course, I've heard of the Mechanic Empire, but I still don't want to join you."

Sardeem's confidence fixed on his face. This time, he was the one that was shocked instead.

He had thought that as long as he mentioned the Mechanic Empire, recruiting this person would be a piece of cake. He did not expect 'Barne' to reject him.

"Don't you know how many resources the Mechanic Empire has and how valuable they are to a Mechanic?" Sardeem said with an incredulous tone.

Manison had been stockpiling technology and blueprints for countless years. Not even mentioning the Cutting-Edge Knowledges, he most likely even had the Ultimate Knowledges for the Mechanic class, as well as all kinds of secret or lost blueprints. He even had tons of spaceships and weapon blueprints of the three Universal Civilizations. These attracted countless Mechanics to join under his command... of course, those Knowledges all had to be exchanged for contribution.

Han Xiao raised his brows.

"I know what you mean, but not all Mechanics want to be Manison's subordinates, right?"

He was indeed tempted by the resources of the Mechanic Empire. However, that did not come for free. He had to do things for the Mechanic Empire over the long term. Unlike joining under Sardeem, whom he had confidence that he could completely beat, joining the Mechanic Empire was different as he certainly could not beat him. This meant that once he joined the Mechanic Empire, his true identity would definitely be exposed, and he would really end up working for him.

Therefore, there was no way that he was going to accept the invitation. This was like a Fortune 500 company trying to hire him, but he would rather start his own company. Although my company is not as big as yours now, I'm the one that gets all the profits!

Sardeem narrowed his eyes, turned around, and sat back in the chair. With an expressionless face, he said, "Then you can leave now."

Seeing that Barne had made up his mind, he did not want to waste any time and energy convincing him.

He was not worried about Han Xiao knowing his identity. After operating Planet Macipher for more than a hundred years, his background was no secret to many people. He dared to tell the truth of his background because he was not afraid of it being exposed. He was legally operating Planet Macipher, so what if people knew that he was part of the Mechanic Empire? His Excellency Manison was not a wanted criminal; having a subordinate in the Shattered Star Ring to build a stronghold did not break any laws.

Han Xiao did not care about Sardeem's dissatisfaction. He shook his head and left the room with a little resignation.

He was not afraid of offending Sardeem, but this meant that Sardeem would definitely monitor him more closely, which would make stealing the Eternal Light blueprints even more difficult.

Fortunately, Sardeem did not discover my true identity. His misjudgment of my strength works to my advantage. I should be able to fool him with some tricks, but if I still can't steal it in the end, I can only use Barne's identity to rob it... Or should I change to another identity?

While thinking about murdering and robbing, Han Xiao slowly walked away.

...

After Han Xiao left, Sardeem was the only one left in the office. He shook his head and was rather disappointed.

Initially, he had thought that recruiting Barne would be simple, but he did not expect this guy to be so stubborn.

Di di di...

At this time, Sardeem's communicator rang.

As he looked at the caller, his expression instantly changed, and he immediately picked up the communicator.

"Greetings, Your Excellency Psyker!"

The person that was contacting him was Psyker!

Psyker's video call appeared on the screen, and he asked, "If I remember correctly, Planet Macipher is your territory, right?"

"Yes, what can I do for you?"

Sardeem's tone was very respectful, completely different from how he talked to Han Xiao.

As the leader of the Star Pupil Holy Race, it was simple for Psyker to contact the owner of a known neutral planet.

Furthermore, he had known Sardeem for a long time. The Arcane Church was behind him, so he had access to a lot of information. Sardeem's true identity was no secret to him at all.

As he was backed by the Arcane Church, although Psyker was in the remote Shattered Star Ring, he was still quite known in the Central Galaxy's Beyond Grade A circle. These powerful individuals all knew that he was a semi-ally of the Arcane Church and was a valuable chip for them.

Although Psyker focused on managing his race and did not like to cause trouble like the Tyrant, in terms of influence in high society, Psyker was the one at the top among the four Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring.

Therefore, Sardeem showed him a lot of respect.

"Hmm, I have something I need you to do," Psyker said slowly. "I need you to pay attention to a 'Light Fox' model spaceship. I will send its appearance to you later. No matter who arrives on your planet in this type of spaceship, pay close attention to them. They're very likely there to repair their spaceship, so find a way to keep them on Planet Macipher."

"Okay, I got it." Without a thought, Sardeem agreed—this was basically a gifted favor.

Although he claimed to be neutral, he knew what kind of people he had to give privileges to.

"You must stall them and not let them escape the Shattered Star Ring," Psyker emphasized.

"Understood." Sardeem nodded.

Psyker then hung up.

As one of the EsGod doppelgangers had used teleportation to move Colin and the others to steal the Evolution Cube, the Star Pupil Holy Race had no visual records of these people and did not know what they looked like. However, due to the battleship fight outside their mothership, they knew the looks of these 'Light Fox' spaceships.

The mark that Psyker had left on the Evolution Cube showed that the Evolution Cube was no longer escaping in hyperdrive and had stopped for the first time. After looking at the star map, Psyker realized that the Evolution Cube had stopped near Planet Macipher.

Since he knew the location of their spaceship, he could guess what those thieves were planning.

Therefore, Psyker came up with a plan and contacted Sardeem to get his help.

While doing so, he had been heading toward Planet Macipher all along. As long as Sardeem could stall them for a few days, he would be able to arrive.

With his power, Colin and the others would not be able to escape.

...

At the same time in the orbit of Planet Macipher, Colin piloted the heavily damaged 'Light Fox' spaceship and slowly approached the port of Planet Macipher.

Due to the superiority of their spaceship's engine, they had maintained high-speed hyperdrive and crossed a small half of the Star Field in close to ten days, leaving their pursuers far behind.

They had finally arrived at this famous neutral planet. Planet Macipher was the place that they had chosen to repair their spaceship.

Chapter 752: Emperor Mechanic!

The Light Fox spaceships flew toward the Planet Macipher port. Inside the cabin, Colin was speaking to his subordinates.

"We will first land in a sub-city. You guys will go and find a local shipyard immediately. Have them transport our spaceships over and repair them as soon as possible. Money isn't an issue... As for the rest of us, we will be finding a relatively hidden spot in the sub-city to rest."

The others replied disorderly.

"Don't worry," Orozen said lazily, "Planet Macipher is a neutral planet. No one will trouble us. The Star Pupil Holy Race doesn't even know the direction we escaped in. There's no one chasing after us, so we're basically safe. We just have to stay one or two days on Planet Macipher and wait for our spaceships to be repaired. Then, we can take the Evolution Cube back."

Speaking of the Evolution Cube, desire appeared in Orozen's eyes as he subconsciously glanced at the tiny black cube hanging on Colin's neck.

Noticing his glance, Colin said, "We will figure out how to use this thing after we leave the Shattered Star Ring. Don't even think about it now."

With such a treasure in hand, everyone was tempted, but no one had any underlying thoughts. They just wanted to experience the Evolution Cube's effects at most.

Although the Evolution Cube was a Universal Treasure, it was not worth betraying EsGod for.

As EsGod had the data of the Evolutionary Civilization, they knew a thing or two about the Evolution Cube as well, so they did not have any unnecessary expectations for it. After all, even with the Star Pupil Holy Race having so many Calamity Grades, Psyker was still the only Beyond Grade A.

However, the fact that using the Evolution Cube would make them stronger was an indisputable truth.

This time, the spaceships entered the port, completed the simple procedures, and descended toward one of the sub-cities on Planet Macipher.

As soon as they left their spaceships, Colin and the rest started moving. They found a relatively unknown shipyard and paid them to repair their spaceships.

The Light Fox spaceships were equipped with top-notch hyperdrive engines. It only took them a few days to travel the distance that would take normal spaceship months. Otherwise, they would not have arrived at Planet Macipher, which was at the edge of the Shattered Star Ring, in just ten days from the Star Pupil Holy Race's territory. They insisted on repairing the spaceships because the speed of the Light Fox spaceships would save them a ton of time while traveling. They definitely would not change their spaceships unless they had absolutely no other choice.

As they had escaped as fast as they could, they did not know for sure if there were any pursuers behind them. However, to them, the super high-speed hyperdrive of the Light Fox spaceship was more than enough to get rid of any pursuers. The Star Pupil Holy Race might not even know where they had gone. Of course, the connection between Psyker and the Evolution Cube was a secret, so they did not know that their location had already been exposed.

As for their identities, they were not worried at all. They had stolen the Evolution Cube while using the teleportation ability of the EsGod doppelganger, so the Star Pupil Holy Race did not know what they looked like.

The only time they were exposed was back in the Tyla Civilization, which was already many months ago and had nothing to do with them stealing the Evolution Cube. No one would link the two incidents together. After all, the Star Pupil Holy Race did not announce that the Evolution Cube had been stolen, not even in the local news on Planet Avitan. The secret war was still at the top of the news.

Therefore, to Colin and the others, arriving at the Planet Macipher meant that they already had one foot out of the Shattered Star Ring. They thought that they were completely safe.

As their spaceships were sent for repair, Colin and the others stayed in a hotel in the sub-city.

What they did not know was, the moment they entered Planet Macipher, they were already noticed.

...

Only half an hour after Psyker's call...

"The Light Fox spaceships have already appeared..."

Sardeem received the information immediately.

The port entry information throughout Planet Macipher was monitored by him. As soon as Colin's spaceships entered, they were discovered. Sardeem monitored Colin and the others closely.

"They went to Sub-City No.2, found a shipyard there to repair their spaceship, and went to a hostel located at..."

The entire planet was under his surveillance. After locking onto the Light Fox spaceships, Sardeem then monitored Colin and the rest.

He did not recognize them, but after his assistant artificial intelligence searched for a while, he found Orozen's bounty from the Tyla Civilization.

"A group of wanted criminals? Why is Psyker after them?" Sardeem could not help but imagine. "Could it be that he wants to use this opportunity to establish a good relationship with the Tyla Civilization? It is indeed possible for Psyker to do something like this, but the fact that he's doing it personally... maybe it's because he wants to increase his influence?"

Given how much information he lacked, of course, he had no idea that the Evolution Cube had been stolen.

Also, Sardeem would definitely not link the small black cube on Colin's neck to the gigantic Evolution Cube.

"Psyker just wants me to stall them. Hmm, if not needed, I don't have to fight them."

Sardeem pondered for a while and decided not to alarm them.

Instead, he issued a new order to his mechanical low enforcement troops and secretly increased the patrol density of the area around Colin and the others. This would allow him to monitor them even more closely.

"Right..."

Sardeem thought of something else. He called the shipyard that had taken the job to repair the Light Fox spaceships and ordered them to delay the process.

Although this shipyard did not belong to him, with his position on Planet Macipher, he had the power to do this.

"That should be enough. Now, I just have to slowly monitor them..."

Sardeem gave a new order to the control center of the floating city to alert him as soon as Colin and the others did anything abnormal. He then put this matter aside.

As the owner of a planet, he was very busy, so there was no way he was going to stare at the monitors all day long.

...

After the unpleasant meeting with Sardeem ended, Han Xiao realized that no one chased him away. He completed the job for the afternoon as usual, but when evening came, he received some bad news.

The Cornerstone Summit Corporation had moved him out of the Eternal Light project and did not let him continue participating in this project. He was no longer needed to build the spaceship parts, and the blueprints in his hands were also taken away.

He had already learned all those blueprints, so taking them away did not matter to him. However, the signal given by Sardeem was very clear—he was not going to let Han Xiao have any chance of catching a glimpse of the Eternal Light blueprint.

Sardeem has started to guard against me. If I continue to stay here, I will only become manual labor and will never participate in important projects.

Han Xiao shook his head.

I've already got the talent, so there's no need to continue staying on Planet Macipher. I can leave as soon as I get the Eternal Light blueprint...

Although Sardeem had raised his guard against him, Han Xiao already had some plans in mind to steal the remaining core blueprints of Eternal Light.

Speaking of which, Sardeem was the one who had given him the idea.

Initially, Han Xiao could not find out where those core blueprints were hidden in the database of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, so he was at a dead end. However, after Sardeem actively told him his true identity, he now had a new goal.

It turned out that Sardeem was the actual owner of the Eternal Light blueprint.

This meant that he definitely had an Eternal Light blueprint in his home, so Han Xiao did not need to do anything to the Cornerstone Summit Corporation.

Sardeem's home was that magnificent floating city base above Planet Macipher.

Han Xiao's target was to hack Sardeem's floating city!

Sardeem doesn't know my true strength. I wonder if he will regret telling me his true identity today... Oh, I almost forgot, he definitely won't because he will never know I have hacked into his floating city.

If he did not work in the Cornerstone Summit Corporation because of a talent, he would not have attracted Sardeem's attention. If he did not attract Sardeem's attention, Sardeem would not have attempted to recruit him. If he was not recruited, he would not have known that Sardeem was the real owner of the Eternal Light blueprint.

It could be said that Sardeem had personally led the way for him.

Han Xiao sneered in his mind.

The floating city was the base of a Grade A+ Armed Branch Mechanic. Compared to the database of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, its artificial intelligence defense was on a completely different level.

However, Han Xiao was a Virtual Mechanic whose level was even higher than Sardeem. As long as he made sufficient preparations, he would be able to hack into the control panel of the floating city without being noticed.

It's best to increase my chances even further...

Han Xiao was now level 221. He would trigger the Class Advancement of [Apostle Mechanic] at level 225. His Virtual Technology would be enhanced once again after the Class Advancement.

He had plenty of Experience in his interface. As nothing urgent had happened before, Han Xiao wanted to hoard enough Experience until he could reach level 240. Now that he needed it, he did not wait any longer.

The night on Planet Macipher was as boisterous as the day. The entertainment venues there were open throughout the night. Spaceships flew between tall buildings, leaving colorful flame trails like rainbows in the night sky.

Due to how rich the nightlife was, no one stopped Han Xiao from leaving the Cornerstone Summit Corporation hostel.

He went to the ground port, returned to the hangar that he had rented, walked into the spaceship, and entered the training room. This was to prevent the impact caused by his Class Advancement from attracting unwanted attention.

After closing the door of the training room, Han Xiao opened the interface and spent Experience leveling up without hesitation.

Very soon, he reached level 225 and received the Class Advancement mission of [Apostle Mechanic].

Han Xiao had spent seven years stockpiling Mission Completion Cards, so of course, he still had some. He immediately completed the Class Advancement mission.

The next moment, his brain trembled.

You have used a [Mission Completion Card]!

You have completed the Class Advancement mission!

You have received a new class [Emperor Mechanic Lv.1].

+300 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +8 END, +12 INT.

You have received 10 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

You have received the talent [Machinery Emperor]!

You have acquired the ability [Emperor Machinery Affinity]!

You have acquired the ability [Emperor's Gift]!

You have acquired the ability [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel (Unactivated)]!

You have acquired the ability [Secondary Dimension Army (Unactivated)]!

You have acquired the ability [Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power (Unactivated)]!

You have acquired the ability [King's Mentor (Unactivated)]!

The effect of all your Virtual Technology related abilities and talents has increased by 35%

Chapter 753: Striking First

[Emperor Mechanic] was the next stage of [Apostle Mechanic], which had a maximum level of 35. As the name suggested, an Emperor Mechanic could rule countless mechanical soldiers. Its abilities and talents provided huge bonuses to the Army Style while also having the ability to gather much more power into the Mechanic themself.

The introduction of the [Machinery Emperor] talent was 'Machinery obeys you like your people.' Its effect was a 150% increase in Virtual Intrusion efficiency and a 200% increase in Machinery Affinity, as well as an increase of one level to all machinery related abilities. This bonus could exceed the maximum level.

This talent also had another core effect. Just like the [Apostle Mechanic]'s talent, [Mechanical Force Ascension—Apostle Body], [Machinery Emperor] also caused his Mechanical Force attribute to ascend once again, acquiring the ability to gift machinery stronger powers. This was the prerequisite of many of the Emperor Mechanic's abilities.

Of course, the new Machinery Affinity ability, [Emperor Machinery Affinity] was stronger than [Apostle Machinery Affinity], which gave 150% Machinery Affinity at the max level.

[Emperor's Gift] was one of the core abilities. Its effect was to use Mechanical Force to enhance a single machine permanently, giving it extremely powerful additional attributes. It could only be used three times on the same target and had a very long cooldown. The extent of the enhancement depended on Han Xiao's own attributes, and the target had a random chance of receiving an extra special ability.

To put it simply, this ability could enhance common mobs into elites or even mini-bosses!

Mechanics had the ability to enhance machinery from the start, but this ability only started to ascend to another level at this stage.

As for the other 'Unactivated' abilities, they could only be used once the corresponding Cutting-Edge Knowledges or even Ultimate Knowledges were learned, which Han Xiao had yet to do.

[Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel] required a few Cutting-Edge Knowledges including [Advanced Space Application]. It was an enhanced method of transmitting Mechanical Force through the Void.

Due to his race, Han Xiao could transmit Mechanical Force across long distances, but this was only achievable because he was a Void Race. [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel], however, was technology that could be used widely, not just on himself and not just on Mechanical Force, but any kind of energy. It was a much more advanced method of transmitting energy over long distances. This was also the technology that Manison used to make an AI civilization into his 'Indestructible Mechanic Empire'.

[Secondary Dimension Army] could hide his army in a secondary dimension. He would maintain the connection to this secondary dimension and could then open it anytime to summon the army. This was a more advanced portable technology than the compressed orbs.

[Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power] was an ability that could gather great forces onto himself, like an advanced version of Machinery Apostilization.

At the same time, once the mechanical army receiving Mechanical Force bonuses reached a certain size, they would provide attribute bonuses to himself through the Mechanical Force link. This bonus depended on the size of the army.

The larger his army was, the more bonuses [Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power] would provide, which meant that the Army Style benefitted from this the most.

Once he activated this ability and provided bonuses to the mechanical army through his Mechanical Force, he would receive a huge amount of bonuses. Of course, the energy consumption of this ability was enormous. Normal Mechanics would not be able to activate [Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power] for a long time if they did not have the ability to recover energy quickly.

[King's Mentor] and [Emperor's Gift] were similar; they were both abilities to enhance machinery. The difference was, [King's Mentor] was an AOE ability. Its effect was also rather special. It could store the special Mechanical Force enhanced by [Machinery Emperor] in machinery over long periods of time. With the machinery's energy furnace, that Mechanical Force would be kept within the machinery's body, giving the machinery self-growth capabilities.

This meant that the machinery would level up on their own without Han Xiao improving them manually.

As long as the enhanced mechanical soldiers were not destroyed in battle, their attributes would slowly increase, and they would turn into elites. Blue grade mechanical soldiers might slowly become purple grade; level 100 mechanical soldiers might slowly acquire the attributes on par with level 120 mechanical soldiers.

This was like turning the mechanical soldiers into real living soldiers that would become experienced war veteran as long as they survived.

The ability introduction was 'A king is one who has survived hundreds of battles.'

These abilities had already showcased the specialty of [Emperor Mechanic]—a ruler of countless mechanical soldiers that were treated as living soldiers. This was where the machinery started to ascend into becoming mechanical lives.

The upgraded Mechanical Force could turn into a special form of energy that could become the machinery's own energy source, like the 'energy' of the mechanical lives.

[Apostle Mechanic] was the watershed of the late stages of the Mechanic class. The later the stages, the closer the Mechanic's abilities would resemble acts of God. The word 'emperor' was the perfect word to describe the Mechanic's ability at this stage—the absolute ruler of machinery.

...

In the training room, Han Xiao's eyes were overflowing with electric sparks as he endured the pain brought by the changes of his Class Advancement.

This was not a Race Evolution, so Han Xiao's body did not change, but the energy in his body became violent as if his Mechanical Force was boiling. At a microscopic level, it was as if every one of his cells turned into a supernova, absorbing Mechanical Force continuously then compressing themselves time after time.

Through this process, his Mechanical Force slowly changed and ascended.

Enormous Mechanical Force surged within his body. Han Xiao could almost hear the tide.

After a short while, it was as if the cells in his body finally became exhausted, and the energy in his body started to calm.

Whoosh!

Han Xiao took a deep breath. His senses felt refreshed once again.

Energy was fundamental to Supers. It was not just the fuel of great power—it was also the catalyst of the evolution of Super-Genes. This Class Advancement caused his Mechanical Force to evolve to another level. Although his race was still the same, Han Xiao could feel his genes become stronger.

At the later stages, every Class Advancement required even more levels than the twenty level Promotion requirement, along with the increased benefits of the Class Advancement.

This Class Advancement improved his Mechanic abilities tremendously. Although his attributes did not change much, all these new abilities and talents were extremely powerful.

While browsing the new abilities, Han Xiao was quite joyous.

"Four unactivated abilities that need the corresponding Knowledges to activate. Tsk, I will only be able to test their effects after activating them..." Han Xiao pondered. "As of now, only [Machinery Emperor], [Emperor Machinery Affinity], and [Emperor's Gift] can be used. Also, the abilities and talents related to Virtual Technology are enhanced by thirty-five percent, so hacking into Sardeem's floating city is more likely to be successful."

After contemplating for a while, Han Xiao decided not to level up any of his abilities. Level 240 was right around the corner, so he did not want to spend his experience anywhere else.

He then spent the rest of his Experience in leveling up to see how much more he needed exactly to reach level 240.

The remaining Experience only filled up three-quarters of his Experience gauge and was not enough to level up.

He should be just two levels away from Beyond Grade A.

"Hmm, about the same as my estimates. In just a few days, the Experience provided by the players should be able to fill this gap." Han Xiao nodded.

He would have more than enough time to study his new abilities in the future, but he had another goal that night. He immediately connected himself to the quantum network.

His vision turned dark. The next moment, the nodes in the quantum network lit up one after another like fireworks. The size and brightness of these nodes varied. Beams created by information transmission connected those nodes with one another, forming a network illustrating the shape of the city.

Han Xiao looked up. Above the main city, the quantum network nodes of the floating city were as bright as stars, shrouded in countless silk shaped defense measures like a crystal covered in runes.

With one thought, Han Xiao headed directly to the floating city's quantum network nodes. The floating city node expanded in his vision as he entered right into this node.

A thick wall formed by data streams entered his eyes, and many data dots patrolled around like an army.

This was the most outside layer of the floating city's control center firewall.

"Phillip, get him."

Of course, Sardeem understood the threat of Virtual Mechanics. As a Grade A+ Mechanic, he had deployed many defense measures for his base. The virtual defense of the floating city's control center was many levels above that of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation. Usual Calamity Grade Virtual Mechanics would not have been able to penetrate it at all.

However, Han Xiao's Virtual Technology had just been enhanced after his Class Advancement, so it was rather easy for him to deal with the floating city's virtual defense.

After all, Armed Branch Mechanics were not strong in this field. Furthermore, Han Xiao's raw strength was already above Sardeem to quite an extent.

Hacking without living a trace and without being noticed was harder than directly demolishing the opponent's artificial intelligence. Even Han Xiao did not dare act too hastily. He worked together with Phillip and slowly hacked through the defenses of the floating city's control panel to avoid triggering the alarm.

While his base was quietly being violated by Han Xiao and Phillip, Sardeem had no idea that this was happening.

After spending quite some time, Han Xiao finally went around the defense of the floating city's control center and entered the control center, gaining temporary access.

"Got it." Han Xiao was content. "Phillip, search his database for the Eternal Light blueprint."

"Searching, hum... Found it, hum!" Phillip's tone was very cheerful.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he could not hold back his laughter any longer. "As expected, this guy did not put the blueprint in the database of any of his businesses but his own base."

Sardeem most likely exchanged this blueprint from the Mechanic Empire with contributions. Mechanic Empire's home was so far from the Shattered Star Ring, so there was no way the physical copy of the blueprint would be transported there. Hence, the initial way he received the blueprint was definitely through data transmission. It was highly likely that Sardeem still had the complete blueprint stored in the data form.

As the defense of the floating city was on a completely different level compared to the Cornerstone Summit Corporation, most Virtual Mechanics were not able to hack it. That was why Sardeem felt safer storing it in the database of his base.

Because of that, Han Xiao did not have to steal the physical copy of the blueprint; he just had to copy the floating city's database which was much easier.

Han Xiao chuckled. "Phillip, copy all the blueprints in his database."

Since the complete blueprint of Eternal Light was in the database, all the blueprints that Sardeem had obtained from the Mechanic Empire were likely in it as well.

Since he had gone through so much trouble to hack into it, Han Xiao did not mind taking everything that Sardeem had in his storage.

While doing so, Han Xiao took a look at what Sardeem was doing, which made him feel rather strange.

Sardeem happened to be browsing his database as well. As the alarm had not been triggered, even though they were using the database at the same time, he did not notice Han Xiao. He had no idea that Han Xiao had entered his control center and that his home was basically being robbed right now.

As Phillip was copying the blueprints, he had nothing else to do, so he opened the command log of the control center to see what Sardeem had been doing lately.

The log recorded all of Sardeem's commands. Han Xiao was initially just scanning through casually, but when he noticed the history of Sardeem manually operating the control center today, his eyes stopped on that line of the log.

"Deploying a large number of mechanical law reinforcement troops to Sub-City No.2 to monitor a group of people? Interesting, isn't Sardeem neutral? Why is he suddenly surveilling people? It must be at least a Calamity Grade, like Barne, to attract his attention... Hmm, I got it, this guy is probably going to recruit someone else under the Mechanic Empire's name once again. If it really is a Calamity Grade, I might be able to snatch a talent away from him before leaving Planet Macipher."

Han Xiao could not help but giggle. He casually brought up the image of the target of the surveillance. When he saw the image clearly, his smile froze on his face.

It was Colin and his gang in the image. Han Xiao has never seen these people before, but he recognized one of them.

Orozen!

A wanted criminal of the Tyla Civilization, the killer of Harrofal, and a possible subordinate of EsGod!

This man was the mission target of the Grade A Bounty Mission [Harrofal's Revenge]!

This was completely unexpected to Han Xiao. He was stunned as guesses flashed through his mind.

"It's these people‽ They've been missing for many months, so why are they suddenly here‽"

Han Xiao started to feel alarmed.

Harrofal's last words said that these people were very likely EsGod's subordinates whom he had sent to avenge him. Harrofal was already dead, and now these people had suddenly appeared on Planet Macipher after a few months...

Could they have finally found him?

Han Xiao did not feel that was the case. He had kept his whereabouts hidden and disguised his identity; there was no way EsGod's subordinates would have been able to find him.

"This is Planet Macipher, the edge of the Shattered Star Ring. Now that they're here after a few months... Hmm, could it be that they're planning to leave the Shattered Star Ring and escape from the Tyla Civilization, not coming for me anymore?"

Han Xiao frowned, deep in thought. From his perspective, what had happened regarding Harrofal was their only link. With such limited clues, he could only make very little speculations.

He did not expect to meet EsGod's subordinates there. Was this their plan, or was it a pure coincidence?

After pondering for a while, Han Xiao had made up his mind.

"No matter what, since these people are here, be it to avenge Harrofal or to complete the Bounty Mission, there's no reason to let them get away!"

Harrofal was his friend that had fought alongside him. Though Han Xiao did not have the time to search for the culprit, he would not let them go since they had appeared right before his eyes.

Han Xiao looked at the surveillance footage again, and he thought that he had guessed Sardeem's goal.

"Humph, it seems this guy wants the bounty as well. I have to strike first!"

This was not difficult for him at all. Since he had already hacked into the floating city's control center, he just had to make the mechanical law reinforcement troops not trigger the alarm, and he would be able to get to these people before Sardeem.

The only problem was, Han Xiao felt that these people might have EsGod's doppelgangers.

Han Xiao clenched his fists. Due to that possibility, the threat of Orozen and his gang was very close to Beyond Grade A to him, so he remained cautious.

"Currently, I'm hidden, and they're not. My only choice is to kill them before they can summon the EsGod doppelganger!"

Han Xiao clenched his teeth.

He did not know how strong these people were except that Orozen was Calamity Grade, but he could easily beat a group of normal Calamity Grades.

He should have a fifty percent chance of killing them before they could use the EsGod doppelganger!

Chapter 754: Did I Become Blind‽

After locking onto Orozen's location, Han Xiao immediately contacted Feidin and Hila.

"Where are you?"

The scene of a beast fighting colosseum appeared on the screen with a couple of beasts from different planets fighting each other in the plaza. The plaza was separated from the spectator stands with a protective shield, and the stands were filled with people. Feidin was seated within the crowd, and both Hila and Aurora were beside him with all their attention focused on the plaza.

"This is the biggest gambling den in the city, so we're gambling here," Feidin replied helplessly.

"Since when do you like gambling?" Han Xiao asked with doubt.

"Cough, I don't like it, but Chen Xing insisted on coming. She said that it would be a waste to not collect free money and asked me to earn some..."

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly and asked, "So, what about the other two?"

"They insisted on following me..."

Just as he finished saying those words, the battle in the stadium ended. A large python with screen scales spat out a venomous fog and paralyzed the final beast.

"We won again! We won again!" Aurora waved her arm excitedly. "Sister, we've won four times in a row now!"

Hila nodded before turning around to look at Feidin with a hint of addiction in her eyes. "What will you be betting on next?"

Feidin shrugged helplessly, as if he did not wish to lead them further astray.

Han Xiao felt his head ache upon witnessing such a scene and said, "Stop playing already. We have something to do. Come and meet up with me. I will be waiting for you guys at City No. 2. I will send you the coordinates later."

Han Xiao then hung up and left the port for City No. 2 while maintaining his connection to the main system of the floating city.

Why bother waiting for another day? Han Xiao decided to move against Orozen and his gang immediately!

However, Sardeem was a subordinate of the Mechanic Empire, so Han Xiao did not plan to reveal his true identity. Furthermore, he had already obtained the blueprints, and there was no need for him to remain on Planet Macipher. Barne's identity was already useless, so he was not afraid of making trouble under Barne's name. He did not need to worry about the repercussions of dealing with Orozen on the surface of the planet.

Han Xiao waited at the gathering point of City No. 2 for a while, and Hila's group of three met up with him soon after. The moment that they saw Han Xiao, Aurora immediately detected Han Xiao's change and let out a gasp.

"Your life force has been strengthened again!"

Feidin and Hila were both stunned as they heard that.

Han Xiao did not deny it and nodded. "I have a feeling that I have already touched the door to becoming a Beyond Grade A Super."

Hila's body shook, and she looked at Han Xiao with a complicated gaze.

Feidin was extremely happy for Han Xiao and asked, "Are we going to leave Planet Macipher?"

"Yes, but before we leave, I have something else to do..."

Han Xiao immediately explained to the others about what he intended to do.

Hila nodded. "Since the enemies are Grade A Supers, Feidin and I will accompany you, and Aurora should wait on the spaceship."

Feidin did not have any issue with killing a wanted criminal, but he was a little puzzled. "With your strength, you shouldn't need our help to deal with two Calamity Grade Supers, right?"

Han Xiao shook his head, and his tone became solemn. "Don't look down on them. They are subordinates of EsGod and have an EsGod doppelganger with Beyond Grade A strength. We need to kill them the instant the battle breaks out, so I will be going all out from the start. I will be more confident with both of you there!"

Upon hearing that this matter was related to a Beyond Grade A Super, Hila and Feidin both became serious.

"If the enemy summons EsGod's doppelganger, my life won't be in danger because of my strength, but it is different for the both of you. Thus, both of you must listen to my orders; we only have a single chance."

Han Xiao immediately described his plan to them.

He had already suffered a loss once, so he did not make any rash moves this time. Because the enemy did not know of his existence, he decided to first make sufficient preparations.

City No. 2's Star Bridge Inn was where Colin and the others were staying.

Star Bridge Inn was located in the red light district of City No. 2, and this was a district with various entertainment facilities. This inn was located in the middle of the street and was extremely eye catching.

Colin and his gang had arrived on Planet Macipher that day. After sending their spaceships for repairs, they spent their money like water in the inn and called for hostesses of different races to serve them.

The members of Fallen Ark naturally did not have any discipline and were used to indulging in their desires. Even though Colin was extremely focused on the mission, he did not reject this activity. The moment they began their long return journey, they would have to spend a few years in the desolate universe belt. Those last few days on Planet Macipher would be their final chance to enjoy themselves.

Colin pushed aside the hostess who was sleeping on him and climbed out from his bed. The large bed was currently filled with more than ten exhausted females of different species.

He then put on his robe to cover his scarred body and took out a bottle of beer from the fridge. Finishing half the bottle in a single mouth, he walked to the window of the room and looked outside at the view.

It was already late in the night, but there were still many pedestrians on the streets. However, at least forty to fifty percent of them were drunk. Green and red lights intersected each other to form rainbow-colored lights in the sky of the city, and the entire planet seemed to be indulging in luxuries. From time to time, an aircraft would cut across the sky; they were the mechanical patrol squad making their rounds.

Looking out at the scenery, Colin recalled all of his actions over the past few months. He had performed two great feats in the Shattered Star Ring. He had thrown the Star Pupil Holy Race into complete chaos with their local Beyond Grade A Super being tricked by him as well. Following which, he had managed to complete his mission and retreat successfully. Colin could not help but have a sense of pride in his heart.

He then touched the Evolution Cube, which was hanging on his neck, and smirked with disdain.

"Ah... the Shattered Star Ring."

This Star Field did not amount to much.

Just when this thought surfaced in his head, a blinding light exploded from the window before him.

Boom!

The window frame exploded the very next moment!

The shockwave from the explosion sent the unprepared Colin flying backward. His back smashed through the wall of the room, and he landed in the corridor of the inn. At the same time, a similar explosion happened in all the rooms, and all of Colin's subordinates were sent flying.

The entire inn experienced explosions with rocks and concrete slabs flying in all directions. A huge dust cloud enveloped the entire inn, and the inn was reduced to ruins.

A naked Orozen also fell into the corridor, and both Colin and Orozen looked at each other. The look of fury in their eyes revealed the same message.

There is someone who actually dares ambush us?

Could they be bounty hunters?

The enemy was definitely after the bounty issued by the Tyla Civilization, but with both of them present, the bounty hunters were seeking death!

Colin glared at Orozen fiercely and was about to unleash his Calamity Grade strength to get rid of the bounty hunters.

The very next moment, two mental attacks swept across the entire inn. One was dark red and the other colorless.

Hu!

The brains of all his subordinates exploded, and only Colin and Orozen were able to endure the two mental attacks. However, they felt a splitting headache, and their minds blanked out, temporarily losing control of their body.

There were actually two Calamity Grade Supers among the bounty hunters‽

The faces of Colin and Orozen changed greatly.

But before they could even struggle, a brilliant ray of light shone in their eyes again.

This was the last scene that both of them saw.

Outside the Star Bridge Inn, the pedestrians were all shocked and hid as far away as they could.

A moment ago, a large mechanical army had suddenly appeared and surrounded the entire inn. The mechanical army rained down heavy fire on the inn with tens of thousands of shots being fired every second.

Boom!

The street that the Star Bridge Inn was located on had been flattened!

The crowd on the streets were blocked out by the mechanical army and could not see what was going on inside.

On the other side of the encirclement, Han Xiao watched as the mechanical soldiers brought two corpses before him.

The two corpses belonged to Colin and Orozen.

Before either of them could even fight back, they were wiped out by the ambush of the mechanical army!

Han Xiao had tried his best to overestimate the combat strength of the enemy and was prepared to personally engage with the enemy when the mechanical army rained down their fire from the side. However, he had never imagined that the two Calamity Grade Supers would die under a single round of fire. He was truly dumbfounded.

This had gone much more successfully than he expected.

Han Xiao had formulated a few backup plans but realized that they were all completely useless. The ease of this mission truly shocked him.

Weren't they the subordinates of EsGod? Why were they so weak?

I thought that the subordinates of EsGod would be a little bit more powerful. It doesn't feel any different from killing other Calamity Grade Supers...

Han Xiao's mouth contorted, and he felt as though he had just plunged his fists into cotton.

This was no different from killing a chicken with an ox's blade.

Oh, it may be because I just had a Class Advancement, which increased my strength. Thus, I am able to suppress ordinary Calamity Grade Supers more easily. Right, neither of them have a talent that ignores true damage. I triggered the True Damage attack thrice, so it's not too surprising for them to have been taken out in a single go.

Han Xiao could only persuade himself as such.

Originally, he could already suppress almost all Calamity Grade Supers. After completing his Class Advancement, not to mention two Calamity Grade Supers, he would be able to face even twenty of them.

With Orozen dead, the [Harrofal's Revenge] mission was also completed. He then got Phillip to use one of his mechanical suits to take Orozen's corpse back to the Tyla Civilization in exchange for the bounty.

At this moment, Han Xiao looked at the other corpse and spotted the cube on Colin's neck.

What is this thing? It actually wasn't destroyed despite the attacks of the mechanical army?

Han Xiao bent down to pick up the black cube with curiosity.

The instant that he touched the black cube, an introduction of the item popped up on his interface.

Glancing at the introduction, Han Xiao's jaw dropped, and he almost did not dare to believe what he had seen.

Evolution... Cube?

Did I become blind‽

Isn't this Psyker's Universal Treasure? Why would it appear here‽

Did I just pick up a divine weapon on the streets‽

Han Xiao held onto the Evolution Cube and was stunned silly on the spot.

He then came to an enlightenment.

Turning around abruptly, his gaze was fixed on Feidin, who was by his side.

"Why are you looking at me?"

Feidin felt his hair stand from Han Xiao's gaze.

Han Xiao swallowed a mouthful of saliva and gave a thumbs up.

"Feidin! Awesome!"

Feidin had a face full of confusion.

A few minutes later, Sardeem led a large machinery army and arrived at City No. 2.

Only a pile of rubble was left behind, along with a huge crowd watching by the side. Han Xiao and his mechanical army had long disappeared.

The security squad hurriedly cleaned up the battlefield but could not find a single clue.

The group of people being monitored were all killed without their corpses being left behind. I can't even find a single trace of their attackers!

Sardeem was truly exasperated.

Because of Han Xiao's control, the scouts that Sardeem had used to spy on Colin did not send any information to Sardeem. All the mechanical patrol squads did not stop Han Xiao's group, and the surveillance footage had been destroyed.

Up until now, Sardeem had been kept in the dark and did not know what had happened.

Just who killed Colin and his group?

Just how powerful would an enemy capable of instantly killing a Calamity Grade Super be?

What was the objective of the attackers? Were they bounty hunters, were they Psyker's special force, or was there a hidden reason?

If the attackers were not Psyker's men, this meant that the people under his watch had been killed with the attackers disappearing. Just how would he answer to Psyker?

Sardeem felt a headache coming on and could only report the situation honestly to Psyker.

Chapter 755: Preparing for a Hot Potato

Meanwhile, Han Xiao took Hila and Feidin to escape from the scene. He clutched the Evolution Cube in his hand, his expression conflicted.

It was an unexpected joy to be able to pick up the Evolution Cube. After this ecstasy, Han Xiao gradually calmed down.

Since the Evolution Cube had already appeared, it should have nothing to do with Feidin. There had to be a deeper reason behind this, likely an event that happened somewhere that he was unaware of.

The emergence of the Evolution Cube had also cleared up any blind spots of information. Han Xiao's brain moved rapidly, re-examining this series of events and speculating on the causes and consequences.

The appearance of Psyker's Evolution Cube in the hands of these people means that they stole the Universal Treasure from Psyker in some way and transported it. No wonder they went silent for months after killing Harrofal. Turns out, their plan was not to retaliate but to plot to steal the Evolution Cube...

Han Xiao now understood their plan.

It seems like I was mistaken. These people were not here to deal with me but to steal treasures...

But why did they kill Harrofal? Did he have something to do with the theft of the treasure, or was there another motive behind it?

In his previous life, the Evolution Cube had only been made known to the players when it was in the hands of the Arcane Church. Until Austin revealed the secret, Han Xiao did not know that the Evolution Cube actually belonged to Psyker during this time period. While this might not have been a secret to the higher levels, it was not something that was publicized, and with the current level of the players, it was difficult to obtain this sort of intelligence.

In the later versions, players who joined the Arcane Church faction could pay contribution points and Enas in exchange for the opportunity to use the Evolution Cube.

The effect of the Evolution Cube was mainly for the transcendence of a species, and its specific role varied from each person. If the weaker party became stronger, the stronger would increase even more. However, the first time that it was used would give the greatest effect. Any subsequent attempts would become weaker until there was no longer any effect.

The Evolution Cube went from Psyker to the Arcane Church. I'm not sure what happened halfway. Did EsGod interfere in the transportation?

Han Xiao suddenly paused. He recalled that in his past life, there was intelligence about EsGod creating trouble in the Star Pupil Holy Race. However, it did not occur during this time period but an event in between Versions 3.0 and 4.0. The players did not experience it in person, only seeing a text record on it, and there was no mention of the Evolution Cube.

"Phillip, do a search on the latest news report of the Star Pupil Holy Race," Han Xiao ordered.

Planet Avitan's news was quickly searched through by Phillip, but due to the PR control by its government, the specific process was obscured. There was only mention that Planet Avitan had suffered heavy casualties and did not mention the name of the EsGod.

Because the huge Star Field would generate hundreds if not more of such stories every day, the event on Planet Avitan did not affect the Shattered Star Ring on a large scale. Thus, Han Xiao would not normally have paid attention to such a small story that did not involve him.

Han Xiao thought for a moment. The incident on Planet Avitan should have been committed by EsGod. I am eighty percent certain that they stole the Evolution Cube from Psyker, with the strategy of feigning an attack in the east but hitting the west.

In that case, the attack on the Star Pupil Holy Race by EsGod was carried forward.

In connection with Harrofal's death, Han Xiao had a feeling of shock.

Could this be related to me? Is this the so-called butterfly effect?

A pity, if only there was one person left alive.

Han Xiao was a little troubled. He had planned for everything to be foolproof, going out with full force, but who knew that their opponents would be so weak that they would be wiped immediately? There was no chance left to interrogate any of them.

Wait a minute...

At this point, Han Xiao lurched to a stop. Thinking about the intelligence that he had received, a new doubt surfaced in his mind.

Since EsGod was acting secretly, and there was no sign from the Star Pupil Holy Race that the Evolution Cube had been stolen. Then, the reason Sardeem was monitoring this group would be interesting indeed.

Perhaps Sardeem was not interested in the bounty reward offered by the Tyla Civilization but the Evolution Cube in their hands‽

Han Xiao's brows furrowed. He thought of three possibilities.

The first possibility was that Sardeem had some sort of special intelligence channel and managed to obtain news of the location of the Evolution Cube, thus wanting to take it for himself.

The second was that the Mechanic Empire was aware of this matter and wished to be the fisherman that obtained all the benefits, thus instructing Sardeem, who was situated in the Shattered Star Ring, to obtain the Evolution Cube.

The last possibility was that Sardeem had been asked by Psyker to help the Star Pupil Holy Race regain the Evolution Cube... no, Psyker might not have told the truth, as Sardeem was only told to monitor them, so he might not have known about the existence of the Evolution Cube.

Whichever possibility it was, Sardeem was a competitor, and in the worst-case scenario, it meant that a Beyond Grade A Super, Psyker, was also on his way there.

Weighing the Evolution Cube in his hand, Han Xiao's eyes were solemn.

He was no stranger to the Evolution Cube. At least he knew that the original shape of the Evolution Cube was huge, so the cube in his hands should be a portable version of the Evolution Cube.

Austin said that he himself had not seen the appearance of the Evolution Cube before. Psyker has not publicly displayed the Evolution Cube like the Arcane Church, so there should be few people that know of it, and Sardeem himself may not even recognize it...

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something, and his face changed as he hurriedly contacted Aurora who was on the spaceship.

"How's the situation on the ground at the port?"

Aurora was mystified. "Uncle, how did you know that there was a situation? We've just received a notice from the ground control that someone attacked the city, so the departure passage will be temporarily closed and departure restricted. Only when all the perpetrators are caught will they loosen the regulations."

Indeed!

Han Xiao kneaded his fingers.

The moment he got rid of the subordinates of the EsGod, Sardeem immediately locked down the entire planet, not allowing anyone to leave.

Such a big move was not only just to 'arrest the perpetrators of the attack on the city' but also to keep the Evolution Cube on this planet.

However, this would raise a new problem. With him having concealed his tracks, Sardeem had no way to pursue him. Even if they did security checks on Planet Macipher, how long would it take to find the Evolution Cube? With the number of people present, the difficulty was just like finding a needle in a haystack. Without the corresponding detection method, just shutting down the planet was futile.

Thus, Sardeem should have some methods of locating the Evolution Cube. Maybe it's a detection instrument that can sense the position when it comes within a certain distance. This may also be the detection method of Psyker. The detection should be limited, otherwise I would have long been spotted by Sardeem.

Although he did not experience the whole process himself, based on the clues that the Evolution Cube gave him, Han Xiao could guess the sequence of events. His mind suddenly brightened up.

With this in mind, Han Xiao told the other two to stop.

His original intention was to leave Planet Macipher immediately after killing Orozen, but Sardeem had already stopped the air traffic control before he could even get into his spaceship. If he wished to leave, he would have to forcibly break through their defenses, so he was in no hurry. Rather than rushing back to the port, he might as well think of how to deal with the Evolution Cube that he had now gotten his hands on.

Han Xiao summed up his current situation.

Getting the Evolution Cube meant having to face Sardeem, whose intentions were unknown; Psyker, whose house had been robbed; the scheming EsGod; and the Arcane Church!

At least two Beyond Grade As and a Universal Civilization would be looking for trouble with him!

Han Xiao sucked in a deep breath of air, realizing that this Evolution Cube was a hot potato!

While it was a joyful surprise, it posed a danger!

Therefore, he had to be cautious when dealing with the Evolution Cube.

Han Xiao turned solemn and quickly calculated the pros and cons in his head.

There are only two ways to deal with this. Hide it or give it away.

If I wish to keep the Evolution Cube... Well, I'm not far away from the Beyond Grade A class myself, so I have the qualifications to occupy a Universal Treasure. But the consequences will be becoming an enemy of Psyker. EsGod will also target me in order to obtain the Evolution Cube. I already have a relationship akin to fire and water with the Tyrant. If Psyker and the Tyrant join hands... things don't look too optimistic.

But the benefit of keeping it is that not only can I use it to strengthen those in the Black Star Army, I can also use it to attract more forces. There are few civilizations that can resist the temptation of the Evolution Cube. Psyker did not do this as he and the Arcane Church monopolized the usage of Evolution Cube. They did not wish to use it to cultivate more competitors.

Han Xiao secretly nodded to himself. Sardeem might have locked down the planet, but he could not stop him from taking the Evolution Cube. Even without forcibly breaking through, he could still quietly take the cube away from Planet Macipher with a Void Dimension Jump.

So long as Sardeem was unable to find the cube, sooner or later, the lockdown would end, and the trio would then be able to get out through the spaceship.

The issue was, if he kept the Evolution Cube, he would not be able to disguise it from the other organizations. The Black Star Army would then become a target of public criticism.

Han Xiao groaned.

Even if I hand it over, choosing the person to hand it to will be a problem—EsGod, the Mechanic Empire, the Universal Civilization, or Psyker.

Passing it over to EsGod would turn him from a foe to an ally, but if things were revealed, he risked offending the three Universal Civilizations as well as many other forces. Generally speaking, the risks were too great, and the disadvantages outweighed the advantages.

It would also be strange to hand it over to the Mechanic Empire. It would be in line with Planet Macipher and Sardeem, throwing the Evolution Cube that was the hot potato over to someone else, and using it to exchange for a large amount of resources. At the same time, it would also allow him to get rid of the danger, stay out of the fight, and avoid any struggles.

If given to a Universal Civilization, they would turn into staunch allies. Who it was given to would affect the benefits. The Federation of Light would give a lot of resources in exchange, whereas the Crimson Dynasty would give him a ticket to the Flickering World in addition to the resources.

These two were possible. As for the Arcane Church, it would be detrimental for him to hand over the cube to them.

If he passed it to the Arcane Church, things would be more complicated since Psyker was already considered an ally of theirs. The Arcane Church might not forsake Psyker to favor him, and either way, he would lose a Beyond Grade A ally.

However, with him turning into Beyond Grade A, the Arcane Church might not use force to try to snatch the Evolution Cube, which meant that the final result would be them returning the Evolution Cube to Psyker to maintain their relationship if he handed it over to them. In that case, not only would they retain Psyker, they would have him as their ally and still be allowed to use the Evolution Cube.

Psyker might appreciate the Arcane Church, but the same could not be said of Han Xiao.

Of course, the Arcane Church was a hegemon and would not be afraid of annoying Psyker. There was also the possibility of them pocketing the Evolution Cube.

The final option would be returning it to the owner and keeping things quiet. This would undoubtedly allow him to gain the friendship of Psyker, and he might even be able to borrow the Evolution Cube from time to time like the Arcane Church.

Just as Han Xiao was weighing the costs and benefits, Feidin asked, "Black Star, where are we going now? Aren't we going back to the spaceship?"

Han Xiao regained his senses, thought about it, and shook his head. "There's no need. Hila, bring Aurora over."

They could not go back to the Cornerstone Summit Corporation anymore. Sardeem would definitely suspect himself first of all as an unknown Calamity Grade Mechanic, and he would have reported him. Since he would be suspected whether he returned or disappeared, there was no need to keep up with the pretenses.

Anyway, I was the one who did it, and I, Barne, am righteous and unafraid of trouble!

Han Xiao temporarily let go of his mental struggle.

He was long used to taking a rain check and calculating the best possible outcome, but no matter what, the Evolution Cube belonged to him alone for the moment.

Enjoy it before deciding!

"Your Excellency Psyker, I've already locked down the planet's port."

On the other side, Sardeem was communicating with Psyker.

"Before I arrive, don't let anyone go," Psyker blandly replied.

"Alright... but please hurry. I cannot keep the lockdown for an indefinite period of time."

Sardeem had an expression of helplessness. Luckily, there was an excuse of hunting down the perpetrators to maintain law and order, but locking the port for too long would cause Planet Macipher's business to suffer, and this was something that he could not accept.

"You've worked hard. I'm almost here," Psyker replied.

"Ok, what should I do now?"

"There's no need for you to do anything else. Just ensure that no one leaves Planet Macipher. If anyone tries to forcibly leave, stop them personally."

He could tell that the Evolution Cube was still on Planet Macipher, but the distance was too far from it to be accurately predicted. Thus, when Sardeem informed him that EsGod's subordinates had been killed, Psyker was slightly surprised but regained his calm afterward.

As long as the treasure was still on Planet Macipher, it would all be good. The moment he arrived personally, he would then be able to discover the position of the Evolution Cube.

Chapter 756: Genetic Optimization and Ambitions

Along one of the continuous mountain ranges of Planet Macipher, a mountain face was dug out by Han Xiao's machinery to form a cave, and the cave was equipped with a fully automatic environmental shelter, disguised as a rock. In the light of dawn, those outside could not see the existence of the cave, and the energy detection shield blocked out many of the satellite detectors that Sardeem had arranged in outer space, making it impossible for the owner of the planet to discover any energy responses here with just satellites. This area was a blind spot on their radar.

Within the cave was a hollowed-out mountain belly, and Han Xiao had unfolded a portable mechanical fortress there, occupying thousands of square meters. Numerous mechanical foundations were spread across the mountain walls, supporting the hollowed abdomen of the mountain. This area had turned into a stronghold, and the multiple mechanical foundations also served as light sources, illuminating the darkness of the cave.

After laying his hands on the Evolution Cube the previous night, Han Xiao had analyzed his situation clearly and decided to leave the Planet Macipher's city to set up a temporary hidden stronghold in the wilderness of the planet to prevent Sardeem from detecting their usage of the Evolution Cube. After Hila brought Aurora over, Han Xiao took the three of them there and built a small base with the compressed orbs that he carried with him.

He always carried equipment to set up a temporary camp.

After settling down, Han Xiao took out the Evolution Cube, explaining his hypothesis so far. Originally, the three of them were confused over Han Xiao's sudden irrational behavior, but after hearing the history of the item, they were enlightened.

The trio looked curiously at the small black cube in Han Xiao's hands. Aurora was purely curious about Universal Treasures, while Hila was interested in its ability to promote one's strength.

Feidin, however, showed an anxious expression. "This is the Evolution Cube of legends? Since we've picked it up, what do we do now? Do we return it to Psyker? Will he think that we stole it?"

Because he had followed Han Xiao to visit Austin, he knew that this belonged to Psyker.

Han Xiao could only helplessly reply, "I haven't thought of that yet."

"It can't be that you're thinking of keeping the Evolution Cube," Feidin said. "If you do, we'll also become enemies with Psyker. Now that you've already provoked the Tyrant, if we add on Psyker, that would mean that you've provoked half of the Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring..."

Han Xiao interrupted him. "We can discuss that later. Since the Evolution Cube is in my hands, let's first use."

"How do we use it?" Hila impatiently asked.

"If my memory serves me right..."

Han Xiao flipped the small black cube around, scrutinizing it. Every face was as smooth as a mirror, absent of any notches. Even when he exerted strength with his fingers, it did not leave any traces.

After hesitating, he covered the two sides of the cube with both his palms, pressing down on all corners of the cube simultaneously. The next moment, the inky black surface lit up with streams of light, and a spherical black energy ball wrapped around the cube, suspending it in midair.

"The first step was right..." Han Xiao was overjoyed.

The easiest way to utilize the Evolution Cube was to enter it when it was in its natural state. However, when the Evolution Cube was fixed in its portable mode, the container needed to be opened in a specific manner to expose an opening where the energy from the cube could exit.

The first step was thus to put the container into its 'Ready' status. This was what Han Xiao had just done. However, it did not mean that the cube had been activated yet.

A cover would then materialize around the cube, which served as a password input screen. A series of specific 'passcode symbols' would have to be drawn on it to open the container. This was equivalent to a password. Compared to the Secret Message Bead, this was actually quite simple.

Many players from his past life had used the Evolution Cube in the Arcane Church in exchange for their Contribution Points. Thus, there were a few that had watched the NPCs from the Arcane Church unlock the Evolution Cube in person and recorded it. The process was not a secret to him, and there were even others who posted a summary of the passwords for the Evolution Cube, which were made up of forty-two different symbols.

However, the exact shape and position of the symbols were a little vague to Han Xiao. Fortunately, his Intelligence attribute had improved so much that his memories were already structured like a bookcase. All his memories were stored in different categories, which could be manually accessed and viewed. Such thinking modes could be mastered by ordinary people just after training, let alone for Mechanics with extremely high Intelligence and large brain areas. Otherwise, would it not be too difficult for them to memorize their blueprints?

After pondering for a while, he slowly recalled the structure of the symbols and started to trace with his fingers on the energy cover of the cube, leaving behind golden trails. He quickly finished drawing the symbols, but the energy hood was only drawn back, and the cube dropped onto the ground. Obviously, it was a failure, causing him to stagger slightly.

That's right. The password set by the Arcane Church might not be the same as that set by the EsGod. Han Xiao suddenly realized the issue. He was a little depressed. If he failed to open the Evolution Cube, he could only smash it to allow it to regain its original size. The commotion created by that would be too big, and people would definitely notice.

Frowning and sighing, he consoled himself. That might not be the case as well. The Evolution Cube belonged to a lost civilization, and making portable containers was also this civilization's technology. It is very advanced and is not something ordinary people can decipher. Maybe the Gods can make containers such as these, but it should be difficult to improve the technology.

As such, these forty-two symbols should be the fixed password of the container. As to why the container was not opened... maybe my drawing was inaccurate, or the order was wrong.

Han Xiao did not know that he had guessed upon the truth. This set of symbols was a fixed activation password of the portable Evolution Cube, which could not be changed. It was not only used to unlock the container but also the key to harnessing the energy of the Evolution Cube.

This was the top-secret information left behind by the Evolutionary Cube's Civilization. At present, such knowledge was only in the hands of EsGod. Even Colin and the others did not know how to open it, to prevent their greed, betrayal, or accidental disclosure of information.

In his previous life, the Arcane Church had not been afraid of leaking out such information as no one could take away their items, so Han Xiao had become one of the few people currently who knew the password needed to open it.

He tried more than thirty times, slowly replicating the symbols, refining his accuracy. Finally, on his thirty-seventh try, there was a different reaction from the Evolution Cube.

From the center of every face on the cube, a small hole appeared, in which a black stream of ribbon-like particles escaped, surrounding the cube and propelling it in the air.

"It's open!" Han Xiao exclaimed.

Looking at the others, Han Xiao first took a deep breath, before stretching out his palm and releasing his Mechanical Force toward the Evolution Cube.

Hu!

The next moment, the black stream seemed to have discovered a vent to escape from and flocked over to Han Xiao, continuously infiltrating his body from his skin.

Itchy!

That was his first thought.

This sort of itch seemed to be born from his soul. His skin, muscles, bones, blood vessels, and organs all felt the itch, but it was impossible to reach out and scratch it like scratching one's body. The symptoms could not be relieved at all.

At this point, notifications started to pop up from the interface.

You have utilized the Evolution Cube (Gold Grade)!

You have received a permanent special benefit—[Gene Optimization: Evolution Cube]!

Identifying species... Identification complete. Your current species is: [Void Star Pursuer].

Your genetic structure is now being adjusted to the best state of the [Void Star Pursuer]. Please do not interrupt the Evolution process.

The first optimization has succeeded. Your potential qualities have increased. You have received +6 STR, +4 DEX, +5 INT, +4 MYS, +3 CHA, and +30 Energy.

Because your Energy Level is above Level 0, the second optimization has automatically succeeded. Your potential qualities have increased, and you have received +8 STR, +7 DEX, +11 END, +7 INT, +5 MYS, +6 CHA, and +40 Energy.

...

Because your Energy Level is above Level 14, the sixteenth optimization has automatically succeeded. Your potential qualities have increased, and you have received +64 STR, +67 DEX, +72 END, +76 INT, +61 MYS, +43 CHA, and +240 Energy.

When he was rushing toward level 238, his Energy Attribute had broken through the 40,000 mark, achieving the [Level 14] bonus.

For each additional energy attribute level, one would be able to access an additional layer of genetically optimized attributes as a reward. Hence, the stronger one's body was, the better the effect of one's first use. The attributes awarded were based on a variety of factors, such as cell activity, life span, and species—of which the species had the greatest impact. The Evolution Cube would be optimized based on the race, and if one's racial species was more powerful, their benefits would be greater.

When the Evolution Cube was used for the second time onward, it would not be calculated based on the new strength level but rather repeat the optimization process for each layer. However, the attributes given would be greatly reduced, with each subsequent usage giving out less than the previous one, until there was no effect. Only through the sublimation into a new racial species would one then regain some benefits, but even that would be far less effective than the first use of the Evolution Cube.

Han Xiao endured his itchiness while calculating in his mind. This series of genetic optimizations had provided him with an extremely terrifying increase in his attributes. The five attributes of Strength, Dexterity, Endurance, Intelligence, and Mystery shot up by more than five hundred points, while Charm was increased by nearly four hundred points. As for Energy, there was an increase of 2,100!

This wave of soaring attributes exceeded the total amount of attribute points that he had obtained up till Energy Level 14!

The sum of all his improved attributes added to reach more than three thousand points, which was equivalent to Han Xiao's attributes being improved by a third. The effect was outstanding!

Because the potential of the [Void Star Pursuer] was strong—coupled with his young age, high vitality cells, and strong energy—the increase was terrifying!

When he had upgraded his profession to Emperor Mechanic, rising to level 238, his total Energy count had been at 32,600. Right now, after utilizing the Evolution Cube, he suddenly leaped up by another 2,000 points, reaching 34,450.

Even though the itchiness in Han Xiao was hard to bear, he could not help but reveal an expression of joy. This genetic optimization was too worthwhile.

However, the notifications on the interface had not yet ended.

The first time utilizing the Evolution Cube awarded you with sixteen layers of genetic optimization. There will be a +40% experience penalty to level up, which will last for 16 months.

Han Xiao nodded to himself secretly. Players would suffer from experience penalties upon using the Evolution Cube. After all, the attributes obtained were equivalent to gaining ten or more levels. It was just like the saying of pulling up seedlings to help them grow—it would be impossible without a cost. This principle was just like how a stronger lifeform would find it harder to sublimate themselves. Each time the Evolution Cube was utilized, there would be a forty percent experience penalty, and the duration would depend on the number of genetic optimizations obtained.

However, this was nothing to Han Xiao. Just a forty percent experience penalty, under the influence of his thirty percent increase through the Political Asset, was essentially just a ten percent penalty. Han Xiao's experience gain relied on the experience of his leek fields. He could afford to just wait for a while, using this sixteen-month penalty in exchange for a large increase in attributes. This was a permanent force that would result in larger combat power.

Furthermore, the stronger one's attributes, the higher the energy level. As such, his chances of breaking through to the Beyond Grade A at level 240 was even higher now.

At this time, the interface popped up with the last few notifications.

Special Conditions met: On your first time utilizing the Evolution Cube, you unlocked more than ten layers of genetic optimizations.

Special effect triggered.

In the next advancement, you will receive an additional opportunity to perform a Race Evolution.

Gene Optimization has ended.

The black particle flow finally stopped flowing, retreating into the Evolution Cube.

Han Xiao hurriedly squatted down to take a breath, calming himself. He then slowly sensed the power within his newly increased attributes, giving him the feeling that he could blow up a whole planet.

Feidin rushed up to help, asking, "How was the effect?"

Han Xiao only waved his hands, signaling that there was no need for any aid. He then slowly stood up, feeling refreshed. Seeing Hila staring at him, he could not help but laugh.

"I've tested it, and the side effects are small. All of you should have a go."

Hila immediately nodded. "Let me go first then."

Han Xiao did not hesitate, opening the Evolution Cube again to allow the black particle stream to flow toward Hila.

From the perspective of an outsider, the black particle stream would wrap the user into a black cocoon. It took a while for Hila to break out of the cocoon, as though emerging from the cocoon as a butterfly. There was a red glow in her eyes, which then slowly faded.

"Sis, how do you feel?" Aurora curiously asked.

Hila clenched her fists, and her sharp look softened suddenly, as she revealed a rare smile.

"I feel really great."

Seeing the situation, Han Xiao smiled. He was happy to share the Evolution Cube, which would allow him to improve the backbone of his group.

Soon, there were another two cocoons beside the Evolution Cube. It was Feidin's and Aurora's turn to enjoy the baptism of genetic optimization.

Han Xiao stood beside them, looking at the two people who were undergoing the process, and suddenly spotted a problem.

If the Evolution Cube returned to Psyker, he would not know the opening symbols, only being able to destroy the container and release the evolution block, making it return to its original state.

It seemed ... that only Han Xiao knew how to use the evolutionary block in its portable state.

Once this thought was born, Han Xiao's eyes flashed.

Maybe this is a foundation for cooperation...

In a short while, Feidin and Aurora also completed their optimizations, and each experienced with their own changes.

"Ok, what's the plan now?" Feidin immediately asked. Since the Evolution Cube had been used, it was time for them to think about what to do next.

Han Xiao's answer was out of his expectations.

"You all will stay here."

The three of them stopped in shock.

"Are you planning to..." Feidin was in disbelief.

Before waiting for him to finish, Han Xiao nodded. "Sardeem has already sealed up the entire planet, so Psyker will probably catch up soon. I have my ways of protecting myself from a Beyond Grade A but not you guys. We will act separately this time. You guys stay here temporarily. I have a way to leave this planet."

His real objective was to utilize the Void Dimension Jump to leave Planet Macipher on his own. This way, he could precisely test the accuracy of the detection method that Sardeem or Psyker had.

No matter how he planned to deal with the Evolution Cube, he could not avoid taking a risk. In this manner, it would be better if he just operated solo. This way, he would not need to worry about his teammates.

In reality, this Evolution Cube was a hot potato, but since it had already fallen into his hands, Han Xiao was not willing to hand it over.

Risk and opportunity co-existed side by side. This was the situation that he had analyzed, and there was no doubt that only by keeping the Evolution Cube in his possession could he maximize the benefits.

As for whether he had the ability to keep it... if he did not try, how would he know?

Thus, Han Xiao decided to enter the desolate universe belt with the Evolution Cube by himself, giving himself time to accumulate enough experience to reach level 240.

While he did not know the exact context, he felt that the facts should be similar to his own deduction. It was likely that there would be a pursuer, which was most probably Psyker.

Han Xiao had nothing against Psyker and even respected such heroes who cared about their races.

The Evolution Cube only worked for an individual, but the descendants of powerful individuals would also end up inheriting certain genetic optimization effects. Furthermore, undergoing another process through the Evolution Cube would be a positive cycle, and this was exactly how Psyker had managed to evolve his Star Pupil Holy Race to its current state.

To this day, the Evolution Cube was still a very important tool for the development of the Star Pupil Holy Race...

However, what had that got to do with him?

He was not a member of the Star Pupil Holy Race!

He was not even the one who stole the cube!

He just picked it up!

Han Xiao had already made his decision. At least, he had to exchange blows with Psyker once. If he could not fend him off, it would not be too late to negotiate!

Chapter 757: This Is Not Personal; It's Just Too Tempting.

On the floating city of Planet Macipher, Sardeem was using all his law reinforcement troops to search for clues of the culprit who attacked Colin and the others.

He had not slept the previous night. Psyker's order was to lock the entire planet down to prevent the attackers from escaping, but Sardeem thought that if he could find the attacker soon, there would be no need to continue locking the ports down, which affected his businesses.

As it was related to his own profits, he was very motivated.

Sadly, he did not acquire any clues throughout the night—it was like the attackers had disappeared into thin air. There were no traces of them anywhere on any surveillance devices.

"Could they have the ability to teleport or something?" Sardeem scratched his head. "Or did all of my surveillance devices stop functioning?"

Sardeem could not help but look through the command records of the floating city's control center, but he did not discover any signs of it being hacked. Han Xiao had cleared his browsing history there long ago while also ending his temporary access. With Sardeem's ability, it was next to impossible for him to find out what Han Xiao had done.

Ring ring!

While Sardeem was getting frustrated, Psyker's call arrived once again.

"Your Excellency Psyker, what is it this time?" Sardeem suppressed his frustration and made his tone sound as natural as he could.

He was Mechanic Empire's subordinate. Sure, he did do quite a few things for Psyker because Psyker was a Beyond Grade A, but Psyker seemed to be commanding him as if he was his subordinate, which made Sardeem a little unhappy. This was mainly because locking the planet down damaged his profits, the key reason his attitude changed.

However, what Psyker said almost made Sardeem jump up from his seat.

"The fugitive has left Planet Macipher and is running outside the Shattered Star Ring. What are you doing?" Psyker's tone was relaxed no more and seemed truly grave, with a hint of blame.

Just a moment ago, he had sensed the Evolution Cube leaving Planet Macipher, moving away at hyperdrive speed. It had undoubtedly been taken away by someone, which made Psyker lose confidence and start to feel anxious.

"Impossible, I've locked down all the ports. No one should be able to leave Macipher for the time being!" Sardeem's face was filled with disbelief, and he almost thought that Psyker was deliberately blackmailing him.

How did Psyker know about the whereabouts of the attacker? Psyker was not there, and not even Sardeem, the owner of the planet, noticed someone escaping.

"Maybe the fugitive has some kind of ability to avoid your lockdown. Anyway, he's escaped. I need you to help me do one more thing," Psyker said with a low voice.

He was in quite a bad mood. He had been very close to arriving at Planet Macipher and easily retrieving the Evolution Cube. However, at such a crucial moment, an accident occurred. He had no idea if this was the act of another group of EsGod's subordinates ordered to continue the mission or that the Evolution Cube had been intercepted by someone else. No matter what, the situation was slowly getting out of his control.

EsGod's subordinates had died, and the person who now possessed the Evolution Cube and was escaping was a mystery!

"What do I need to do?" Sardeem put away his little thoughts.

"I will point you in the direction that the fugitive is running, and you follow them. My spaceship is very fast, so I will catch up with you soon."

"This..." Sardeem hesitated. He was confident about his strength so he was not worried about the danger but that someone would cause trouble on Planet Macipher while he was away.

As Psyker had not told him the truth since the start, Sardeem had started to realize that this matter seemed to be very significant.

"You'll be rewarded handsomely for helping me."

"...Okay then." Sardeem agreed in the end. "Does this mean that the lockdown on Planet Macipher can be canceled?"

"Whatever." Retrieving the Evolution Cube was Psyker's only target; everything else was none of his concern.

As the communication ended, Sardeem did not delay any longer and started to pack up and leave, chasing after Han Xiao with the coordinates sent by Psyker.

While gathering his mechanical troops, Sardeem ended the lockdown.

At this time, Sardeem suddenly recalled something and immediately contacted the upper echelons of the Cornerstone Summit Corporation.

"Where's Barne?"

"Your Excellency Sardeem, Barne was out the whole night last night and has yet to appear."

Sardeem narrowed his eyes. This Calamity Grade with unknown origin was the first person he suspected.

"I remember he has three friends, where are they?"

"Er... they're missing as well."

"They're most likely the attackers!" Sardeem heavily slammed the table with a vicious look on his face. He had thought that Barne was there to steal blueprints, but it turned out that he had something to do with this Psyker incident. This guy had prepared his ambush for more than twenty days!

Having thought of that, Sardeem immediately entered Barne and his friends' faces into the control center and made all the surveillance facilities notify him as soon as they discovered their whereabouts.

After that, Sardeem took along a ton of elite Giant Soldiers, boarded his spaceship, turned into a stream of light, and chased after Han Xiao.

At the same time, in a mechanical stronghold in a certain mountain in the wilderness of Planet Macipher, three people were waiting.

Han Xiao had secretly left the planet through Void Dimension Jump while leaving the stronghold behind for Feidin and the sisters to hide, as well as to monitor Sardeem's movements.

"Sis, the lockdown has been lifted, and Sardeem has left."

In front of a few virtual screens, Aurora was controlling the machines swiftly with her fingers.

As her Esper ability lacked combat power, she had learned a lot of other knowledge during the time she was on Floating Dragon Island. She had gained a ton of subclasses and was developing toward an all-round commander.

"Black Star guessed right. Sardeem left the planet and is going after him," Feidin said with resignation.

"And we're left behind..." Hila clenched her fists with a frustrated expression.

In order to protect the three of them, Han Xiao had left alone to lure out Psyker, who might appear. It was clear that the three of them were a burden.

Hila wanted to fight alongside Han Xiao, but Han Xiao had rejected her because she was not strong enough to deal with a Beyond Grade A Super.

She was irritated with herself for not being able to help him.

She had trained ten years with Ames and become a high-level combatant in the universe, so she had thought that she could finally help Han Xiao, but it turned out she was still a burden.

Hila clenched her teeth tightly and felt frustrated. She had ended her training to help Han Xiao, but now she had become someone that needed his protection once again. She was not willing to be protected by Han Xiao all the time; she wanted to fight alongside Han Xiao. Otherwise, how could she repay him for what he had done for her and Aurora?

Seeing that she was not looking too good, Feidin said in a worried tone, "Hila, don't overthink..."

Hila returned to being expressionless and said coldly, "Don't worry, I won't disobey his orders. Even if I insist on going after him to help, I'll only cause more trouble to him and become even more of a burden."

Feidin breathed a sigh of relief. After spending so much time together, he knew how stubborn Hila could be. He did not worry anymore and said with a smile, "You don't have to undervalue yourself. Black Star sees you as someone very important to him, and you still have a lot of room to grow. In the future, you will definitely be of great help."

Hila curled her lips and tightened her fists.

"You don't have to worry about him. After all, we've all undergone the effects brought by the Evolution Cube, which you should know about. Black Star is definitely even stronger," Feidin said.

Hila nodded. She knew very well of the Evolution Cube's effects—they were so significant that it almost felt like she had been reborn.

"Don't worry, I made many life force potions for him on the spot. He will be fine." Aurora chuckled. "Don't you trust my ability? You were just telling me to make more potions earlier."

Before Han Xiao left, Aurora had made many life force potions for him on the spot. She had learned pharmacology from Emerald Grass in the past and studied it further on Floating Dragon Island, so the level of her subclass was very high. Combined with her Esper Ability, every one of those potions was equivalent to full health recovery.

When Aurora was making the potions earlier, not only did Hila not stop her younger sister as usual, instead, she agreed to Aurora using more life force to make potions for Han Xiao.

Recalling that, Hila blushed a little bit and turned away to avoid Aurora's eyes while changing the topic.

"The planet lockdown has been lifted, and Sardeem has left. What should we do? Stay here or leave in a spaceship?"

Feidin thought about it then said, "We shall leave Planet Macipher after Sardeem is further away. It's safer that way."

Hila and Aurora nodded. As long as Feidin was the one that made the decision, it might not result in a profit, but it would definitely not result in a loss.

Outside the Shattered Star Ring edge, in the desolate universe belt, a light suddenly appeared. Han Xiao left the Void Dimension and appeared with his skin a little red from the universe's radiation.

Before him was a gray desolate planet. Han Xiao slowly landed on the cracked ground, crossed his legs, and hovered about a meter above the ground, waiting for his Army Boxes to arrive in hyperdrive.

He had used Void Dimension Jump to leave Planet Macipher, so his Army Boxes were still on the spaceship. He would only be at his peak as a Mechanic once his mechanical army arrived. As the Emperor Mechanic's [Secondary Dimension Army] was still unactivated, his army was not with him at all times.

That's a point. This is my first time actually leaving the Shattered Star Ring.

Looking up at the sky, this thought suddenly appeared in Han Xiao's mind.

In the last twenty odd years, he had always been in the Shattered Star Ring.

There were desolate universe belts between Star Clusters, as well as between Star Fields, where the latter was much bigger than the former. He had once fought in the desolate universe belt between Klent and Purple Crystal, which paled in comparison as compared to now.

The desolate universe belt that separated two Star Fields had extremely sparse resources and very low value. The planets were scattered, and it was deadly silent. Even if a civilization was born there, it would have no future because of the vile environment. In the entire known universe, desolate universe belts made up to more than sixty percent of the area. In the unexplored universe, desolate universe belts consisted of even larger areas.

After feeling nostalgic for a while, Han Xiao got back to business. He opened the faction interface and started a discount event for all the Knowledges in the faction store. The reason he did this was to reward the army members for having participated for many months in the secret war. The Contribution Point cost of learning Knowledges was sixty percent off!

In order to quickly make up the experience that he needed for the last two levels, Han Xiao used the promotion to stimulate purchases. Knowledges were a necessity for players, and the only difference was when they would learn it. Han Xiao needed the players to learn them right now, so having a promotion was the best method to encourage that. He was willing to earn fewer Enas for that.

This way, even with the forty percent experience penalty, it would not take long.

Before the enemies caught up, Han Xiao had quite a lot of confidence that he could level up to level 240.

Beep beep!

At this time, his communicator suddenly rang. It was a message from Hila.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes as he read it.

Sardeem has left Planet Macipher? He set off as soon as I left, so it seems although their locating method is not accurate enough, they are able to remotely locate the Evolution Cube.

This means that my whereabouts are transparent to them, and Sardeem and Psyker are heading right toward me.

As Han Xiao finally figured out the enemies' detection method, Han Xiao felt more confident.

The ability to locate the Evolution Cube should be where their confidence came from!

He did not wait for his Army Boxes anymore and once again used Void Dimension Jump, turning into a stream of light and heading further away.

Since he was being chased, he could not stop. This battle was unavoidable; all he could do was make detours to meet up with his Army Boxes while stalling for the time.

While in hyperdrive, Han Xiao pondered.

I have quite a number of trump cards. Aurora's potion, Dragon Emperor's Character Summon Card, the rarely used [Painful Revenge] and [Luck Curse]... I must use everything I have that's effective against a Beyond Grade A. It's been very long since an opponent that required me to use my full strength. However, the Psychic class counters me for quite a bit. Psyker also has powerful AOE abilities. As a Beyond Grade A, he will be able to easily destroy a ton of my mechanical soldiers. Sadly, I don't have the time to strengthen my mechanical army now...

As he had already tried in the stronghold, the Evolution Cube had no effects on his mechanical soldiers. After all, they were objects and did not have genes that could be improved. Maybe it would only be effective after they turned into real mechanical lives.

Sadly, [King's Mentor] was still unactivated, so he would only be able to test that in the future.

Without any machinery that was useful at the Beyond Grade A level, he would not be able to reach his peak performance right after his Promotion. If only he could increase the power of his machinery before fighting Psyker...

Han Xiao's eyes lit up suddenly.

Oh, that's right, Sardeem...

Chapter 758: Like Rain Pouring on a Field

With a flashing stream of light, Sardeem's spaceship stopped outside an asteroid belt.

He had been chasing Han Xiao, following the directions that Psyker gave, for a whole day. He had noticed that the target did not head directly into the desolate universe belt but traveled in an arc around the edge of the Shattered Star Ring at a slower speed than his spaceship.

He finally caught up with the target at this asteroid belt. The coordinates given by Psyker showed that the target was hiding in the asteroid belt right then.

The target has stopped here... Sardeem had a serious look on his face.

Countless asteroids floated in the universe like a river. Some were tens of thousands of meters wide, and some were just a dozen meters wide. They blocked Sardeem's view, and he could only use the radar on his spaceship to slowly scan the asteroid belt.

Given how large the asteroid belt was, it was indeed a great place to hide. Scanning through it was undoubtedly a troublesome task.

However, the moment Sardeem had this thought, the radar responded.

"Alert! Abnormal energy target detected!"

The vision on the porthole of the spaceship expanded. At the top of an enormous oval-shaped asteroid, a man was sat with his legs crossed. His face was hidden under his helmet, and his body was covered by the streamlined mechanical suit, with dark blue patterns evenly distributed across the surface of the armor. He was facing Sardeem's spaceship, clearly aware of Sardeem's arrival.

Sardeem narrowed his eyes. He stopped the spaceship, opened the hatch, and walked out. Red and gold armor extended from his chest over his entire body, forming heavy armor around his body.

Sardeem spoke first and sent a message to Han Xiao with an unfriendly tone. "Barne? Is that you?"

Han Xiao smiled faintly. "You can continue to call me that."

Sardeem snorted. He knew that the name 'Barne' was just an alias. As for his true identity, he did not ask back then, and he had no idea now.

However, that did not matter. He would have more than enough time to find out after he captured and interrogated him.

Having this thought, Sardeem's eyes started sparkling, and he came up with a plan.

Initially, Psyker only asked him to follow the target. However, since he had caught up, he was not afraid of fighting. Maybe he could pry out Psyker's secret from 'Barne' before Psyker arrived. He had no idea why this person was running and why Psyker was chasing after him, so he was in a rush to find out.

"I have one more question," Sardeem said with a low voice. "Your real goal was attacking these people, wasn't it? That's why you hid on Planet Macipher beforehand. Yet, you tried to steal blueprints while working in my business under a disguise. Weren't you afraid of getting exposed?"

From the way he looked at it, 'Barne' came and stayed on Planet Macipher to kill the group of people including Colin. Hence, he could not figure out why 'Barne' was so daring to be exposed right under his nose. Would waiting in a hotel in the city not have been stealthier?

"Will you believe if I say it's all because of luck?" Han Xiao smiled with resignation.

At the start, he just wanted to obtain a talent, then he discovered Eternal Light's blueprint, so he focused on stealing it. After that, Orozen suddenly came right before him. He then simply wanted to kill a wanted criminal but was dragged into the storm around the Evolution Cube...

Could this be because of the great Feidin?

"Luck?" Sardeem narrowed his eyes and found that very suspicious. He shook his head and said, "Never mind, I know I won't get anything from you now. You will learn to speak later when you're in my hands."

Right after his sentence ended, Sardeem's Mechanical Force erupted. The cabin of the spaceship opened. Red and gold Army Boxes shot right toward Sardeem like rockets and opened on the way. His mechanical army quickly formed a formation and hovered behind Sardeem.

With a brief look, there were about two to three million machines. Their models were very different from Han Xiao's; they were bulkier and more ferocious.

As an Armed Mechanic, Sardeem knew more blueprints for war machinery. The mechanical army under his command mainly consisted of heavily armored and large machines. There were five-meter-tall heavy mechanical soldiers everywhere and a few thousand conspicuous Giant Soldiers. The biggest was more than a thousand meters tall, even larger than many asteroids around them.

Other than all kinds of mechanical soldiers, there were also many combat devices that were often used in galactic wars.

Sardeem launched a ton of compressed orbs, which then expanded into huge parts that connected with his armor, forming a several-hundred-meter-tall Giant Soldier. He backed away into the center of his army. Many defense fortresses and hovering guards moved to surround him, forming multiple layers of defenses. There were also space stabilization devices around him, preventing the enemy from using hyperdrive to close the distance on him.

This was the authentic Army Style of fighting—the Mechanic was the commander in the middle of the army, focusing on utilizing the troops and formation to defeat the enemy step by step.

Seeing that Sardeem had summoned his army, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. As he scanned through Sardeem's army, he could not help but lick his lips.

"So much heavy machinery, good stuff." Han Xiao's fingers moved around slightly in anticipation.

The millions of mechanical soldiers simultaneously aimed at Han Xiao. Seeing Han Xiao did not even respond, Sardeem frowned slightly.

"You're a Mechanic too. Where's your army?" Sardeem said with a mocking tone. "Or have you decided not to embarrass yourself and are willing to surrender?"

Han Xiao smiled. He pointed behind Sardeem.

"Isn't my army arriving?"

Shocked, Sardeem turned around immediately.

Behind his army, streams of light rocketed from far away. It was the Black Star mechanical army that had arrived through hyperdrive!

As the Army Boxes opened one after another, more than ten million mechanical soldiers swarmed out like a black tsunami. It was more than three times bigger than Sardeem's army!

"How is this possible‽"

Sardeem's expression changed drastically with fear.

Suddenly, he realized that this 'Barne' was not just an ordinary person but someone well known from somewhere.

The size of the mechanical army represented the wealth of the Mechanic. Even maintaining the army required money. In the entire Shattered Star Ring, very few Mechanics could afford such an enormous mechanical army.

Names flashed through his Sardeem's mind, and he finally stopped on one.

Panicked, Sardeem hastily turned around and stared at Han Xiao with disbelief.

"You're... Black Star‽"

"That's correct. Here's a green hat as a reward." Han Xiao chuckled.

With the Evolution Cube in hand and breaking through to Beyond Grade A around the corner, there was no need to continue playing the 'Barne' role.

"Fire!" Sardeem's cool shattered instantly as he hastily ordered his army to start firing. The back of his army faced the approaching mechanical army, and the front of his army fired on Han Xiao.

Facing millions of light beam attacks, Han Xiao did not want to take it head-on. Like pulling on a cloth, his hands pulled down strongly. [Strengthened Void Distortion] caused chaos in the time-space around.

Countless light beams' courses deviated. Countless asteroids around him were penetrated and shattered by the light beams, turning into dust. Even the enormous asteroid under Han Xiao crumbled.

After the initial round of fire, the tens of thousands of meters area around Han Xiao became an empty space in the asteroid belt, while he remained unharmed. He was covered in an azure psionic energy shield that was rippling brightly, blocking all the stray attacks.

Seeing Sardeem's mechanical soldiers' barrels lighting up again, attempting to start the second round of fire, Han Xiao immediately entered the Void Dimension.

The next instant, he appeared behind Sardeem's army, slashing right toward Sardeem, who was protected by layers of defenses.

Surrounded by enemy mechanical soldiers in all directions, Han Xiao activated Apostilization. The psionic energy around him overflowed, shooting and spraying Psionic Impacts like they were infinite. He penetrated tons of mechanical soldiers with ease, turning every mechanical soldier before him into scrap metal, breaking through the layers of defenses extremely quickly.

The Evolution Cube had made him much stronger. Only a tank Mechanic like him would dare to go so deep into the enemy army.

Suddenly, Han Xiao's vision was covered in darkness. A several-hundred-meter-tall Giant Soldier stood in his path, covered in spaceship grade shields and equipped with more than a thousand artillery cannons.

The gigantic mechanical palm slammed down like a mountain.

Without even dodging, Han Xiao raised his hand and stopped this slam head-on. His size was like an ant compared to the Giant Soldier, but as his mechanical suit thruster operated at its maximum power output, he was not blown away. Han Xiao's fingers lodged into the Giant Soldier's palm, and he hung from it.

The Giant Soldier clenched its fist immediately. However, the next moment, countless tiny cracks appeared on the Giant Soldier's palm and spread over his entire palm. Dark blue light shone from within the cracks. Before the Giant Soldier could react, the entire arm was blasted into pieces by the psionic energy that Han Xiao had injected!

Countless parts were blown away by the impact, toppling the mechanical soldiers around.

With [Energy Enhancement Aura (Cosmetic)], the lighting effects looked very dazzling and colorful—despite not having any actual bonus, it looked cool.

After crushing this Giant Soldier that blocked the way, Han Xiao's legs stomped in the air as he accelerated in an instant, shattering the machinery in his path and heading right toward Sardeem, who was in the middle.

"He's too strong." Covered in sweat, Sardeem hastily deployed more troops to stop Han Xiao.

At this moment, the Black Star mechanical army on the other side finally clashed with Sardeem's army.

The difference between them was clearly visible—Han Xiao's mechanical army was black, and Sardeem's was red. At this time, the black side formed a comb-shaped formation and penetrated right into the red side's formation, stirring up their formation.

Then, like an unstoppable train, the black side pushed the red side into the asteroid belt not far away. The formations of both sides were shattered, and it became a chaotic brawl.

Millions of light beams flashed every second, quickly shrinking the size of the asteroid belt. The area was illuminated by blinding lights.

Countless mechanical soldiers were destroyed on both sides every second, turning into scrap metal floating in the universe.

In the midst of all this, Han Xiao did not forget about Virtual Intrusion. More and more of Sardeem's troops started to switch sides.

As a Giant Soldier shattered a team of Black Star mechanical troops, it suddenly turned and punched right through the head of another Giant Soldier.

The troops sent to stop Han Xiao became vanguards that opened the way for him. Han Xiao was initially advancing alone, but he suddenly gained a few thousand 'traitors' to protect him.

Sardeem was on edge and had no choice but to keep backing away. He could still fight to a certain extent with his army in his hands and might even be able to escape, but once Black Star got too close, it would be the end of him.

Authentic Army Style users would not be afraid of the enemy rushing through the layers of defenses, since it would be suicide for a normal Mechanic to use the tactic that Han Xiao was using. However, Sardeem did not think that he would be able to penetrate Black Star's defenses. With so many prior cases, everyone knew how terrifying the 'Indestructible Body' was. He did not want to be the next case.

...

As the intense battle carried on in the asteroid belt, the entire asteroid belt was reduced to dust.

After lasting for so long, Sardeem finally had nowhere to back away to. He was caught by Han Xiao from behind.

The defense measures around him were shattered by Han Xiao, and the troops around were all occupied by Han Xiao's mechanical army. All Sardeem had was this Giant Soldier that he was controlling manually. He had no choice but to fight Han Xiao in it.

Both of them had the ability to Apostilize. Psionic energy clashed time after time, spreading out like impact waves. Every punch that Han Xiao landed on the Giant Soldier shattered a large area of its exterior armor. Sardeem could only run around. He was no match for Han Xiao at all.

In terms of the Army Style, Han Xiao had more machines. In terms of personal strength, Han Xiao was stronger. Plus, he had just received a chunk of attributes from the Evolution Cube, so their differences were even larger. It was completely one sided. Han Xiao chased after Sardeem and tore his Giant Soldier apart piece by piece.

The exterior armor of the Giant Soldier was finally shattered. Han Xiao dashed inside the Giant Soldier, grabbed Sardeem, and used Mountain Ape Throw to throw him right out of the Giant Soldier, leaving a trail of shattered parts behind.

The next moment, Han Xiao instantly accelerated and caught up with Sardeem, who was still tumbling. Mechanical Force covered his entire body, and his fist was instantly enhanced by [Gene Liberation], [Legendary Battle Technique], [Overload], [Mechanical Force Overload], [Lethal Critical Hits], and all sorts of explosive abilities!

Bang!

His punch penetrated the armor and landed heavily on Sardeem's abdomen. Like a drum, his organs made a thunderous sound within his body, making his ears ring.

Having taken the True Damage of this punch, as a paper Mechanic, Sardeem entered the Stunned state instantly.

Before Sardeem bent his body in agony, his chin was grabbed by a large hand, shattering his helmet. The fingers grabbing onto his skull started to tighten.

"D—do—don't—" Sardeem felt like his head was going to explode. He quickly begged for mercy, but in space, no one could hear his scream.

Han Xiao tilted his head. An air bubble popped out from his shoulder and shrouded the two of them. He then opened his helmet and said, "You've lost. You don't want to die, do you?"

"Don't kill me!" Sardeem hastily yelled. He was not stupid, so he was not going to use the Mechanic Empire's name as protection. The Mechanic Empire was countless miles away and would not go all the way there to avenge him even if he died. Furthermore, Black Star was not someone that would be intimidated; threatening him with Mechanic Empire's name would only anger him further.

Wimping is the right thing to do!

"Then tell your troops to stop." At this time, Sardeem's mechanical army was still fighting with his mechanical army.

With his life in Han Xiao's hands, Sardeem did not dare resist. He quickly stopped his troops.

The two mechanical armies stopped fighting quickly.

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. He smiled and said, "Give me authority over your troops."

Sardeem's expression changed drastically as he ground his teeth.

He was bleeding in his heart. Giving up the authority meant that he was gifting all these troops that he spent a very long time building to Black Star.

"Are you unwilling?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "I can get your troops all the same if I kill you. The only difference is that I'll have to waste a little bit of time. If you're willing to die, I really have no problem with it. In fact, after killing you, I can even take over your Planet Macipher. Tsk tsk, everything you've worked for will be mine. Is that what you want?"

"St—stop, I'll give you the authority." Sardeem's face was pale. He had no choice but to reluctantly give the authority of his army over to Han Xiao.

"Don't be so mad. At least you're still alive."

Han Xiao was content. He told Phillip to count the troops that he had just seized. He just had to rewrite the authority, and they would all be his.

Then, Han Xiao took out many electromagnetic cuffs and restrained Sardeem tightly.

He was not planning to kill Sardeem. After all, he was the Mechanic Empire's subordinate no matter what. Since Sardeem was the one that started this battle, taking his resources was just considered a small conflict. Even if Sardeem reported this to the Mechanic Empire... why would Manison ever concern himself with something so trivial? On the other hand, killing Sardeem was a different matter. Han Xiao did not want to attract the Mechanic Empire's attention at this time.

Nonetheless, he could not let Sardeem leave right away.

While filled with hatred, Sardeem was relieved. He had worried Han Xiao would kill him after getting the authority of his mechanical army, but it seemed that he was going to live.

"I have some things to ask you. If you cooperate, you can suffer less..." Han Xiao grabbed him. "By the way, this isn't personal."

Sardeem replied with an obedient attitude. "I will cooperate."

Seeing that Han Xiao was not going to kill him, Sardeem slowly regained his calm. He looked obedient on the surface, but he was actually resentful.

If he had fought Black Star on his base, Planet Macipher, he did not think that he would have lost.

However, that was meaningless. The only thing that Sardeem could rely on was Psyker, who was hurrying after them.

As long as Psyker arrived, he would be rescued. A Beyond Grade A would easily demolish a Calamity Grade; Black Star would be no match for Psyker.

Sardeem did not know the existence of the Evolution Cube. From the way he looked at it, Han Xiao did not know that Psyker was chasing after him.

Therefore, before that, he planned to stall Han Xiao and not resist.

Han Xiao glanced at Sardeem and saw right through him. Sardeem clearly felt that Psyker would save him and was looking forward to the Beyond Grade A arriving in a rainbow cloud.

That was good for him. It would save him some energy.

With this mechanical army, I have more to fight Psyker. I'm now at level 239. The promotion was indeed the right choice.

Chapter 759: Born!

One day later, a water droplet-shaped spaceship flew into the desolate universe belt from Planet Macipher. It had a unique appearance, like a translucent azure bubble. This ship belonged to Psyker.

Psyker could sense that the location of the Evolution Cube was still moving within the desolate universe belt. With his speed, he would catch up to the target in about ten hours.

Who intercepted my Evolution Cube?

More than ten hours earlier, the coordinates of the Evolution Cube had stopped moving for a while. During that period, he had lost contact with Sardeem. Psyker had sent many communication requests but to no avail.

It was clear that Sardeem had met the target and been defeated.

Psyker became more interested in this mysterious hijacker. Firstly, the fact that the target was able to defeat Sardeem meant that his strength was at the top of the Calamity Grades. Secondly, the target was very mysterious. He suddenly appeared, grabbed the Evolution Cube, and fled. This meant that the target somehow knew what the Evolution Cube looked like after it was shrunk down.

Based on these two factors, Psyker felt that this person might either be one of EsGod's subordinates, a third party that knew about EsGod's plans, or an opportunist that found out about this through some foresight ability. He felt that the latter two were more likely.

Since he defeated Sardeem, he should know that I'm chasing right after him, yet he's still fleeing. He knows that's the Evolution Cube, but he still doesn't plan to return it to me. Does he think that he can escape from my hands?

Psyker could not help but shake his head, creating a simple impression of this person.

Someone so greedy that he valued fortune more than his own life!

Does this person not know how strong Beyond Grade A Supers are?

Among the four Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring, the Dragon Emperor and he were the lowest profile ones. Could this person think that he was easy to mess with?

As the leader of a Star System civilization, Psyker had met countless strange people but rarely anyone so arrogant.

Of course, Psyker would not be angered because he had been underestimated. As the leader of a civilization, he had learned to maintain his cool a long time ago—he just found it laughable.

It had been a very long time since anyone underestimated him.

As Psyker's thoughts drifted away, he recalled that the last time he felt ashamed was hundreds of years ago.

At that time, the Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring had not been the same people as now. He had still been a teenager who followed his family's financial group to the mother planet of a Star Cluster civilization for business. However, because of his race, he had been despised and picked on by those arrogant Star Cluster civilization citizens.

It was not personal, just an advanced civilization looking down on a backward civilization. Yet, this made him feel more ashamed than if it was personal—looking down on the bloodline he was proud of had hurt his most fundamental dignity as a member of his race.

Psyker still motivated himself using that experience. That Star Cluster civilization had become the civilization that had no choice but to watch the Star Pupil Holy Race rise right under their noses because of the Arcane Church.

If not because he had acquired the Evolution Cube in those ruins, the Star Pupil Holy Race would not have become what it was.

As Psyker regained his focus, his eyes became firm.

He had to retrieve the Evolution Cube!

Only then would his race continue to be supported by the Arcane Church!

...

Central Galaxy, Abyss of Stars, the Federation of Light's Mother Planet, Supreme Court...

There was a circular stage. Dozens of holographic projections hovered above the stage. They were clearly separated into two sides, sitting opposite each other. On one side were the Elder Representatives of the Federation of Light, and on the other side were the Dynasty Emissaries led by the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Ambassador.

The two sides had been in this meeting for two consecutive days. In the past decade, similar meetings had happened close to a hundred times, all for one topic, but it had never come to a conclusion.

This time, it was different.

"So, on behalf of the Federation of Light, I hereby announce the final conclusion of this meeting. This meeting has now ended." The leader of the Elder Representatives of the Federation of Light drew half a full stop to this meeting that had lasted an entire decade.

The Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Ambassador nodded firmly with an expressionless face.

As the topic involved the ownership of an enormous Star Field, the two sides negotiated for a decade. Diplomatic means were just supportive methods; the real source of their chips came from the countless threats, resource bribes, political pressure, deterrence from Beyond Grade A Supers, and many other means in the past ten years.

After single-handedly creating the Crimson Tide that brought chaos to more than ten Star Fields for an entire decade, the Crimson Dynasty finally obtained their fruit of victory today. The two sides had come to an agreement that both were satisfied with. The Federation of Light had compromised.

This time, the leader of the Federation of Light Elder Representatives suddenly spoke.

"What is the Crimson Dynasty going to name this new Star Field?"

With a tone filled with pride, the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Ambassador replied, "We thought of the name long ago. This new Star Field that's going to be included in the Dynasty's territory will be called the Flickering World!"

...

Inside the enormous Purple Crystal satellite fortress, the Section Zero alliance was resting after a bloody battle. Damaged battleships were sent into the military factory for repairs one after another. The soldiers of the various forces wasted no time before resting and enjoying the help from their logistics departments.

The privileges and treatment of the Black Star Army warriors who returned to their exclusive supply station were clearly much better than the other organizations. The NPCs were mixed with the players as they claimed their resources and repaired their equipment.

The fortress was extremely crowded.

Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the others squeezed into the queue, sent their equipment for repairs, and then squeezed themselves out. Due to how crowded the place was, they even lost a little bit of health while they were pushed around in the crowd.

"What are you guys going to do later?" Frenzied Sword asked.

"The Knowledges in the faction store have been discounted recently, so I'm planning to learn a few," Maple Moon said.

Hao Tian nodded, hinting that he was going to do the same.

Frenzied Sword then looked at Bun-Hit-Dog, only to realize that he looked very down. He could not help but ask, "What's going on? Why are you so down?"

Bun-Hit-Dog sighed. "We fought so long on the frontlines of the secret war that our Mission Rating has increased so many levels, but why hasn't Black Star come to join the battle recently? I'm lacking material."

Maple Moon began to wonder as well. "I wonder, too. The battle has been so intense. The high-level combatants of the Bloodshed Land have been rampant in the past few months. I always get killed by their AOEs. If only the captain was here..."

Li Ge suddenly appeared and said, "I agree."

Where did you come from?

Hao Tian pressed Li Ge right back into the crowd.

Frenzied Sword returned to the topic. "Maybe this is so that we can do more missions. Think about it. If Black Star was here, would we have so many battle opportunities? We might just end up watching cutscenes every day.

Bun-Hit-Dog was enraged. "Cutscenes are exactly what I want. Where else am I going to get material?"

The others shook their heads with resignation.

Frenzied Sword and the others were not alone. Countless army players were wondering about this as well.

As the leader of their faction, Black Star did not participate in the secret war, nor had he sent any messages in the past few months. It was like he went missing.

Where did Black Star go?

...

"To my knowledge, Black Star has been missing for a few months and did not take part in the war during this time. As Purple Crystal lost Black Star's help, our high-level combatants were able to achieve rather good results..."

On Planet Heber, Staff Sergeant Jorde was reporting to the Tyrant.

Heber sat on his throne like a tiny mountain and listened to Jorde's report in silence, occasionally nodding.

Jorde continued with excitement. "New information arrived from Klent earlier. Not long ago, the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light finally came to an agreement. The handover process is going to take a few months. Only then will the Crimson Dynasty deal with the issues regarding their allies. The time it will take for them to start dealing with the secret war between Klent and Purple Crystal should be about half a year..."

"Oh?" Heber's tone rose.

"This means that the secret war will only last half a year longer, which is shorter than we expected." Jorde was exhilarated. "We still have control of West Wind, Kaya, Chaida, and the border Star Systems. In half a year, Purple Crystal will not be able to regain control of them. Your Excellency Tyrant, this means that we've won!"

"Not bad..."

Heber nodded slowly. He then suddenly asked, "How's Black Star doing?"

"After he fell into my trap, he went missing for months, I don't know where he is now." Jorde rubbed his chin. "However, he may know about the agreement that the Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light have made, so I think he should now be planning his escape."

"Planning his escape?"

"Yes. Black Star must know what situation he's in. He knows that he is definitely no match for you. I think that he might escape from the Shattered Star Ring."

Heber shook his head. "He's not that kind of gutless coward... Hmm, maybe he will seek help from the Dragon Emperor or the Purple Crystal civilization to stop me."

Jorde nodded.

"No matter what, I can't let people think that there isn't a price for killing so many of my subordinates," Heber said slowly. "Klent got what they want, and I need to make an example out of someone."

...

In the Palace of Hidden Spells, Austin sat with his legs crossed in midair and explained Magic theories. He was surrounded by Mages of all races who were carefully listening to the Magus' teachings.

"Therefore, it can be seen from the mistakes in the third, seventh, and nineteenth circuits that the question asked by the Beyond Grade A 'Holy Sorcerer' Mapier hundreds of years ago is flawed. That'll be all for today."

The mages bowed and swamped out. Very soon, the hall became empty, leaving only Austin.

Austin took a deep breath. He took out his communicator from his secondary dimensional pocket and browsed through the news that he had missed.

"This is all entertainment news. Tsk, this female celebrity looks quite nice. What's her na... Ahem, the situation in the Primeval Star River is still horrible... Hmm, more civilization ruins discovered in the Ancient Star Desert... Sigh, horrible stuff... Hmm? The Crimson Dynasty and the Federation of Light have come to an agreement?"

Austin was surprised. He was reminded of the situation of the secret war and his reminder for Han Xiao a few months ago.

Austin rubbed his tender chin with his tiny hand.

"The secret war is about to end. The show is finally going to start. I wonder what choice Black Star made. I hope he doesn't disappoint me..."

...

Outside the Shattered Star Ring, Han Xiao took Sardeem and landed on a desolate planet. This was an extremely hot planet. Its ground was covered in cracks filled with lava, volcanoes erupted all the time, and the planet surface was filled with tons of lava lakes and rivers.

"This is it." Han Xiao nodded in his mind.

It had been a day since he captured Sardeem. He had already obtained intelligence from Sardeem and confirmed his speculation that Psyker could locate the Evolution Cube.

Hence, Han Xiao decided to choose the battlefield and wait for Psyker, who was about to arrive.

Phillip counted Sardeem's army. After losing a few hundred thousand mechanical soldiers in their battle, Han Xiao had seized more than two million troops, which increased his chances.

Of course, his confidence did not mostly come from that machinery.

A few hours ago, the experience from the players had finally filled up the experience bar of level 240!

He landed on this planet to complete his level 240 Promotion that he had been looking forward to for a very long time.

Han Xiao suppressed his excitement, turned around, and gave an order to the mechanical troops that restrained Sardeem.

"Keep him under control. Don't let him go anywhere."

"Roger," the artificial intelligence Sparta replied coldly. It then controlled the many machines to all aim at Sardeem, ready to fire as soon as Sardeem did anything strange.

"Hmm!" Sardeem was tied up by electromagnetic chains all over his body, and even his mouth was sealed. The Super-Gene in his body was dried out by Han Xiao temporarily as well. He was extremely weak and could not move at all. All he could do was whine through his throat.

Leaving Sardeem behind, Han Xiao flew off alone. He crossed more than a thousand miles and randomly entered a crack on the surface.

He deactivated his mechanical suit and moved within the lava with his body. With his talent [Cosmic Environmental Adaptation], he was resistant to all kinds of harsh environments. The thousand-degree lava was no different to him than a shower.

"I wonder when I will be able to shower with Fixed Stars like the Tyrant... Wait a minute, why am I comparing myself with a Pugilist?"

Very soon, Han Xiao crossed the underground lava river and entered an empty space thousands of meters under the surface.

"This place should be secretive enough. The impact wave won't be able to leave here very easily."

Han Xiao was rather satisfied with this place.

Looking down at his muscular body, the runes drawn by Lagi made his body look as exquisite as a piece of art.

"Tsk, amazing... sigh, I've used the Evolution Cube, I wonder if I'll become a monster like Psyker after becoming a Beyond Grade A."

Han Xiao took off the Evolution Cube and slapped it into the wall. He rubbed his hands and opened the interface.

"Come on!"

After taking a deep breath, Han Xiao put all the experience into leveling up.

Straight toward level 240!

...

On Floating Dragon Island, Ames walked down the corridor of the palace with her long legs and feather-looking dress. By her side were Aesop and Vilna.

"Haven't found them yet?" Ames said with an unsatisfied tone.

"No..." Vilna replied.

"Damn Black Star, where did he take my students!" Ames was enraged.

When Hila and Aurora finished their training with her a few months ago, she had originally planned to send people to protect them secretly. However, in the last few months, Black Star and the two sisters had gone missing together. She could not find them at all.

"You're too worried. There's absolutely no need. Black Star won't harm the two of them," Aesop said with resignation.

"Hmm? You think I'm an irresponsible teacher like you?" Ames raised her brows.

So much hatred... Aesop wiped off the cold sweat on his forehead.

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, if you want to know where the sisters are, why don't you let me ask Black Star directly?" Vilna could not help but ask that.

Ames gave her a glare and said, "If I have to go to Black Star for everything, why did I create your team?"

Vilna had no words and could only lower her head.

It was actually created by Black Star... Aesop shook his head in resignation. Nonetheless, he agreed with Ames—Floating Dragon had to have their own intelligence channels. After all, Black Star might leave any day.

At this time, Aesop suddenly stopped.

Ames and Vilna only noticed that Aesop had been left behind after walking a few more steps. The two of them turned around only to notice that Aesop had closed his eyes and was frowning.

"What did you see?" Ames asked curiously. Aesop's Esper Ability would occasionally activate automatically to give him some foresight.

Aesop suddenly opened his eyes. His face was filled with shock.

"The fifth Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring... is born!"

Chapter 760: Exclusive Race!

[Emperor Mechanic] levelled up to Lv.15.

+300 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +8 END, +12 INT.

You have received 10 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

Boom!

When his level reached level 240, a powerful surge of energy exploded within Han Xiao's body. The electric Mechanical Force violently left burn marks on the floor and walls like a thunderstorm.

The level 240 Promotion Mission appeared. Han Xiao glanced at it. It was not difficult, but he was not going to stop now. He had two more Mission Completion Cards, so he directly used one of them to complete the Promotion Mission.

Level 240 Promotion Mission completed!

Promotion successful!

END Bonus increased! 1 END = 210 Health = 220 Stamina.

From level 60, a Race Evolution would occur every 40 levels. The last Race Evolution was at level 220, so level 240 would usually be a normal Promotion. However, with the benefits that he had received from the Evolution Cube, he received a bonus Race Evolution chance.

The [Gene Optimization—Evolution Cube] effect has been triggered.

You have received a bonus Race Evolution.

You have taken another step on the path of evolution. You have ascended in the hierarchy of life. Your genes have reformed... Under the influence of the Evolution Cube, the chances of Mutation Option appearing in this Race Evolution have increased.

Race Detected: [Void Star Pursuer (Human Form)]

Randomly drawing 9 matching evolutionary directions...

Drawing complete!

Please choose one of the following 10 options for your Race Evolution. Warning! The evolution process is irreversible. Please choose carefully! [Appendix—Evolution Path Feature Descriptions]

[Void Commander (Human Form)]—66% Compatibility

[Void Devourer (Mutated Form)]—42% Compatibility

[Void Ripper (Mutated Form)]—38% Compatibility

[Thunder Element Tyrant (Energy Form)]—17% Compatibility

[New Edge Mechanical Race (Human Form)]—58% Compatibility

[Void Silencer (Human Form)]—49% Compatibility

[Chaos Demon]—27% Compatibility

[Void Pathfinder (Human Form)]—72% Compatibility

[Chaos Secret Sorcerer (Energy Form)]—35% Compatibility

[Child of Star Core (Physical Form)]—9.7% Compatibility

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

The influence of the Evolution Cube was obvious—there were quite many mutated options in the ten options. This was probably how Psyker went through atavism.

As for the options related to the Void Race, the two Mutated Form options were out of the question. [Void Silencer] and [Chaos Secret Sorcerer] were more suitable for Mages. His best option was [Void Pathfinder], which was the next stage of his current race. [Void Commander] was the path toward Void Lord.

The other mutated options were quite good as well. Mechanical Race was the bloodline left behind by a Beyond Grade A Mechanic among the Primordial Ones. Becoming a Beyond Grade A meant becoming a one and only being in the universe, but reproduction was still possible. Beyond Grade As had very long lives, so there would be more than enough time for them to pass down their race. That Mechanic Primordial One had long passed away, but the Mechanical Race still lived in the universe. As the name suggested, they were born Mechanics.

Manison of the Mechanic Empire was the leader of the Mechanical Race. He was the second Beyond Grade A of this race.

[Child of Star Core] was also a very talented species. They were born in the cores of stars.

After some contemplating, Han Xiao selected [Void Pathfinder]. Although the Mechanical Race was very suitable for Mechanics, their potential was not as vast as that of the Void Race. Since he was so far down this path, unless he encountered an extremely powerful option, he would not easily change his path.

Selection complete. Undergoing Race Evolution... Evolution complete.

Your race has been changed to: [Void Pathfinder (Human Form)]. Molecular structure is improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed, and adaptability enhanced... Your potential aptitude has been improved!

+130 STR, +180 DEX, +317 END, +169 INT, +169 MYS, +73 CHA, +3180 Energy.

Energy Level bonus attributes have been changed!

The original five talents did not disappear, but [Void Molt] was enhanced into [Void Blessing]. The increase in its effect was about twenty-five percent.

Also, he received a new talent—[Void Path]!

As the name suggested, this was the upgraded version of Void Distortion, which allowed him to directly open the gate of the Void Dimension. This was also how the name [Void Pathfinder] came about.

Opening the Void Dimension had many uses. He could throw the enemies' attacks inside like trash, or he could send the enemies into the Void Dimension. He could even connect to a certain area within the Void Dimension and let the beings in there out into the world.

The only flaw was its long cooldown, or he could just hide his mechanical army in it. In terms of bringing his mechanical army along with him, the unactivated [Secondary Dimension Army] was still a better choice.

Maybe because he followed the direct evolution path, Han Xiao did not feel too much pain this time. This time, a notification that made him exhilarated finally popped up on the interface.

You have satisfied the Prior Requirement: Achieving >32759.1 Ona after Promotion.

Race Mutation activated!

At this instant, the pain level in his body suddenly shot through the roof. Han Xiao's expression became twisted. It was as if someone kept pumping air into his body and his body could explode at any moment.

"Race Mutation... this is it!" Han Xiao clenched his teeth and held on as he stared at the interface.

This was the true evolution toward Beyond Grade A!

You have reached the peak of the hierarchy of life. You have found your own direction on the path of evolution. You're going to undergo changes you have never experienced before. From this day forth, you are going to become a unique being like no other in the entire universe...

Detecting evolution path... complete.

Your evolution have gone through [Carbon Based Human (Yellow)], [Type I Spacehuman], [Void Prowler (Human Form)], [Void Observer (Human Form)], [Void Distorter (Human Form)], [Void Star Pursuer (Human Form)], and [Void Pathfinder (Human Form)]...

Please select 10 from the Racial Talents below...

The choices were all Racial Talents that he had once possessed. Some had disappeared, but they had now all become available choices.

This exclusive race would gather the essence of his previous evolutions, Han Xiao realized.

As he had taken the Void Race path, he had no need for some duplicate talents, so the choices were easy. Firstly, he kept the six strongest talents of [Void Pathfinder]. Then, he selected two talents from [Void Observer]—[Void Vision—Observer] and [Observer's Mark]. He had missed these two abilities for a very long time, and he could finally regain them!

For the remaining two, he selected [Chaos Entity—Release] and [Adaptability]. The latter was the jack of all trades talent of the Galaxy Human Race, which gave a ten percent bonus to all resistances, including Psychic Resistance. He had selected this with Psyker's threat in mind.

After confirming the choices, a new notification popped up on the interface.

Please select 2 from the 5 Race Evolution choices below and receive one talent from each.

[Chaos Apostle (Human Form)]

[Void Destroyed (Mutated Form)]

[Void Preacher (Spiritual Form)]

[Advanced Ethereal Race]

[Saint—Galaxy Beast Race]

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The previous ten talents were all from the previous evolutions, but these two would be from the next stage of the evolution.

As he would become a unique race after becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, the following Race Evolutions would only enhance his exclusive race and grant him the talents of other races.

Absorbing talents had nothing to do with compatibility as he would not go through any mutation.

Enduring the immerse pain in his body, Han Xiao hesitated for a while and chose [Chaos Apostle] and [Void Preacher]. The former was to maintain his [Void Pathfinder] evolution path and the latter was because it was a Spiritual Form. Han Xiao felt that it would increase his Psychological Resistance, which would help him in dealing with Psyker.

The talents of these two races appeared on the interface. Han Xiao browsed through and made his choice.

You have received the talent [Void Ethereal Echo].

You have received the talent [Supreme Piety].

[Void Ethereal Echo] came from [Chaos Apostle], which could be used for many purposes such as applying debuffs to the enemy, restricting the enemy's movement, defending, or attacking. It could only be used for one purpose at a time and had a cooldown of five minutes.

[Supreme Piety] was one of the [Void Preacher]'s talents. It gave a ninety percent Psychological Resistance increase and immunity to all kinds of deceptive psychic attacks, as well as a twenty percent chance to reflect psychic attacks.

"Okay, I now stand an even better chance against Psyker."

Han Xiao was very pleasantly surprised. This single talent gave more bonus than all the Psychological Resistance talents that he previously had.

This time, a new notification popped up on the interface again.

Please select your preference for the exclusive Racial Talent.

This was referring to the thirteenth talent of this Race Mutation, which was the special talent of his exclusive race. It was no longer a talent from another race but creating his own talent.

This special talent would be the race talent to be passed down to his descendants.

The choices were attack, defense, resistance, health points, Machinery Affinity, and many others. The special talent would decide the direction of his exclusive race's development, and there was only one chance to choose it. Han Xiao did not dare take the matter lightly, so he selected the Mechanic preference.

Preference selected. Creating unique talent...

You have three chances to recreate. Your choice cannot be canceled after confirmation.

Creation complete.

[Natural Mechanical Senses]: +180% Machinery Affinity, +2 levels to all Mechanic type abilities, not limited to maximum ability level.

[Confirm/Recreate]

Han Xiao shook his head. This talent was rather ordinary, so he used one recreation chance.

Creating... Creation complete.

[Source of Mechanical Force]: When your Energy Attribute is Mechanical Force, receive 50 bonus Energy every level.

[Confirm/Recreate]

This was not bad. If he selected this talent, he would gain 12,000 bonus Energy, which would most likely increase his Energy Level another level.

It was almost impossible to create a Molding Talent level ability, so [Source of Mechanical Force] was not bad at all.

He had two more recreation chances. Feidin was not around, so Han Xiao felt very insecure.

One more time. The exclusive talent of a Beyond Grade A won't be too horrible no matter what... I think.

After making up his mind, Han Xiao clenched his teeth and used another recreation chance.

Creating... Creation complete.

[Mechanical Genius]: Total Machinery Affinity * 1.15, +30% Machinery Creation Performance.

Yo, this is what I'm talking about!

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

With this 1.15 multiplier to his total Machinery Affinity and the 1.08 multiplier of [Basic Mechanical Sense], it would give more than half the bonus of Reynold's Molding Talent [Perfect Mechanical Sense], which was decent.

Furthermore, the thirty percent performance increase in his machinery creation was the most valuable bonus. The machinery that he created would have higher attributes. The thirty percent increase would make his mechanical army much stronger.

He would definitely have to create a new mechanical army suitable for Beyond Grade A battles afterward, so this ability would come in handy.

"This is it!"

Han Xiao did not use the last recreation chance and selected 'Confirm' immediately.

You have received Exclusive Talent [Mechanical Genius]!

Tip: The effects of the Exclusive Talent will increase along with Race Evolution.

The 13 talents have been confirmed.

Exclusive Race created.

Please select a name...

As the first being of this race, Han Xiao could name it.

"What race should I be called? Void Mechanical Race? Commercial Genius Race? A Pugilist That Doesn't Want to Be an Esper Isn't a Good Mechanic Race?"

The agony from evolving continued. Han Xiao decided not to waste time thinking of a name and used his own name.

He still recalled that the underground mutants that he had saved back then were called the Black Spirit Race, so using his own name would not be a problem.

Exclusive Race Name confirmed.

Your race has become: Black Star Race

Detecting Race Appearance...

Based on your evolution experience, you can change your appearance to up to 2.7%.

As Han Xiao had maintained his human form all along, he could not change his appearance much, nor did he want to, so he decided to keep his original appearance.

Molecular structure is improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed...

According to the preference of the Black Star Race, you have received bonus attributes.

+367 STR, +317 DEX, +534 END, +881 INT, +380 MYS, +249 CHA, +5600 Energy.

Energy Level bonus attributes have been changed!

[Race Mutation] Completed. Your Grade has increased to S.

+100 END Bonus! 1 END = 310 Health = 320 Stamina

33,000 Energy was the triggering point of Race Mutation. Beyond it was the territory of Beyond Grade A.

Grade A Grade Bonuses disappeared.

You have received Grade S Bonuses.

Grade S Bonuses: +50 END, +25 All Resistances. +25% Highest Attribute , +15% Other Attributes, +750 Free Attribute Points, +50 Potential Points

Please select 2 from the 7 options below as Grade Talents.

Han Xiao clenched his fists in excitement. Just like how he received [Superhuman] when he became a Calamity Grade Super, Grade Ss had their own talents as well, which was also the main reason they were so much stronger than Calamity Grades.

Physical Resistance

Psychological Resistance

Power Bonus

Status Enhancement

Health

Explosive Power

Energy

Han Xiao focused and pondered. Power Bonus was a must. It would enhance everything just like [Superhuman], including Mechanical Force enhancement. This was the source of the destructive power of Beyond Grade As.

What he had a hard time choosing was the second option—he could not decide between Psychological Resistance and Health.

Psychological Resistance would be great against Psyker, but so would health. Furthermore, health would be more viable. He had yet to forget his two other enemies that did not use psychic attacks, EsGod and the Tyrant.

"Is taking beatings my fate?" With complicated feelings, Han Xiao sighed and made his choice.

You have received Grade Talent [Supreme Power]!

You have received Grade Talent [Eternal Body]!

[Supreme Power]: You have gained power exceeding the Calamity Grade. The energy in the universe is yours to control. Your ability strength has increased, including but not limited to all weapons, equipment, machinery, and other combat means controlled by you. Bonus depends on Total Level.

Lv1 – Lv100: +4% attack every 10 levels; Lv100 – Lv200: +6% attack every 10 levels; Lv200 and above: +10% attack every 10 levels]

Current Bonus: 140% (This can be stacked with [Superhuman] bonuses)

[Eternal Body]: The life span of your cells is very long-lasting.

+1 END Bonus every 2 levels.

Current Bonus: +120 END Bonus

"The enhancement brought by these two talents is... horrifying!"

Han Xiao was stunned.

No wonder Beyond Grade As were so powerful!

The agony became even more apparent and violent. Han Xiao focused on feeling the changes in his body.

Just as Austin had said, after he became a Beyond Grade A, the Soul Embryo in his mind disappeared instantly, directly destroyed by his Beyond Grade A mind.

The chain of debuffs brought by it on his interface disappeared all at once. He had returned to his peak state.

The pain finally faded after a few hours, taken over by the continuously expanding sense of power. It felt clearer and stronger than ever before. His sense of the world had never been this sharp.

The energy in his body overflowed from his every pore. His body was covered in dark blue light.

"I've finally succeeded!"

Han Xiao was ecstatic. From that day, he would be a Beyond Grade A standing at the top of Galaxy!

Calming himself down, Han Xiao distributed his Free Attribute Point evenly between Intelligence and Endurance, then looked at his attributes.

Despite being mentally prepared, he was still shocked by the numbers on his interface after he became a Beyond Grade A.

Level: 240

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star Race

Attributes: 2,346 STR, 2,930 DEX, 4,265 END, 6,672 INT, 2,108 MYS, 986 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Points: 84

Health: 2,533,510

Stamina: 2,487,270

Energy: 52,270 [Lv.15]

Lv.15 Energy bonus stat: +671 STR, +848 DEX, +1080 END, +1305 INT, +653 MYS, +141,520 Stamina Limit, +952% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 43,837

Grade: S (Beyond A)

Grade S Bonuses: +50 END, +25 All Resistances. +25% Highest Attribute , +15% Other Attributes, +750 Free Attribute Points, +50 Potential Points

Remark: Beyond Grade As are far more powerful than Calamity Grades. No matter which Star Field it is, you stand at the peak of it.

"Way too powerful..." Han Xiao's eyes widened with excitement.

Becoming a Beyond Grade A made him way stronger than Calamity Grade. He was in completely new territory.

With these attributes, no wonder no Calamity Grade could ever match a Beyond Grade A. Even he could not have beaten a Beyond Grade A before this. It was just like how a human would never be able to beat Godzilla with their bare hands.

Even he had more than 2.5 million health, so he wondered how much Tyrant had.

If those Primordial Ones never penetrated this limit, maybe the current universe would still have thought that Calamity Grades were the limit of individual strength.

"This is the power of a Beyond Grade A..."

Han Xiao felt the changes in his body. He felt like he could punch right through this planet under his feet.

And this time, it was not an illusion!

Beep beep!

Before he could test the limits of his power, Phillip suddenly sent a message.

"Master, hum... the radar has detected a spaceship in the outer atmosphere, hum!"

Han Xiao looked up immediately. As if his sights could penetrate the thick rock walls, his eyes locked onto a water droplet shaped spaceship outside the planet.

"Psyker? He's finally caught up..."

Han Xiao's eyes became firm.

This was the perfect opportunity. He could test out how strong he was among Beyond Grade As in the battle with Psyker!

Chapter 761: Negotiations

The waterdrop-shaped spaceship slowly entered the atmosphere and descended. The scene of fire and cracked lava jumped into Psyker's sight.

Psyker had already sensed the position of the Evolution Cube just below the planet, so close that he could accurately sense its position now.

"The coordinates have stopped at this planet for a few hours now... Did he give up on the Evolution Cube and choose to escape, or did he purposely stay here just to meet with me?"

Psyker tried to guess the intentions of his unknown enemy and felt that the person might have set traps for him, causing him to be unable to continue pursuing him. As a precaution, he gave up the thought of flying down using just his fleshly body, instead flying over to the coordinates he detected in his spaceship.

After flying for a while, the detection radar suddenly pinged as it had spotted a life signal hundreds of kilometers away. The distant area was expanded, and it could be discerned that there were hundreds of Mechanical Warriors around a living body, as though keeping it in captivity.

"That looks like Sardeem." Psyker's expression grew grim, and he immediately flew over to Sardeem.

The troops on the ground raised their muzzles, opening fire at the spaceship overhead.

Boom boom boom!

A surge of invisible mental power formed a shield, distorting the space like a wall of air. The Particle Cannon blasted shattered into blue specks of light upon hitting them.

Explosions continued to move, but the shield remained motionless.

The next instant, a pale white mental shock wave materialized, sweeping across the ground.

Swoosh!

The hundreds of Mechanical soldiers below did not possess the bonuses of Mechanical Force and were naturally shattered in a single blow. The mental wave avoided Sardeem, and he was the only one left standing after the shockwave had passed.

The Psychic profession was the profession specializing in mental strength. Its strength lay in its mental attacks, and at the same time, it possessed the means to perform physical attacks. The driving force behind this was using one's mental strength to affect the surroundings in order to generate the physical attack.

Psyker crushed the restraints on Sardeem's body with his mind before beaming him up into the cabin.

"Cough cough... you're finally here!"

Sardeem held onto the cabin door weakly with an expression of joy.

He was saved!

A Beyond Grade A Super was so reliable. Believing in Psyker was the correct thing to do!

"Who's the enemy?" Psyker did not waste time talking, going straight into the main topic.

"It... it's Black Star!"

"Black Star? I've heard this name before... oh, it seems like someone from the Colton Star Cluster. He took part in the secret war and ended up provoking Tyrant."

"Yes, yes, yes, it's that Beyond Grade A Seed. He claimed to be invincible among Calamity Grades."

Invincible among Calamity Grades? So, is it his moniker that gave him the confidence to go against a Beyond Grade A?

Psyker shook his head. The Colton Star Cluster was far away from his Star Pupil Holy Race, and while news about Han Xiao had passed through him, he did not pay attention to him. To him, a simple Calamity Grade was just an ant no matter how famous he was.

He had no interest in the secret war. If he had the time, he would have spent it worrying about the fertility problem of the Star Pupil Holy Race.

"Your Excellency Psyker, Black Star threw me over here a few hours ago. He should still be on this planet. Just now, when you wiped out the mechanical soldiers, you revealed yourself. I believe we should hurry to capture Black Star, lest he runs away again."

Sardeem immediately raised that suggestion. He could not wait to see Black Star get into trouble.

He could not forget the humiliation that he had suffered and wished to take back his mechanical troops. Psyker was his backer, and in his eyes, a Calamity Grade would never be a match for a Beyond Grade A. No matter how Black Star struggled, he would only become a punching bag for Psyker.

Sardeem gritted his teeth, viciously thinking, I'm not only going to get back my mechanical army, I'm even going to steal yours!

"Oh, that makes sense. We should settle it quickly," Psyker said as though it was natural.

With his perception pointing the way, he was not afraid of Black Star running away but rather more afraid that if Black Star had nowhere left to run, he would smash the portable container of the Evolution Cube to pieces, revealing the true form of the Evolution Cube. In that case, he would have to gather all the manpower of his Star Pupil Holy Race to move the Evolution Cube back, and he hated such trouble.

Just as he was prepared to pilot his spaceship over, he felt the Evolution Cube in his perception begin to approach them. Very quickly, a tiny black dot grew ever larger toward their location.

Rumble!

The fast-moving shadow shot over the ground, raising up gales, and the magma flowing on the surface was split to the sides due to the wind pressure.

The next moment, the black shadow stopped in midair not far off, facing squarely with Psyker.

"That's Black Star!" Sardeem immediately pointed as he exclaimed.

"To think he came knocking on his own..." Psyker felt a little mystified. He roughly understood the intentions of the other party—to negotiate with him.

His gaze was fixed on the small Evolution Cube hanging from Han Xiao's neck. With his perception, he knew that this was the compact version of the Portable Evolution Cube.

Hum!

Without waiting for Han Xiao to open his mouth, Psyker raised his hand, and a blast of psychic power roiled out, hitting Han Xiao on a spiritual level.

He was too lazy to speak pleasantries to Han Xiao. He knew that the other party planned to use the Evolution Cube as his bargaining chip, but what qualifications did Han Xiao, as a Calamity Grade, have to speak on equal grounds with him?

Psyker was unwilling to give him the upper hand. Thus, without a single word, he attacked directly.

If you have anything to say, wait till I get the Evolution Cube!

Before Han Xiao could speak, a wave of mental energy struck at him. Fortunately, he had been mentally prepared to use his new talent [Void Dimension] from the [Chaos Apostle] race, drawing a large amount of power from the void to offset the psychic energies. The barrier he created diffused close to half the mental damage.

The remaining amount of psychic energy pierced through, invading his brain, and he felt pain in his mind as though countless nails were being hammered in. However, his talents such as [Supreme Piety], [Advanced Mental Toughness], and [Soul Lock] had more than doubled his mental resistance. This blow shaved off more than 80,000 of his overall HP, with the interface showing that Psyker had utilized his skills to deal extra damage.

This was the true strength of a Beyond Grade A Super!

However, with Han Xiao's current HP, this attack that was enough to destroy Calamity Grades did not even count as a light injury to him, and he recovered in the blink of an eye.

This jerk is really decisive! Han Xiao turned solemn.

However, this was what he wanted. Only by first showing his strength to the other party would he be qualified to negotiate on equal grounds.

While his thoughts moved, Han Xiao's hands did not slow down as well. Without a second word, he immediately applied the Luck Curse on Psyker, and without retreating, he activated [Apostilization] as well as [Void Blessing]. With an arrogant bearing, a sea of Psionic energy was launched, akin to a river of stars in a galaxy as it rushed toward Psyker's spaceship.

Boom!

The surge of Psionic energy violently smashed against Psyker's mind barrier, akin to a waterfall against a rock. The light blue colored sparkles resembled the splashing of water, and the surroundings vibrated endlessly, with roaring echoes.

"This strength... isn't quite right."

Psyker could not help but be surprised. The pressure withstood by his spirit was totally different from his original expectation of easily blocking the attack.

While there was only a bit of pressure, having been a Beyond Grade A for so many years, this was the first time that he had felt pressure coming from a Calamity Grade.

Clank!

The next instant, Han Xiao poured out more energy, summoning his Mechanical army. Flashes could be seen around the sky as the Army Boxes arrived one after another, releasing an overwhelming number of Mechanical troops. A black colored wave of soldiers occupied every inch of the sky.

Not only was Han Xiao's mechanical army there but Sardeem's too. The total scale was over ten million.

Buzz!

Mechanical Force resembling sparks of electricity rushed out from Han Xiao, connecting to each mechanical soldier like a ginormous lightning web. At this moment, all the Mechanical soldiers' actions were synchronized.

Han Xiao then released his full strength. The level of energy that he emitted sharply climbed, and his momentum continued to expand.

It was at this moment that Sardeem had a bad premonition in his heart.

Right on cue, Psyker opened his mouth.

"You're wrong."

Sardeem regained his senses and replied in confusion, "What's wrong?"

"You said he was a Beyond Grade A Seed. You're wrong."

Sardeem could not help but turn to Psyker, and to his shock, he found out that Psyker's expression was no longer easygoing. At some time, his expression had turned stern.

"He's not a Beyond Grade A Seed..." Psyker's tone was grave. "He's a true Beyond Grade A!"

Like a bolt of lightning blasting apart his mind, Sardeem's thoughts turned blank. His whole body stiffened, and his eyes slowly grew larger, as his expression turned from disbelieving to terrified.

Black Star... was a Beyond Grade A‽

This meant that the Shattered Star Ring now had five Beyond Grade A Supers‽

Sardeem's face was pale. If Han Xiao was still a Calamity Grade, he would have had no issues making him an enemy. However, the other party was now a Beyond Grade A. What sort of revenge would he dare perform?

When did this happen? Two days ago, when I was exchanging blows with him, he was still a Calamity Grade! Could it be that he purposely hid his strength?

Maybe, when he had disguised himself as Barne, he was already a Beyond Grade A.

Then, has he been fooling me all along‽

Seeing that he was so vocal about managing to have a contact with a Beyond Grade A, Sardeem now felt utterly speechless.

If Black Star and Psyker start fighting, the aftermath of a Beyond Grade A battle...

Sardeem now started to panic. He had thought that once Psyker arrived, he would be safe, but now it seems like he would die there!

At this time, the mechanical army surrounded Psyker's spaceship, and dense rows of muzzles aimed at him. At the same time, the dim glow of accumulating energy could be seen.

Hum!

Psyker's seven eyes immediately grew huge, and his psychic energy was poured out, weaving layer after layer of barriers that wrapped around the entire spaceship.

"Fire!" Han Xiao pressed down sharply with his palm.

Pew! Pew! Pew!

Millions of particle cannons were fired in unison toward the same target, and the next moment, the various psionic rays converged at a single point, triggering a chain reaction. At the center point, a dark-blue energy ball was formed and quickly expanded.

The Mechanical army retreated as this energy ball swelled to more than a hundred kilometers in diameter before exploding!

Boom!

The sound was akin to a mountain collapsing.

A dazzling blue beam shot up toward the sky, heading for the atmosphere.

Without dust nor a mushroom cloud, all the Psionic energy vanished as though it had never existed.

The area was transformed into a deep pit, with the land seemingly having vanished into thin air. This explosion almost blew through the crust of the planet, and the remaining power had penetrated the mantle, causing it to turn into a bottomless hole.

Rumble!

The veins in the surrounding thousands of kilometers had all been affected, with several earthquakes happening simultaneously. All the volcanoes in the area erupted, and the cracked ground produced countless deep rifts. The crust was shredded by the tectonic movements, and magma raged from the rifts, rising like red hot dragon ridges.

Seeing the extreme changes, Han Xiao could only sigh in appreciation.

Just how many times has my offensive strength multiplied?

His Attributes and Machinery Affinity had soared, and the bonuses given by [Supreme Prestige] allowed Han Xiao's strength to step into the realm of Beyond Grade A.

My Mechanical army has not yet been renewed. The moment I return and create a set of stronger machines, as well as a large number of Planetary Obliteration Cannons, that will be the peak of my combat capability.

Han Xiao settled his mind before turning around to look for traces of Psyker.

While the picture of devastation that he had wrought was shocking, Han Xiao never let his guard down. He would not expect such a blow to pose much of a threat to another Beyond Grade A. After all, the strong aftermath meant that his control of power was still not precise and concentrated.

Even with that huge explosion, the damage inflicted was only 250,000 HP. This was already inferred on his interface, and the majority of his attacks were stopped by the Beyond Grade A Psychic mental barrier.

In the epicenter of the explosion, there was a cracked light sphere, red in color. That was the psychic barrier of Psyker. Even his mental and psychic energies had been superheated by the Psionic blast, turning into lava red and constantly emitting steam.

The mechanical army gathered once again, and upon seeing this, Psyker glanced at Sardeem, who was trembling beside him, and shook his head.

After staying silent for a while, he dissipated his mental barrier, opened the hatch, and flew out, facing Han Xiao.

"Good strength."

Psyker first lowered his head to start at the bottomless pit before turning back to face Han Xiao. He did not reveal any emotions on his face as he said, "Let's talk."

After this simple exchange, Psyker understood that the other party was on the same level as him. Thus, he could only change his attitude and acknowledge that Han Xiao was qualified for equal conversation.

While he had never made any contact with Black Star before, he would have no choice but to remember this person in the future.

Making this gesture also showed that he was ready to negotiate with Han Xiao.

In fact, Psyker was a little pissed. He had originally thought that his opponent was just a Calamity Grade that was too full of himself, but it turned out to be a real Beyond Grade A Super. The worst-case scenario actually happened, and this made the situation even more complicated.

Psyker was not afraid of Han Xiao, but as the leader of a civilization, he was not willing to easily provoke a new Beyond Grade A as his enemy unless there was no hope of negotiating.

As the saying went, whenever talented people emerged, they would leave their mark on the world. Every new Beyond Grade A expert signified some sort of change in the Star Field. While the Shattered Star Ring had not had a new Beyond Grade A expert for a long time, it did not mean that the same went for many of the other Star Fields.

With Psyker's long lifespan, alongside with his contacts in the Arcane Church, he could follow the news beyond the Shattered Star Ring. He was well read, so he did not lose his composure, but upon witnessing the birth of yet another Beyond Grade A, it was unavoidable that he would be surprised. He just chose not to show it so as not to affect the negotiations.

Seeing this situation, Han Xiao bade his mechanical army to stop before flying in front of Psyker.

The two stood opposite each other, sizing the other party up.

"State your conditions. What do you wish to do with my Evolution Cube?"

Psyker took the initiative to speak. He did not wish to speak in riddles and immediately approached the main topic.

Han Xiao raised his brow.

This guy's personality is really direct, probably not too good at talking...

However, that made sense. Their exchange just now was merely a simple blow, exchanging shots to prove their strength. It was far from what a Beyond Grade A Super could do.

Psyker was willing to communicate mainly because Han Xiao had proven this strength and because it was impossible to eliminate him in a single blow.

Han Xiao's mind was full of nasty words, but he thought about it and spoke solemnly whilst holding onto the Evolution Cube around his neck. "Actually, there's a way for us to cooperate."

"Speak." Psyker remained expressionless.

Han Xiao nodded before explaining the need for a password to crack the Evolution Cube in its portable form. Following which, he said, "I know how to unlock this Evolution Cube, so I can allow it to maintain this portable state and carry it around with me, so it won't be stolen. As for you, since you do not know the password, you can only release its original form, and one day, it might be stolen by the EsGod again, leading to many deaths.

"Thus, I propose that I hold on to the Evolution Cube. Let me divert their attention. You can borrow the Evolution Cube whenever you wish, and both of our forces will also be closely allied to each other, so you do not have to worry about it being stolen and still can continue to utilize its strength. It's a win-win."

Psyker patiently listened before passively saying, "Ah, then I'll also propose something. How about you give the password and the Evolution Cube to me? The Star Pupil Holy Race will be your closest allies, and you can always use the Evolution Cube anytime you wish. Furthermore, I'll help you to get rid of the Tyrant. How about that?"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched. "And if I don't agree..."

"Then I'll help the Tyrant get rid of you." Psyker interrupted Han Xiao without hesitation, pressuring him. "Now, give me your reply. Will you hand it over?"

Chapter 762: Apologies, I Won't Let You Support My Ass

"Is that a threat?" Han Xiao was mystified. This was really too direct.

"No, I'm just helping you understand your current situation." Psyker's tone remained calm yet steely.

With them both being Beyond Grade A Supers who wielded immense strength, the laws of the various civilizations had already lost their purpose in front of them. Beyond Grade A Supers were the class that represented prestige, and they had already stepped out of the rules of society. Thus, any nonsense from Psyker was useless, and he chose to immediately strike his opponent's weak points. This was more useful than exchanging a lot of bullcr*p pleasantries.

As for Black Star's current situation, Psyker was not too aware, but he knew that the Tyrant had set his sights on him. Thus, no matter whom he joined, the balance would be broken.

What he was betting on was that Black Star, as a new Beyond Grade A, would choose stability as a priority. He still had to accumulate his strength and influence, splitting apart the benefits in the Star Field as he had just risen to Beyond Grade A. Thus, facing the threat of two older Beyond Grade As, he would likely choose to compromise.

The Star Pupil Holy Race's genes were already almost optimized to the bottleneck. The function of the Evolution Cube had no use for them, and what Psyker needed was to use its value—to trade it with the Arcane Church in exchange for its support.

Over the past few decades, the Arcane Church had repeatedly proposed generous conditions in exchange for the Evolution Cube, and their latest bid proposed that they would support the Star Pupil Holy Race into becoming the designated spokesperson of the Arcane Church in the Shattered Star Ring, allowing it to become a true Star Cluster civilization. This promise moved Psyker.

However, his bargaining chip was then stolen.

As such, it did not really matter if the Evolution Cube was portable or not. Han Xiao's conditions were not attractive in his eyes, as he did not need to borrow it but rather needed the Evolution Cube itself.

No matter what, the Evolution Cube had to be returned to his hands, or else he would lose the support of the Arcane Church. After all, without the Evolution Cube, there was no need to discuss anything else!

Han Xiao thought a little and could understand Psyker's rationale as well as his bottom line. The other party could not compromise, which gave him a headache.

This little comrade refused to perform the win-win cooperation and only wished to take back the Evolution Cube. He could not fulfill Psyker's wishes in any way.

Threatening another's race would do more harm than benefit as well. All galactic civilizations were covered under the Civilization Treaty but not mercenary groups. This was the difference in the nature of their organizations. It would be okay for others to hit him, but he himself could not attack other civilizations. This was how sad and pathetic the life of a mercenary was.

Psyker cared about his own race, and this was a well-known weakness of this. But if he gave in every time someone threatened him with his race, the Star Pupil Holy Race would not have reached this current stage. One could even say that Psyker had received threats his entire life, leading to his tough stance in dealing with problems. Unless Han Xiao decided to abandon his Black Star Army and turn into a wanted man in the galaxy, like EsGod, he would not use the Star Pupil Holy Race to threaten him.

However, he knew of this point and is not willing to use the Black Star Army to threaten me. This means that he still has some morals left and is not willing to force me into a corner.

Han Xiao's heart was moved.

The focus of this competition was for the Evolution Cube, and both parties had some sort of restraining fear. In order to avoid the losses of both, they had not mentioned their respective forces.

However, Han Xiao was unwilling to hand the cube over to Psyker so easily. For most civilizations, the Evolution Cube was an unprecedented opportunity for development, and no civilization would be able to reject this opportunity. If he controlled the Evolution Cube by himself, it will form a huge collective of interests, and the Black Star Army's influences would soar hundreds of thousands of times higher than it currently was.

Taking a step back, with his identity as a Beyond Grade A, if he took the Evolution Cube to work together with the Crimson Dynasty, he would be able to obtain the support of a Universal Civilization. The Star Pupil Holy Race obviously enjoyed such a benefit from the Arcane Church, and they would also be able to join in the forces for early exploration to the Flickering World, laying the groundwork for future versions.

At the same time, the Evolution Cube would still be able to attract countless Calamity Grades and maybe even Beyond Grade As. That was not impossible.

He was not someone like Psyker who only had his own race in mind, keeping all the good stuff only for his race to utilize.

There was only one Evolution Cube, so the benefits were huge. He did not have a chance before, so that was it. However, this opportunity had been presented to him, and he had the strength to keep the treasure. If he gave it up too easily, it would be letting himself down.

When it was time to fight, Han Xiao would never retreat.

Taking the Evolution Cube for himself would give the best benefits, accompanied by the same amount of risks. However, with his body and Aurora's medicine, even if the Tyrant and Psyker joined forces, they might not be able to kill him. His forces would be able to improve even further without any threat, as the supporting ability of the Evolution Cube was top-class. However, if he gave the cube back to Psyker, while there would be no danger, he would have given up a lot of benefits, only being able to obtain the scraps once they had been distributed.

This was the choice of wanting a single tree or taking the entire forest!

Han Xiao no longer thought about it and asked, "Is there no room for compromise at all?"

"If a civilization wishes to develop, it is inevitable that they fight for resources, for the future," Psyker blandly said. "Since ancient times, no matter how advanced or backward a civilization is, you cannot escape this rule, and you cannot fight it. In the end, if you don't follow these rules, you'll be eliminated. I believe you've heard the saying 'a civilization without ambition has no future'."

He would not say things like the Evolution Cube belonged to him and that he should get it back, as they were both standing at the pinnacle of individual strengths. It was useless to reason. In essence, the Evolution Cube was ownerless, but the other influences considered it his only because he had held it for a long time.

If it was something that the Star Pupil Holy Race had created, Han Xiao would probably have handed it over. However, this treasure did not belong to Psyker, and even if the other party wished to use it for righteous causes such as upgrading his own race, this universe was not only made up of the Star Pupil Holy Race. Resources were obtained by fighting, so why did others have to make way for him? The Star Pupil Holy Race was an intelligent civilization but so were others!

Psyker occupying the Evolution Cube and transforming his race would make him regarded as a hero by his people but a selfish enemy by others. The judgement of one's position was purely based on their perspective, especially in Galaxy where relationships were complex. The development of a civilization had long been a process of sailing against the flow.

In Han Xiao's view, the Star Pupil Holy Race had already enjoyed the benefits of the Evolution Cube. Even if they lost it, the Star Pupil Holy Race would still be a strong civilization. Psyker only grabbed onto this benefit and did not wish to let go because he was not satisfied with the status quo, wishing to take his civilization to a higher level.

"A civilization without ambition has no future. This sentence makes sense. You, as the leader of a civilization, indeed have to place the burdens of the entire civilization on your back. It's just that..." Han Xiao sighed. "I don't intend to pay the bill for your ambition."

Psyker paused before his tone got even more severe. "Have you thought it through?"

"There's only one Evolution Cube. Neither of us wish to let it go, and there's no way to reconcile, so there's nothing left to say." Han Xiao shook his head. He had never been a good person who would turn his head away from money. After weighing the cost and benefits, he came to this decision.

"Good, I hope you don't regret this decision!"

Psyker suddenly moved, and boundless psychic energy in the form of shock waves burst out, distorting the air as they attacked the mechanical army behind, directly penetrating the formation.

Boom!

Thousands of fireworks exploded in the mechanical army, and the broken parts flew all over the sky. Nearly a hundred thousand mechanical soldiers were severely damaged, and their bodies were broken. Some were even directly scrapped.

Those mechanical soldiers constructed at the Calamity Grade were indeed too brittle before a Beyond Grade A, even with the Mechanical Force bonus...

"Spread the formation!" Han Xiao ordered the battle Artificial intelligence from his mind, and his mechanical arm changed its shape to form a spiral drill entwined with psionic energy as it thrust toward Psyker.

Psyker hand eye coordination was swift, and he quickly gripped the drill.

Buzz buzz...

The drill in Psyker's hands spun rapidly, and his palms were covered with a psychic shield that was in contact with the drill. Sparks were constantly being emitted from the friction between the two. Psyker's eyes gleamed at this moment.

Han Xiao felt a burst of pain in his mind as he was attacked in the spiritual state once again. Without waiting, Psyker released white light all over his body, and ripples of psychic energy spread rapidly, smashing into Han Xiao like a block. He was pushed back thousands of meters.

Immediately, Psyker's hands clasped together strongly, and a loud blast of energy surged into the sky!

Han Xiao stabilized his body, and upon looking, he found that Psyker's appearance had changed dramatically.

Psyker's body had swollen to become a circle, and the two jade-like corners of his forehead had elongated. The small hair-like tentacles around his head merged to form a huge white tentacle, like a tail on his head. It waved around, seemingly extremely tensile, and three pairs of wings spread out from the vents around his body, turning him into an arthropod.

His seven eyes lit up with a dazzling white light, and the deep purple lines on his skin all lit up, exuding immense energies. Within the joints of his bone armor, sharp bone blades emerged, and a white cloud like psychic power was continuously released around his body.

Psyker had revealed his true combat form.

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. Not everyone would be willing to work with him, and since Psyker had rejected the support, he decided to keep his own ass and speak with his fists.

In the end, using their fists was still the most direct way to resolve any issues.

When negotiations failed, they could only persuade people in such a way.

I just spoke about flipping the table, and this guy really did so. What a fine temper... but don't think I'm afraid of you!

Boom!

Han Xiao no longer conserved himself and activated all his buff skills before exploding out with all his Mechanical Force.

Whoosh!

The Mechanical army lined up, firing toward Psyker, and the psionic rays from the Particle Cannons were akin to a sea of destruction.

Compared to the hasty confrontation previously, this was a real battle!

This was also the first Beyond Grade A battle that Han Xiao had personally taken part in!

Chapter 763: Intense Battle

Two figures, one white and one blue, collided like two meteors!

Boom!

The shockwave from their collision sent the densely packed mechanical soldiers flying in all directions!

The surging psionic energy in Han Xiao's body was unleashed without any restraint, and Han Xiao's fists hammered down heavily on Psyker's psychic shield, sending out intense shockwaves in all directions. Han Xiao did not retract his fists as his armor transformed into a gigantic hand cannon, with a burning red glow charging up in the barrel of the cannon.

Boom!

Violent dark energy shot out from the barrel of the cannon and swallowed Psyker in a tower of light. However, Psyker remained unmoved like a rock within the tower of light.

Han Xiao frowned. This fellow's psychic shield is too powerful. The shield durability is far too high and he can easily generate another shield after the old shield is destroyed. Although he isn't able to ignore True Damage, my attacks would have to first hit him.

A Psychic's psychic shield was like a Mage's magic shield and even more powerful in certain areas. A Psychic's shield was able to defend against both physical and mental attacks, and Psyker was able to freely control the state of the shield. Since Han Xiao only had physical attacks, Psyker could reduce the strength of his mental shield by ninety percent and channel his energy to physical defense. As such, the shield was extremely durable.

Thankfully, Psyker's physique was not particularly strong, and he did not have any talents to ignore True Damage. Han Xiao could also trigger True Damage attacks on the shield to multiply his damage. However, damage done to the shield was not the same as damage done to Psyker.

The Psychic branch was his nemesis, and the most direct solution would be to compete in firepower.

Boom!

The mechanical army got into formation and spread out in the sky, unleashing their never-ending fire down on Psyker. Particle Cannons, dark energy cannons, psionic cannons, and many other different weapons rained down on Psyker.

Including the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon, more than ten satellite cannons shot into the sky, and thick beams of light smashed down on Psyker's shield.

At this moment, Psyker spread out his arms, and a white whirlpool of psychic energy burst forth from his body and sent Han Xiao flying.

The psychic shockwave swept all the mechanical soldiers near Psyker away, and these soldiers were all smashed into pieces.

Following which, Psyker's knees bent slightly, and he looked as though he was about to jump, treating the sky as flat ground.

Bang!

Psyker's body exploded forth, with every step producing a sonic boom as he charged straight into the mechanical army.

The psychic energy surrounding his body began to spin rapidly, and Psyker seemed to have transformed into a drill. He weaved through the army with unstoppable momentum and released mental attacks while crashing through the army.

The formation of the mechanical army was immediately ripped into shreds with many soldiers being reduced to scrap metal.

The intense battle between the two continued and left giant craters on the planet that they were battling on. The planet's diameter was reduced by a few thousand meters; it was as though a layer was shed from the planet.

Han Xiao tried to approach Psyker to engage in a close combat fight, but Psyker refused to tangle with Han Xiao and focused all his attention on destroying Han Xiao's mechanical army. Whenever Han Xiao came close to Psyker, Psyker would use his psychic force to push Han Xiao back.

Psyker was extremely swift and his shield extremely thick. Many of Han Xiao's attacks were avoided by him, but a portion still managed to find their way to him.

A portion of Psyker's attributes were displayed on Han Xiao's interface. His level had a question mark, but his health was not as high as Han Xiao's. Psyker only had slightly more than 2,000,000 HP and had already lost a little more than 100,000 HP. Psyker's HP was recovering slowly, and he could recover 10,000 HP every second. His normal recovery rate was about 0.5% per second, but with his high total HP, the amount of HP that he could recover was not too low.

Han Xiao glanced at the interface and thought to himself, He doesn't have the Beyond Grade A talent [Everlasting Body] and should have chosen a talent related to energy.

Energy was the foundation of the Psychic class, and Psychics expanded energy extremely rapidly.

Upon seeing that the almost one million mechanical soldiers were destroyed, Han Xiao waved his arm, and his Mechanical Force stuck onto the spare parts like a spider web. All the spare parts gathered together, and Han Xiao combined the spare parts with his [Waste Modification] and [Basic Machinery Construction] skills before throwing them back into the fray.

His mechanical army was not too powerful, but he had many methods to repair his army in battle, and it would not be destroyed so easily. However, he did not have a relaxed expression on his face.

This fellow knows that I have not rebuilt my mechanical army yet and is treating my mechanical army as his breakthrough point. His energy is recovering too quickly, and it'll be difficult for me to fight a protracted battle with him.

He had lowered Psyker's HP by about 100,000, but he had lost about 700,000 HP in return. As Psyker destroyed his mechanical army, Psyker would occasionally send him a few Psychic Blasts or mental attacks. Even though Psyker suffered from the Luck Curse and had a decrease in critical rate, his normal damage was not low.

The Mechanic Class lacked skills that guarded against mental attacks, and he had no way to avoid the opponent's mental attacks.

However, his HP had already recovered to the maximum.

His [Middle Grade Cell Proliferation Control] talent converted energy to health with a 1:5 ratio. Because of the upper limit of his energy, he could regenerate 250,000 HP every second. Although the psychic attacks did not allow him to absorb energy, he could control the Watcher Instruments around him to attack him to regain his energy.

I'll be on the losing side if this continues, and I cannot allow him to attack my army without restraint.

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and a machine appeared beside him. This was a high-grade control type machinery that could use a powerful magnetic force to control the target.

A golden Mechanical Force shot out from his palm and struck the machine. This special bolt of Mechanical Force then merged together with the machine, and the stats of the machine were immediately multiplied.

Emperor's Gift!

The next moment, more than ten thick bolts of electricity exploded forth, and an intense magnetic force was released toward Psyker.

Hum!

Psyker, who was flying at high speed, suddenly stopped in midair as though he was grabbed by an invisible hand.

Without the boost from the Emperor's Gift, it would be impossible to catch Psyker.

The control duration was extremely short, and Han Xiao immediately entered the Void Dimension and appeared behind Psyker the very next moment, grabbing both of Psyker's arms.

His Mountain Ape mechanical suit then transformed into handcuffs to lock onto Psyker's body.

Buzz

Han Xiao activated his [Gene Liberation] skill, and the damage of his entire army was increased.

The next moment, the entire mechanical army fired at both of them!

Boom!

A new gigantic crater was left behind on the surface of the planet.

Han Xiao was sent flying far away and only managed to stabilize his body after travelling a few hundred kilometers. His first priority was to recover his HP before looking around for Psyker.

Psyker was also sent flying and was not in a good state.

At this moment, Psyker had a couple of burn marks all over his body. He had been obstructed by Han Xiao previously, and his psychic shield could not block the full force of the explosion. A small portion of his HP was lost during the blast, but he had various talents to guard his mind and would not be affected by a dizzy status or such.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao could feel a sense of danger approaching from behind him.

He hurriedly unleashed his psionic shield toward his back and saw a white, mist-like figure appearing behind him. As though the shield did not exist, the white figure went through the shield and into Han Xiao's body.

Hum!

Han Xiao could clearly feel this white figure entering his mental region and creating destruction all around before detonating itself. His mind was severely wounded, and his entire head felt heavy and woozy.

Psyker's attack had wiped out almost 200,000 HP, and Han Xiao immediately retreated. However, he also heard Psyker letting out a soft grunt at the same moment.

Bearing with the intense headache, Han Xiao looked over and saw Psyker bleeding from his every orifice.

This is... right! Han Xiao immediately looked at the combat information and almost burst out laughing.

Psyker's sneak attack had triggered the twenty percent mental rebound of [Supreme Piety]. Psyker had suffered from the rebound damage.

Although his Luck was low, Psyker had suffered from his Luck Curse and did not have very good luck either.

I wonder if this is because of my good luck or his bad luck...

Right at this moment, Psyker lifted his head up, and six of his auxiliary eyes lit up to form a white circle on his face with his main eye being the center of the circle.

Following which, his appearance transformed again, and the skeleton armor covered his entire body, only revealing his seven eyes.

The combat information displayed that Psyker entered a new state with all his attributes explosively increasing. A new white layer appeared on his health bar, which was a full sixty percent of his max HP.

"Again," Psyker said with a deep voice and his voice resounded like a bell.

Han Xiao's mouth contorted.

Transforming again?

Do you think you are Frieza[1]‽

This is against the rules! Do you think you can do as you wish just because you are a combat race?

A Beyond Grade A is truly perverse with never ending methods.

Han Xiao felt his balls ache.

Although Psyker did not have regenerative capabilities like him, he had many different forms that provided him with extra HP and defense.

When he was in the Calamity Grade, he had an almost BUG like ability among the Calamity Grade Supers. However, every Beyond Grade A existence was like a bug-like character, and not a single one was easy to deal with.

"Hiss..."

Han Xiao took a deep breath and circulated his energy to the maximum. Letting out a loud roar, Han Xiao led his mechanical army to clash with Psyker again!

After their previous exchange, Han Xiao had a rough estimate of the Psyker's strength. Both of them were on par, and it would be extremely difficult for either of them to get rid of the other party. However, with his mechanical army being destroyed, his damage would decrease over time.

Since his mechanical army had to be rebuilt anyway, Han Xiao decided to ignore the damage to his army and make use of this opportunity to measure his combat strength. He would only have the chance to go all out when facing another Beyond Grade A Super.

Bang bang bang!

Their battle lasted a few hours, and they flew around the entire planet a few times, destroying its surface.

The surface of the planet was riddled with many unfathomable craters, and the intense vibrations on the surface of the planet caused lava to shoot out from these craters a few thousand meters into the sky. The entire planet seemed to have become an orange that was riddled with holes, and all its juice was being squeezed out from it.

The lava that spurted out into the sky cooled down rapidly and rained down like meteors.

Bang!

This was the umpteenth time that both the figures had collided and separated.

Han Xiao floated in midair, and the surface of his mechanical suit shattered into pieces to reveal his body. This was already his fourth mechanical suit. His [Machinery Continuation] skill reached its time limit, and his mechanical suit was reduced to a pile of scrap metal.

The mechanical army in the surroundings had become sparse. Han Xiao had used his Waste Modification skill to reform the wasted machines too many times, and the upper limit had been reached. But even if this was the case, his mechanical army still had the size of about four million soldiers.

On the other side, Psyker's skeleton armor was half destroyed with blue blood all over his body, and his psychic energy was much weaker than before.

More than half of my mechanical army has been destroyed, and I'll be on the losing end if this battle continues, Han Xiao thought to himself. He won't be able to deal with me, and I can't do anything to him. There isn't a need to continue this battle. I should rebuild my mechanical army first...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he threw an Observer's Mark onto Psyker.

He would not be able to remove the psychic mark that Psyker had placed on the Evolution Cube and could only return the favor. With both of them aware of the other party's location, he would not be on the losing end.

"Hmm?" Psyker's eyes narrowed. His mental sense was acute, and he could clearly sense the feeling of being spied on but did not know where it came from.

He was not a mage who could grasp multidimensional energy, and although he could feel the Observer's Mark, he could not get rid of it.

Furthermore, Han Xiao was already a Beyond Grade A Super, and it would be even more difficult to get rid of his Observer's Mark. At the very least, it would be impossible for a Calamity Grade Mage to do so.

Clank!

Han Xiao then waved his arm and stored his mechanical army away. Without saying a word, he activated his Void Dimension Jump and disappeared in the blink of an eye.

During the battle, he had intentionally destroyed the other party's spaceship, and it would be impossible for Psyker to catch up to him in terms of flying speed.

Psyker watched as Han Xiao disappeared and did not make a move.

He had already gone all out, but Black Star was not at a disadvantage. It would be difficult for him to snatch the Evolution Cube back with just his own strength...

Han Xiao was not the only one who felt that they would not be able to do anything to each other. Psyker also had such a feeling.

He could not count the number of times he had attacked Black Star with his mental attack. However, the other party only seemed to have lost his mechanical army but remained as lively as a tiger.

Such a situation reminded him of the Tyrant.

"A new Beyond Grade A Mechanic who has a powerful physique like Tyrant," Psyker muttered to himself. "Indestructible Body?"

Right at this moment, a figure flew over. It was Sardeem. His appearance seemed extremely pathetic, and he was equipped with a simple thruster made from spare parts.

"You're still alive?" Psyker looked over.

"I hid myself when the two of you were fighting."

Sardeem had a sense of lingering fear in his heart. He did not have any equipment on him, and the battle of two Beyond Grade A Supers was enough to threaten his life. He had long escaped from Psyker's spaceship and escaped from the battlefield.

Looking at Psyker's appearance, Sardeem asked with a trembling voice, "You... weren't able to defeat Black Star?"

Psyker glanced at Sardeem and replied, "He escaped. I couldn't keep him back."

Sardeem took a deep breath. He had already expected such a reply but wanted to confirm it. Although he was already mentally prepared for such a reply, he was still filled with shock.

"The fifth Beyond Grade A Super has been born in the Shattered Star Ring, and the Star Field will experience a huge change," Sardeem murmured. "I'd better send this piece of news to His Excellency Manison."

"Not just the Shattered Star Ring..." Psyker interrupted him with a profound tone. "Perhaps the attention of the entire galaxy will be drawn."

Psyker's eyes gleamed. The Evolution Cube isn't so easily taken.

With Black Star carrying the Evolution Cube around with him, it would be extremely difficult for him to snatch it back alone. Psyker decided to find a few allies and make further plans.

Before this, I shall leave the item in Black Star's possession.

Since his psychic mark was still present, Psyker felt that things were within his control.

He then looked up at the sky. Psyker was not planning to fly with his body, so he looked at Sardeem.

"You're a Mechanic, right?"

"Er, what's the matter?" Sardeem was stunned for a moment.

Psyker pointed at the spare parts on the ground.

"Build a spaceship."

"..." Sardeem.

[1] This is a Dragon Ball reference. It's where the "This isn't even my final form" meme comes from. Back

Chapter 764: The Impending Storm

Han Xiao left Psyker, who did not have a spaceship, on the unlucky planet and made use of his Void Dimension Jump to return to the Shattered Star Ring.

He contacted Hila and the others, who had left Planet Macipher, and got them to fetch him with the spaceship. Both parties finally met up in the desolate universe belt.

Whoosh.

The hatch of the spaceship opened, and Han Xiao was greeted by Hila and the two others the moment he entered the spaceship.

Feidin walked forward and studied Han Xiao. After making sure that he was completely intact, he heaved a sigh of relief. "It seems like you are alright. We've been extremely worried about you."

Hila snorted. "Speak for yourself..."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao could not help but chuckle. "Actually, it wasn't very dangerous. All of you should be extremely clear about how robust my life force is."

"Talking about life force..." Aurora had a look of confusion on her face, and she said with disbelief in her voice, "If my senses aren't wrong, have you..."

"Has he what?" Hila interrupted.

Han Xiao had a smile on his face and took out the Evolution Cube to play with it.

"Your guess is correct. I fought Psyker, and the outcome of the battle was a draw. He didn't manage to snatch the item back."

Fought Psyker to a draw?

Hila was stunned for a moment, and it took a second to understand what Han Xiao meant. She took a deep breath, and a look of disbelief could be seen on her usually expressionless face. She looked at Han Xiao with her eyes widened.

"Could it be that... Beyond Grade A‽"

"It was by luck." Han Xiao waved his hands but had a look of pride on his face.

After hearing him admit it, Hila, Aurora, and Feidin revealed looks of shock.

Black Star... is really a Beyond Grade A Super already?

Although the three of them had looked forward to Han Xiao achieving a breakthrough and standing among the ranks of the Beyond Grade A Supers, their trip with Han Xiao had felt more like a holiday, and they did not notice any signs of breakthrough from Han Xiao.

All of them had felt that the chances of him achieving a breakthrough were not high.

However, he had achieved a breakthrough just like that! While they were not mentally prepared for it, Black Star had suddenly risen into the next grade and even fought a Beyond Grade A Super who had long made a name for himself to a draw. They truly could not imagine how Han Xiao did it.

The three of them felt their heads blank out at this moment.

After snapping out from their daze, they all erupted with surprise.

Although they were very surprised, it was a good thing!

Feidin was overjoyed. "Wonderful! I've always believed that you had such potential. We don't have to escape from the Shattered Star Ring if this is the case!"

"I never intended to escape..." Han Xiao said helplessly.

Aurora then looked at Han Xiao and asked with shock on her face, "Does this mean that you are already at our teacher's level?"

Ames? It is time for me to have a talk with her, Han Xiao thought to himself and nodded in response.

"You..." Hila hesitated for a while before swallowing what she wanted to say. "Congrats."

She had a complicated feeling in her heart. She had always wanted to chase after Han Xiao. When Han Xiao was still in the Calamity Grade, she could still spur herself to work harder. However, things were different this time.

During the ten years when she was on Floating Dragon Island, she had experienced Ames' strength many times and was extremely clear about the strength of a Beyond Grade A Super. At the same time, she was extremely clear about how difficult it would be to become a Beyond Grade A Super.

For so many years, the Star Field only had four Beyond Grade A Supers. Together with Han Xiao's advancement, there were now five. Hila had known Han Xiao for almost twenty years and witnessed his weak appearance, his invincible Calamity Grade appearance, and his every stage of development.

He had taken him a mere twenty years to go from an ordinary man to a new Beyond Grade A Super. He would probably be the individual who took the least amount of time to become a Beyond Grade A Super in history. Because she understood Han Xiao's past, Hila knew how difficult it was for Han Xiao to have achieved what he had.

Even if Hila refused to admit defeat on their surface, she could not help but admire Han Xiao's achievements in her heart.

If Hila had originally possessed any thoughts of competing with Han Xiao for glory, at this moment, she was willing to become the shadow behind Han Xiao's splendor.

She had a feeling that she was witnessing the birth of a legend.

Of course, it was impossible for her to reveal her true thoughts.

Hila then changed the topic and asked, "Just how did you do it? Can you teach me?"

Er, I can't teach you anything since you don't know how to harvest crops... Han Xiao coughed dryly before placing his hands on Hila's shoulders with a solemn expression.

"No, you don't need me to teach you anything."

"What do you mean?" Hila was puzzled.

Han Xiao then looked at Hila and said, "I have always believed in your potential. Just like how you believe in me, you will stand by my side at the peak of the galaxy one day."

Hila pushed Han Xiao's hands away and turned around to prevent Han Xiao from seeing her flustered appearance. She then said with a soft voice, "Thank you."

So, it turns out that you have so much trust in me. I didn't even know that...

"There isn't a need for thanks between us." Han Xiao waved his arms. "We've known each other for twenty years."

At this moment, Aurora pulled on Han Xiao's clothes and whined, "What about me? Do you believe in me?"

Han Xiao rubbed her head helplessly and said, "Wait until you reach the Calamity Grade."

"Humph. So biased." Aurora turned around.

After soaking in the excitement of Han Xiao becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, they then got back to the main point.

"Black Star, you took away Psyker's Evolution Cube; he won't give up so easily, right?"

"Hmm, he said that he will work together with the Tyrant to deal with me. Compared to the benefits of the Evolution Cube, this risk can be considered extremely low. There isn't a need to bother about him in the near future. He's still busy with something else." Han Xiao shook his head with a smile. From the Observer's Mark, he could see that Psyker was still on the planet and rushing Sardeem to build a new spaceship from spare parts.

Feidin frowned and said, "It'll be very dangerous if the Tyrant and Psyker work together."

Han Xiao waved his arms and said, "It isn't a big deal. Although I am a new Beyond Grade A Super, I do not belong to the bottommost rung of this level. Besides, I have allies as well."

Isn't this a competition of numbers? You're not the only one who knows how to play that game.

As compared to the other Beyond Grade A Supers, his largest advantage was his clear path of advancement.

The other Beyond Grade A Supers would have to find their own path after entering Beyond Grade A, and it was akin to searching around in the dark. However, it was as though he had a torchlight with him, and he could easily progress by harvesting crops. His growth rate would completely outstrip the others.

"How are you planning to deal with the Evolution Cube?"

"Take it back to the camp first and let the officers enjoy the effects of the Evolution Cube." Han Xiao stroked his chin. "I will then use it to find allies and a new backer."

Psyker had the support of the Arcane Church, and he could achieve the same effect with the Evolution Cube in his hands.

Compared to Psyker, his advantage was the fact that the Evolution Cube was now portable. With him carrying it around, the likelihood of it being stolen was much lower.

News of him having the Evolution Cube would spread throughout the Galaxy eventually, and it was impossible for Psyker to help him keep the secret. Psyker might even choose to create more enemies for him.

At that time, all the organizations eyeing the Evolution Cube would have their attention drawn to him. It would be impossible for him to hold onto the Evolution Cube in the long term with just the strength of the Black Star Army, so he needed to find a backer.

Beep beep!

Right at this moment, an emergency transmission lit up on his communicator. Han Xiao glanced at his communicator, and it was a communication request by Ralph.

Han Xiao waved his arm to ask Hila and the others to pilot the spaceship. He then walked to the side and picked up the call.

"Black Star, I have a heaven breaking piece of bad news!"

"You make it sound as though we had good news in the past." Han Xiao was in a good mood and joked.

Ralph ignored his joke and said with a solemn tone, "We verified a piece of news a few days ago. The Crimson Dynasty have concluded their negotiations with the Federation of Light. After the Crimson Dynasty takes over the new Star Field, they will turn their attention to the storm that they created in the various regions. Our secret war with Klent will also come to an end in half a year's time!"

"Oh?" Han Xiao muttered. "This is a piece of bad news indeed."

The Bloodshed Land still controlled a few Star Systems around the borders of the Colton Star Cluster, and Klent was the loyal lackey of the Crimson Dynasty. The Crimson Dynasty would definitely make use of this excuse to demarcate these territories as part of the Klent Kingdom. The authority of deciding borders was something that the three Universal Civilizations gave to themselves, and if Section Zero were unable to chase Bloodshed Land out before then, Purple Crystal would probably lose those few territories.

The Shattered Star Ring belonged to the management zone of the Federation of Light. Unless Purple Crystal gave up their neutrality and chose to submit to another civilization, it would be impossible for anyone to come out and uphold justice for them. The Crimson Dynasty and Federation of Light would be exchanging benefits at a higher level, and Purple Crystal did not even have the right to interfere in their negotiations. They could only watch as their territories were taken away.

Of course, Purple Crystal could strongly protest against the decision made by the three Universal Civilizations and unilaterally decide to reject their decision. However, the outcome of such a decision definitely would not be a pretty one. As the ones setting the rules, the three Universal Civilizations would not allow anyone to challenge their authority. All three civilizations were powerful civilizations who had been through dark times and definitely were not merciful characters.

With the strength to overlook the entire galaxy, they had countless methods to make a civilization submit. The rules were completely irrelevant to those who set the rules.

Thus, Han Xiao was not too surprised about the appearance of the Silver Revolutionary Army. However, it was still far too early to talk about that.

"Black Star, your holiday is over," Ralph said with a solemn expression. "We need your strength to snatch back as many territories as possible."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and came to a decision. "The biggest backing of the Klent Kingdom is the Crimson Dynasty. However, I have an idea to get the Crimson Dynasty to stay out of this matter and not help Klent negotiate with the Federation of Light. This way, it will be useless even if the Bloodshed Land occupies the border Star Systems."

Ralph's eyes lit up, and he immediately asked, "What idea do you have?"

"I..." Han Xiao then thought about something and decided against telling Purple Crystal that he was a Beyond Grade A Super. "It is extremely likely for my plan to succeed, but I have to keep it a secret for now. You just need to believe in me. In any case, the situation can't be worse than it is right now."

It was not that Han Xiao wanted to hide his Beyond Grade A strength. If Purple Crystal knew about his newfound strength, they would announce it to the entire world to serve as a deterrent.

This was not good for him.

His original plan was to remain low profile after entering Beyond Grade A and accumulate his strength. When the Tyrant attempted to kill him, the Tyrant would then underestimate his strength, and he would be able to deal a low blow to the Tyrant. However, the sudden appearance of the Evolution Cube spoiled his plans, and it would be impossible for him to hide his strength. Despite that, Han Xiao did not want to fight the Tyrant immediately.

He needed some time to build a new mechanical army and Beyond Grade A base. He still had to activate many of the Emperor Mechanic skills and allow his combat strength to reach the peak. Compared to letting Purple Crystal announce his strength to the world, he would rather let Psyker slowly reveal news to the Star Field. This way, he would have a bit more time.

There was another reason he did not wish to let Purple Crystal know of his strength. Han Xiao wanted to increase his value.

If he was an ordinary Beyond Grade A, his best choice would be to form an alliance with a Star Cluster civilization just like Heber had done. Although Universal Civilizations also welcomed Beyond Grade A Supers, they would not place such great importance on these Beyond Grade A Supers compared to a Star Cluster civilization. After all, that which is rare is dear.

However, things were different with the Evolution Cube. The Evolution Cube was a unique Universal Treasure, and with Psyker as an example, the Universal Civilizations would offer an even higher price. This way, their Black Star Army would be raised to the next level.

Because of the existence of the Flickering World, Han Xiao had already decided that the Crimson Dynasty would be his most suitable ally.

If he formed an alliance with the Crimson Dynasty, he would be able to resolve the secret war and foil the plans of the Klent Kingdom.

If he allowed things to develop normally, the outcome of the S Grade secret war mission would probably be failure. Although it was because of the uniqueness of the mission, and they would still have some reward, their mission rating would be lowered, and the players of the Black Star Army would not be able to gain the best reward.

Considering the need to maintain the players' reliance on the Black Star Army, joining the Crimson Dynasty was the best choice.

Before Ralph could continue questioning him, Han Xiao hung up and walked to the cockpit.

Aurora sat on the pilot's seat and asked, "Where are we going?"

Han Xiao smirked.

"Back to the army!"

...

A few days later, Sardeem finally returned to Planet Macipher. At the same time, he brought with him a piece of shocking news. He said that he had personally witnessed the Beyond Grade A seed Black Star, who had the title of 'Indestructible Body', becoming a Beyond Grade A Super.

This news rapidly spread through Planet Macipher, and many visitors on the planet did not believe it.

Why would Black Star become the fifth Beyond Grade A Super in the Shattered Star Ring so suddenly? Why did Purple Crystal not react? Could it be a rumor?

This piece of news was not backed by any evidence, and the galactic residents who had been exposed to a wide variety of information were not convinced.

However, Psyker, who was a guest on Planet Macipher, actually personally admitted it!

All doubts disappeared, and the entire planet was filled with shock!

The fifth Beyond Grade A is born‽

Oh my goodness! This is big news!

The residents of Planet Macipher who had received this news were dumbfounded and immediately posted this piece of news on the net.

News of the battle between Black Star and Psyker spread rapidly like a virus throughout the entire Star Field.

A storm that was about to sweep through the entire Shattered Star Ring began brewing...

Chapter 765: Prelude to Change

In some transit station at the border of the Shattered Star Ring.

In an olden style inn, Hadavy sat in the corner and drank a glass of strong wine. There were mixed blood elves performing on the stage with a beautiful tone lingering in his ears. The customers of the inn were of many different races, and they were laughing merrily.

The atmosphere was soothing, but Hadavy had a depressed look on his face.

A few months ago, Jorde had made use of him to launch a sneak attack against Black Star. Hadavy had terminated the cooperation with them in a fit of rage and left the secret war.

He had chosen to join the Bloodshed Land because he wanted to spar with Black Star and stimulate his potential through battle. After fighting Black Star more than ten times, he could not help but feel a sense of appreciation for Han Xiao. In his eyes, Black Star was an opponent worthy of respect.

Hadavy would rather lose to Black Star time and time again than use despicable methods to deal with him.

After this event, Hadavy no longer had the face to find Han Xiao to spar. He planned to leave the Shattered Star Ring and roam the other Star Fields. This was the reason he had visited the borders of the Shattered Star Ring.

Just when he was drinking and depressed, a conversation caught his attention.

"Have all of you heard? The fifth Beyond Grade A Super has appeared in the Shattered Star Ring!"

What? A new Beyond Grade A?

He was a Beyond Grade A seed and his target had always been becoming a Beyond Grade A Super. Thus, he paid close attention to this topic.

With his senses of a Calamity Grade Super, the conversation of the table beside him seemed to be right beside his ears.

"You have heard about it, too? I know about Black Star. There were reports about him a few years ago saying that he was the most likely person to become a Beyond Grade A Super in the Shattered Star Ring. I thought that it was no more than a farce at that time but never imagined that it would actually become the truth."

"He is the leader of the Black Star Army. All of you should know about the Black Star Army, right? It is the famous armed organization in the Colton Star Cluster. I have a friend who is a merchant. Once, his merchant ship was robbed, and he sought help from the Mercenary League to solve the problem. They sent the Black Star Army, and the mercenaries of this organization are extremely friendly and reliable."

"Didn't he become low profile over the past few years?" someone else asked curiously. "I heard that news of him becoming a Beyond Grade A Super is only a rumor."

"It isn't a rumor. Even 'Star Pupil' Psyker admitted that he only fought Black Star to a draw. If he is able to fight a Beyond Grade A Super without losing, he can only be a Beyond Grade A Super."

Ka-la!

Hadavy crushed the wine glass in his hands, and wine splashed all over his body. However, he was still in a daze with a look of shock on his face.

Black Star has actually become a Beyond Grade A Super already‽

Upon hearing news of his old opponent, Hadavy could not help but be filled with envy and jealousy. He had spent a few decades but not touched the door of Beyond Grade A.

He had already given it his all but was still overtaken by others. After being filled with shock, his heart was filled with bitterness.

Why can he do it? What trick did he use?

Hadavy's face changed color, and he hammered down on the table before standing up abruptly. The sudden commotion attracted the gaze of all the customers present.

Ignoring the strange looks on their faces, Hadavy left the inn.

He came to a decision. He would not leave the Shattered Star Ring but make a trip to the headquarters of the Black Star Army.

This time, he would not go on behalf of the Bloodshed Land but using his personal identity.

Perhaps Black Star would not recognize an old opponent like him, and his life might be in danger...

However, he had been troubled by the problem of becoming a Beyond Grade A Super for many years. He decided to take this risk. Regardless of whether Black Star showed him any respect, he wanted to give it a shot.

...

The headquarters of the Mercenary League in the Gelock Star Cluster was a gigantic space fortress built by Black Star, Sky Ring, Blades, and many other large sized mercenary groups. Surrounding the gigantic space fortress were more than twenty armed satellites that were the branches of the respective large sized mercenary groups. The Black Star Army also had a branch located there. To all the members of the Mercenary League, this was akin to a second headquarters.

The million or so new players who were on Planet Deirdre had participated in many different storylines.

Some of them had chosen to join the secret war while others had chosen to remain in the Gelock Star Cluster and follow the storyline of the Mercenary League.

The storyline mission of the Mercenary League also gave huge rewards, and with the background of the Black Star Army, the players had plenty of mercenary missions to choose from.

After a few months, the average level of the players had risen rapidly, and they were all approaching level sixty.

Han Xiao's legends had spread to the Mercenary League, and the players in the branch had also heard about it.

After the news spread, a huge commotion was created on the forums, and the players were all shocked.

Han Xiao was an NPC that the players were extremely familiar with, and many of the players respected him as the leader of their faction. They had witnessed his growth from Version 1.0 to Version 3.0, and Han Xiao was a legendary character in the Shattered Star Ring to the players.

At this moment, a new chapter of this legend had begun.

All the players who participated in the secret war were even more shocked. Black Star had disappeared from the battlefield for a few months, and many of them had been guessing Black Star's whereabouts. However, none of them had guessed that he would return as a Beyond Grade A Super!

This news became a hot topic on the forums, and all the players of the Black Star Army were extremely agitated. As part of the Black Star Army, the promotion of their leader brought them glory as well.

"What else is there to say? Our Army Commander is the coolest! Black Star is the coolest!"

"There were only four Beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring before this, and Black Star is the fifth. Does this mean that our army is going to become a Beyond Grade A organization as well?"

"Of course!"

"Wahahaha. Our Planet Aquamarine faction leader is too awesome. We can match up to all the other factions in the other player regions alone. A growth type faction is too tyrannical."

"@Summer Night Flower, stop hiding. Get over here!"

"@Summer Night Flower, how's life in Bloodshed Land? Come out and share your experiences with us. We won't laugh at you. Hahaha..."

"@Summer Night Flower, please begin your performance."

"@Summer..."

Summer Night Flower's post from a few months ago was now trending, and many players were gloating at his misfortune.

Seeing the excitement of the other players, Summer Night Flower did not dare show himself.

What is going on? The storyline shouldn't be like this!

Some were feeling their nuts ache while others were overjoyed. Compared to Summer Night Flower, Bun-Hit-Dog was overjoyed.

Bun-Hit-Dog had been frustrated over not having any good material the last few months, but Black Star had gone and become a peak expert in the galaxy during this period. There was no better material than this.

He already had some ideas. This can be a milestone episode in the Black Star series.

Many of the older players were having merry conversations on the forums while the new players read the posts from the side silently. The newbies from Version 3.0 did not have very deep feelings toward Black Star, but after participating in the conversation, they had a much deeper impression of Han Xiao.

Very quickly, the news became an official report that was placed on the desks of various large organizations, causing an even greater commotion at a higher level.

Compared to the galactic residents who only wanted to join in the fun, the various organizations of the Shattered Star Ring had to consider how the birth of a new Beyond Grade A would affect the situation in the Shattered Star Ring as well as how they should interact with Black Star.

...

On Planet Heber, Jorde stood up abruptly after reading the report and had a look of disbelief on his face.

"Black Star is a Beyond Grade A‽ How is this possible! Didn't I..."

All of a sudden, his heart was thrown into a mess. His scheme had originally forced Black Star to back out from the war, but Black Star had now become a Beyond Grade A.

All his plans were disrupted!

Jorde hurried over to the Tyrant's abode and looked at Heber. Just when he was about to give a report, Heber took the initiative to speak.

"I know about it already. Klent just contacted me about it; they are extremely flustered. They are trying to verify the truth at the moment and told me to make preparations."

Heber sounded as though he was a little excited.

Upon hearing that, Jorde calmed himself down and asked, "What should I do?"

"You don't have to do anything," Heber said slowly. "When Black Star or Purple Crystal admits that he is a Beyond Grade A, it will become my business."

Jorde could not help but gulp in anticipation. The Tyrant... His Excellency Heber was about to take action!

Heber shook his head and got Jorde to leave. Heber was the only one left in the palace.

Du! Du!

Right at this moment, his communicator rang.

Heber looked at the caller, and his eyes narrowed.

"Psyker? It has been a long time since he last contacted me. Why is this fellow looking for me?"

...

In some region of the Shattered Star Ring, the final Light Fox spaceship was escaping. This fellow was the last of EsGod's subordinates who was lucky enough to survive.

"I lost contact with Orozen and the others, and don't know where the Evolution Cube went. What should we do?"

"They should be dead. Black Star became a Beyond Grade A Super and fought Psyker. The Evolution Cube may be in his hands."

"Quickly report this matter to EsGod. We failed."

...

Very quickly, news spread across the Star Field to every level and region, and more and more people found out about this piece of news.

The entire Shattered Star Ring was shaken!

As long as a new Beyond Grade A was born, it would definitely become the headlines of the Star Field for a long period of time.

Every Beyond Grade A figure had once been in the spotlight of the entire world.

It was now Han Xiao's turn to enjoy such treatment.

The attention of the Shattered Star Ring was gathered on the Black Star Army. Rumors were rumors after all, and everyone was waiting for the new Beyond Grade A to announce his status in the Star Field and admit his strength personally.

However, regardless of the rumors in the outside world, Black Star did not appear, and the Black Star Army did not release a statement. The media was blocked out of the headquarters of the Black Star Army, and even their ally Purple Crystal was unusually quiet.

The longer this lasted, the more anxious the other organizations became, desperate to confirm Black Star's strength.

Everyone was waiting to see what would happen next.

By that point, Han Xiao had returned to the Black Star Army and summoned all his officers.

Chapter 766: Setting Up the Black Star Guards Regiment

The spaceship sailed into the private port of the army headquarters and slid through a secret channel to arrive at Han Xiao's personal dock. This dock was not open to members of the Black Star Army and was a dedicated back door for the senior officers. Compared to the boisterous harbor, this place seemed quite deserted, and the atmosphere was more somber.

Standing around the dock were the dozens of senior officers that had been called over. They had long gathered in this place, with solemn expressions on their faces.

Among them were the Calamity Grades who had been at the front line just a while ago. Due to the rumors of Han Xiao advancing to Beyond Grade A, the situation of the secret war had started to show strange changes. Before this, the two sides had been fighting for several months, but as soon as the news came out, both sides tacitly gathered their troops and began to reduce the number of battles. All of them began the game of wait-and-see, so the Black Star Army was able to transfer their officers back.

Both sides knew that if a Beyond Grade A appeared on both sides, then the direction of the secret war would no longer be left to them.

While Han Xiao had not shown himself, he had already started to subtly influence the situation as a Beyond Grade A, directly affecting the secret war.

Whoosh!

The cabin door opened, and Han Xiao stepped forward. The eyes of many of the officers, including Sylvia's, lit up. They contained excitement, joy, and expectation.

All the officers present sized Han Xiao up. While there were no outward changes to his appearance, everyone could feel a sense of pressure, which came from the natural suppression of a higher life form.

The crowd exchanged glances, with confused looks, and looked toward Feidin, who was standing behind Han Xiao. Feidin only smiled and nodded at everyone else.

Han Xiao stepped onto the dock, sweeping his gaze over everyone present before giving a slight nod. As he walked forward, the officers all made way for him to pass through before walking behind him, entering the inner quarters of the Black Star Army headquarters.

The group arrived at the Army Commander's office in the headquarters. Sylvia was at the back and shut the door after everyone had entered. Han Xiao then turned around to address everyone. He nodded as he said, "I know that many of you are curious if the rumors outside are true. I only told you that I would be issuing a notice, but right now, I can say that the rumors are not wrong. I'm now a Beyond Grade A Super."

Upon hearing the personal confirmation, the taut expressions of the majority of them relaxed. Some even showed expressions of joy, and some, expressions of respect.

Sylvia, Herlous, and the older officers had the most excited expressions. They were the ones most loyal to Han Xiao and had been with the army the longest.

Reynold could not help but immediately wish to beg Han Xiao for some tutelage. He was the one most excited about it.

As for the few Calamity Grades who had joined the Black Star Army a few years prior, they were betting on Han Xiao being a Beyond Grade A seed that would rise to a true Beyond Grade A with time. The moment Han Xiao turned into a true Beyond Grade A, they would also become the backbone of this strong force.

It seemed like their bets had paid off, and their futures were bright.

The Vice Commander Lagi sighed, his face bitter as he said, "Now that you've become a Beyond Grade A, we'll likely be involved in the battle vortex of Beyond Grade As in the future, encountering stronger and stronger opponents. I feel that my life is less safe, so I would like to step down as the Vice Commander... Reynold, are you lacking people in the Logistics department? Is there a more leisurely position?"

Reynold remained expressionless. "That's fine with me. I'm currently lacking a Senior Enchantment Engineer. I'll pay you a daily salary of 2,000 Enas, and you have to work for fifteen hours a day. There will occasionally be overtime. Do you want to try it out?"

"... Forget it, I'll stay as the Vice Commander. I get paid without having to work. That's so much better."

Han Xiao's brain started to cramp up. "Talking about skiving in front of me, do you think that I don't exist anymore? Oh, by the way, where's that Tomar guy that I handed to you? How's his progress?"

Hearing this, Lagi's expression became even more twisted. He seemed to be filled with a negative aura, as though he would squat down at any moment and begin to draw circles on the floor.

"Just where did you find that genius? He's beginning to make me feel as though my years of learning magic are all wasted. Indeed, I should not have chosen the Mage profession all those years ago..."

Ok, that's enough, you can go to the corner and reflect in silence...

Han Xiao's mouth twitched, but he forcibly suppressed the words he wished to say and regained his impassive expression.

"Today, my reason for gathering all of you is for two things. The first was to inform you that I've reached Beyond Grade A. As for its importance, I don't need to emphasize it, but the business of Black Star Army will be able to expand far beyond what it is currently, rising to a real Beyond Grade A organization and fighting head on against Bloodshed Land."

Upon hearing the gravity of this matter, other than Lagi who was still murmuring nonsense, the rest all turned serious.

"By all means, this matter should have been announced in a high profile so that the entire Star Field knows of my existence..." Han Xiao shook his finger. "But for certain reasons, it is temporarily inconvenient to confirm the rumors that I've become a Beyond Grade A. I also do not intend to announce it within the headquarters yet. However, this acknowledgment is basically formal, high-profile behavior, and most organizations already believe in the truth of this rumor. Thus, even if I do not step up, there'll still be messengers that will come and contact us.

"Therefore, I'll need you all to cover up this fact to a certain extent. Secretly contact those forces who intend to cooperate with us, screen them, and handle the cooperative relationships. This matter involves us becoming a Beyond Grade A organization, so the earlier we get this done, the better. As for the specifics, you guys are veterans at this and should know what to look out for."

Everyone else nodded.

Was it not just getting support? They had long learned this from their Army Commander himself.

Han Xiao then raised up his second finger. "The second thing is regarding benefits for you..."

As he spoke, he took out the Evolution Cube, letting it float in midair as he smiled.

"This is the Evolution Cube. That's right. It's the Universal Treasure that was originally with Psyker. After a series of coincidences, I intercepted this thing and had a fight with Psyker. Thus, this is now in my hands..." He then went on to describe the benefits of the Evolution Cube.

As soon as this remark was made, everyone stood stunned, their mouths open in disbelief.

It was rumored that Black Star had fought with Psyker, which led everyone to speculate why they would fight. The officers had also been curious about this but did not expect the reason to be about the Evolution Cube!

The Evolution Cube has changed owners‽

It's now in the hands of our Army Commander‽

One of the Calamity Grades, Misecech, gulped and stuttered with a look full of expectation, "Do... do you mean to allow us to enjoy the benefits that the Evolution Cube brings?"

Han Xiao nodded and laughed. "I've already let Feidin and the rest use it. Since the cube is now in my hands, I'll definitely allow my own officers to enjoy the benefits. You're all the backbone of my army, and helping you all get stronger means that the army will also become stronger."

Most of the Calamity Grades who came later were overjoyed. They did not expect to receive such benefits. For most of the Calamity Grades, they were extremely enthusiastic whenever it came to ways to enhance their strength.

Lagi also stopped his murmuring and immediately lunged forward to grip Han Xiao's hands, his face solemn.

"As your Vice Commander, it's my responsibility to inform you that the priority of benefits should be given by our ranks. I've shed so much sweat and blood for the army, and as your Vice Commander, you should know what I mean..."

Han Xiao swatted his hands away, glancing at him sideways as he retorted, "You might have sweated for the army, but you've never bled for us before, so this makes things difficult to place."

Lagi clutched his chest 'painfully', putting on a helpless expression. "Actually... I was heavily injured once on the battlefield..."

"Scram aside, you won't lose your benefits anyway." Han Xiao could not be bothered to argue with him any longer. "When we talk about work, you lie there like a corpse, but the moment we mention benefits, you immediately jump up. This guy, you're getting more and more sly."

Even Lagi—who was like a salted fish, not interested in anything happening around him—was excited. This spoke volumes about the attractiveness of the Evolution Cube.

The Evolution Cube was provided to the Senior Officers free of charge, and for the other members of the organization, Han Xiao did not intend to hide it. He first intended to form an alliance with the Crimson Dynasty to completely protect the Evolution Cube before opening it to the entire army. According to their ranks, they would pay a corresponding amount, which would allow them to enjoy the Evolution Cube while comprehensively improving the combat capability of the entire army.

This could also attract countless Supers to the army.

At the same time, this was a new service that would be provided to players. The forty percent experience penalty only applied to upgrades, which was not a big problem for the players. As long as it was used after reaching the upper limit of the current version, there was no problem in having the experience penalty.

Even if the players could not resist and used the Evolution Cube before their level cap was reached, it was also not harmful to Han Xiao. Since there would be a penalty for upgrading, players would use their experience to improve their skills or learn new knowledge, which would still flow into his pocket.

This was perfect!

With this in mind, Han Xiao could not help but smile. After that, he shelved the unnecessary thoughts, returning to the actual topic. "Basically, these are the two matters. I'll use the Evolution Cube to help you all optimize your genes in a while. But before this, I would like to announce new personnel appointments."

Hearing his words, everyone quietened down as well.

Han Xiao tilted his head toward Hila, saying, "From today onward, the Black Star Guards will be formally established, selecting the Calamity Grade Supers to be part of it. This is an elite combat team that takes orders solely from me. With regards to officer rankings, Hila will serve as the first captain of the Black Star Guards. Does anyone have any objections?"

While the Beyond Grade A did not require bodyguards, they would always have an elite force under them that was well-known. For example, Heber had his Vanguard Officials, Austin had the Forbidden Sorcerers, Psyker had his Grand Priests, and Ames had... uh... her Black Star Army?

Because Beyond Grade As usually did not deign to personally act, only serving as deterrence, Han Xiao also planned to establish a small elite team that would be used to act in most situations. A Beyond Grade A Super had their own dignity and should not move so easily.

Hila stepped forward and faced everyone with a passive expression. "Who agrees? Who wishes to object?"

While she had only been in the army for a few months, most of the old Officers recognized her and would not have any issues. As for those that had joined later, they recognized her for her identity as the disciple of Dragon Emperor Ames and naturally did not doubt her strength.

Seeing the situation, Hila slowly nodded and returned to standing behind Han Xiao without a single word.

Han Xiao tilted his hand as he asked, "Feidin, would you be interested in joining the Black Star Guards as well?"

While Feidin's status in the army had been more of a guest, after months of getting along, Han Xiao felt that their relationship should have improved, and they were ready to take things to the next level... inviting him to become a direct officer under him.

Feidin thought for a while before revealing a warm smile. "Alright."

This guy is finally mine... Han Xiao secretly exclaimed to himself before turning back to look at the rest of the officers. He then picked a couple more battle-hardened Calamity Grade officers for his elite forces—one of which was Marian.

The Black Star Guards had a total of four members, which could be considered barely established. This was just a prototype, as he would recruit more once his status as a Beyond Grade A was publicized to the Star Field and they recruited more experts.

After finishing all his official matters, Han Xiao then activated the Evolution Cube, performing genetic optimization for all the officers at once. As long as the energy output of the Evolution Cube was adjusted, multiple people could be optimized at the same time.

Once all of that was finished, Han Xiao dispersed the crowd before locking himself in the machinery modification room. He began to create his Beyond Grade A combat equipment. This was the most important task at present, as strength was still fundamental. Other matters would be placed behind the priority of restoring his combat capability.

His mechanical army, mechanical suit, weapons, and so on needed to be remanufactured and updated with his Beyond Grade A class level.

...

"He's already achieved Beyond Grade A..."

Aroshia returned to her home, and Risda emerged in midair, saying, "He has the ability to save our race now. Aroshia, go talk to him."

However, Aroshia slowly shook her head. "We've got to at least wait for him to pass this current hurdle and for the Black Star Army to stabilize, else he won't help. There's no harm in waiting a while longer."

"We've already waited for a long time, and thinking of my comrades being oppressed by Manison, I really don't wish to wait any longer!" Risda was a little unsatisfied. "I can see that Black Star has always been trying to put us off."

But Aroshia blandly replied, "I don't think so. Just the two of us are enough to give Black Star the motivation to deal with another Beyond Grade A."

She had already regained her memories and was now the combination of her three personalities within her mind. She was still her, but she was no longer so ignorant.

"If you're not willing, I'll look for a time to talk to him," Risda said. "There must be a way somehow."

Risda then severed the connection, disappearing in midair.

...

The Black Star Army's silence did not result in the excitement of the Star Field dying down but in fact gave them a mysterious vibe, attracting even more attention from others. Practically everyone was guessing that Black Star should have certain problems that did not allow him to speak up, but he could not remain silent forever.

As the news continued to spread and Han Xiao's influence stewed even more, in an area where no one knew what was going on, many things were happening.

In the presence of this undercurrent, another half a month passed.

Han Xiao exited his machinery modification room—he had built the prototype of his new army.

Chapter 767: Announcement (1)

In Han Xiao's personal factory, dozens of army boxes were lined up in a row with a few hundred different mechanical soldiers lining up neatly. They were arranged from tall to short and light to heavy as though it was an exhibition.

"Seventy percent of the soldiers weren't changed, and the new blueprints that came from Sardeem's collection were mostly giant soldiers. Another portion of blueprints are those newly merged blueprints. Although there isn't an upgrade in my knowledge, I managed to unlock new blueprints after becoming a Beyond Grade A and got a good amount of new blueprints from gambling..."

Han Xiao placed his hands behind his back and studied the different models.

A new army was usually created by using the new skills that he obtained after reaching Beyond Grade A to forge more powerful machines with better attributes. The introduction of new models was not that important.

Because of the lack of time, Han Xiao did not have the chance to learn any new knowledge, and the majority of his mechanical soldiers were still old models. However, their attributes were far stronger than his previous army. With the increase in his Intelligence, the bonus from [Supreme Prestige] and [Mechanical Genius] largely increased the attributes of his mechanical army.

However, even if they were old models, these mechanical soldiers were the elite products that had gone through many generations of improvements. The ordinary soldiers were all rebuilt, and all his elite forces such as the Oathkeepers and Phantoms were also reconstructed. At the same time, he had plenty of new additions such as the giant soldiers, Planetary Obliteration Group, Black Knights, and so on.

As for the weapons with large firepower, Han Xiao had modified the various satellite cannons. Because he had not learned the relevant knowledge, he was not able to construct a true Planetary Obliteration Cannon. However, the satellite cannons that he modified had comparable strength to the Ice Age Star Freezing Cannon. Furthermore, its penetrative and explosive abilities were even more powerful. Although it would be impossible to destroy a planet now, destroying a continent wouldn't be a problem.

With his firepower reaching the Beyond Grade A level, Han Xiao also built a new mechanical suit to replace his Mountain Ape suit.

The new mechanical suit had a black theme with some yellow accents. It looked extremely sturdy and was like a growling beast.

The mechanical suit was made from precious alloys, and the nano transformation technology was further strengthened to improve its self-repairing capabilities. The strength of the mechanic suit was its movement speed. It was equipped with a high speed hyperdrive thruster that enabled Han Xiao to swiftly avoid enemy attacks in battle. As for its firepower, apart from the normal energy and close-range weapons, it also had a psionic energy furnace to increase damage.

The name of this mechanical suit was Battle Tiger. The Mountain Ape suit was suitable for those at level 165, and this 'Battle Tiger' suit was level-215 orange equipment. Its attributes were increased in every way. Its armor was over 100,000 points, and its energy was over 10,000 points. Before obtaining new knowledge and forging a new trump card suit, Han Xiao planned to temporarily use this suit to increase his strength.

The mechanical suit came with many additional abilities, including a variety of close combat abilities and a sound wave attack called 'Tiger Roar'. It was even more powerful than the Mountain Ape suit in terms of violence and was far superior to the Mountain Ape suit in terms of armor and damage. This was a killing machine suitable for many different battlefields.

These machines have all reached Beyond Grade A. As long as there's enough of them, I will be able to fight normally.

There were other larger machines that he had not had the time to build, such as the Eternal Light and a new base. When he activated [Secondary Dimension Army], he would be able to break through the limits of the compressed orb. At that time, he would be able to carry an entire satellite fortress and different super-sized machines with him.

Boom!

Right at that moment, the room trembled slightly.

"Is there a problem?"

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he contacted Phillip.

"What happened?"

"Someone forcefully broke through the defensive line of the headquarters and landed on the satellite base. I will now send you images of the satellite, hum..."

The next moment, the image of the satellite appeared before him. A man broke through from the barricade of the battleships and landed on the surface of the satellite, resulting in an alarm being set off. The warriors of the army then flooded out and surrounded the man.

Upon seeing the appearance of this individual, Han Xiao was slightly shocked.

"Hadavy?"

"Master, hum... your Guards Regiment have rushed over already. Are you going to take care of matters personally?"

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and the Battle Tiger suit transformed into a bracelet on his arm. He then opened the door of the workshop and walked out.

"Tell Hila to not let him escape. I will go over immediately."

At the same time, a few hundred spaceships were floating around the Black Star Army headquarters and recording the scene before them.

These spaceships were the news spaceships from the various galactic media groups. In order to get first-hand information of Black Star's true strength, they had been waiting there for half a month. However, they had been blocked out by the defensive fleet of the Black Star Army and could only float in space nearby.

When a Calamity Grade Super appeared and broke through the defensive line of the Black Star Army fleet, the commotion immediately drew the attention of the galactic reporters, and they all became energetic.

The rumors said that Black Star had already become a Beyond Grade A Super, but there were still those who dared to provoke him. These reporters could keenly sense that this was the chance to dig up some interesting news. As such, they all gathered around to watch.

"I know this person. He's Hadavy, and he had appeared in the secret war before. He is someone on the Bloodshed Land's side."

"Could this be provocation from the Bloodshed Land? Are they announcing war with the Black Star Army publicly‽"

"There will be a nice show to watch!"

In the entrance of the satellite, the soldiers formed three layers of encirclement around Hadavy with numerous cannons being aimed at him. Hadavy was not flustered in the slightest and said, "I am here to see your Army Commander. Since your fleet wouldn't let me in, I could only barge in."

Because Han Xiao had issued the order that he would not meet anyone before going into seclusion, all miscellaneous issues had been handed over to Sylvia and Herlous. The defensive fleet had strictly followed Han Xiao's orders, and Hadavy did not manage to get an exception after reporting his name. He had thus barged in.

At this moment, a beam of red light appeared in front of Hadavy.

"Don't move," Hila said with a frosty expression.

Hadavy paused for a moment and sized Hila up. "Who are you?"

"Captain of the Black Star Guards, Hila."

"Black Star Guards?" Hadavy's eyes lit up.

Chapter 768: Announcement (2)

This was the first time that Hadavy had heard of the Black Star Guards. However, this was not the first time that he had seen Hila.

There was a period of time when Han Xiao had taken Hila around the various frontline battlefields. Before leaving the Bloodshed Land, Hadavy had once looked through Hila's file, and this was the first time that he had met her.

He looked around the surroundings, and the densely packed warriors blocked all avenues of escape.

"Where is Black Star? I want to see him!" Hadavy shouted.

"Our Army Commander isn't someone you can meet whenever you want to," Hila then replied coldly. "Hadavy, you have provoked our headquarters. You'd better surrender yourself right now."

Upon hearing that, Hadavy looked at Hila and said provocatively, "And if not? Are you going to catch me?"

Hu!

Hila lost her patience and immediately took action. Blood-red energy gushed out from her body and smashed into Hadavy's chest. It sent him flying into the sky, and a small red shockwave exploded.

The light faded, and Hadavy floated in midair with a solemn expression on his face.

As a well-known Beyond Grade A seed in the Shattered Star Ring; ordinary Calamity Grade Supers would not be able to harm him at all. However, Hila's casual attack made him feel a wave of deathly energy invading his body. A portion of his cells became inactive, and he felt as though his life force was being absorbed.

Although the damage was not large, the destructive force of the red-haired woman before him was something that an ordinary Calamity Grade Super would not be able to match up to.

After obtaining the benefits of the Evolution Cube, she had experienced an obvious rise in combat strength, and her destructive force had become much more frightening. The death energy that she gave out could reduce the activity of her target and inflict special damage. Even Hadavy was not able to block it completely and had to treat her seriously.

Bang!

Hila's stomp generated a sonic boom, and she shot toward the sky. The dense death energy was like a tsunami crashing down on Hadavy.

The two collided in midair, and an intense battle broke out. Rings of visible energy waves exploded forth, and the warriors by the side did not interfere in the battle between them. They left the battlefield to those two and watched from the side.

A portion of the Calamity Grade officers who were currently present watched the battle by the side and had no intention of interfering.

"Sylvia, do we really not need to intervene?" a Calamity Grade officer asked.

Sylvia shook her head and said, "His Excellency Black Star wants to set up the Black Star Guards. It isn't to protect him but to let the various organizations know that he has an elite force under his command. Hadavy is a powerful fellow, and Hila will be able to gain a great amount of fame as long as she doesn't lose to him. This will be the first impression the world has of the Black Star Guards."

"But if she loses, won't..."

"Someone personally chosen by my teacher won't lose so easily."

The scene of Hila and Hadavy fighting was recorded by all the galactic reporters in the surroundings. This group of reporters watched the fight unblinkingly as they wrote their draft, recording the entire process of how Hadavy charged into the Black Star Army headquarters and was stopped by the Black Star Guards under Black Star.

Boom boom boom!

Both of them were Calamity Grade Supers, and the impact of their battle was not small. Hila trapped Hadavy in the center and unleashed her death energy on him.

Hadavy's body hardening Esper Ability had been developed to a perverse level. Despite that, plenty of scars were still left behind on his body. It was not that he did not have the ability to escape, but he naturally would not escape since he was there to meet Han Xiao.

The dense, red waterfall of death energy knocked Hadavy out of the sky, and he crashed onto the alloy ground.

Boom!

Hadavy hurriedly got up and avoided Hila's follow-up attack while looking back at Hila with a strange gaze. Hila's attack would not threaten his life but made him seem extremely pathetic. Her strength had truly shocked him.

The Black Star Army had a few Calamity Grade officers. In the past, Lagi was the only one who could give Hadavy some pressure, so Hila was the second.

Black Star has more and more experts under him, Hadavy thought to himself.

What a powerful body. Hila frowned.

Death energy then surrounded her body as though she was on fire.

Hadavy's expression turned solemn, and he got into a defensive position. His muscles then bulged up like steel.

The army members watching the battle by the side also began backing off. They knew that the following attack would create a large shockwave, and they might be injured if they were to close.

Just as Hila was about to launch her attack, a deep voice sounded from behind the crowd.

"Hila, that's enough."

Everyone looked over and saw Han Xiao floating over slowly with an immense pressure bearing down on everyone present. The entire place fell silent, and even a falling needle could have been heard.

Everyone's gaze was locked on Han Xiao.

Upon hearing those words, Hila snorted coldly and retracted her death energy.

The crowd then opened a path, and Han Xiao walked in front of Hadavy. "You want to see me?"

In truth, Han Xiao had arrived a long time ago and allowed both Hila and Hadavy to fight for a short while before stopping them.

Just as Sylvia had suspected, since he had set up the Black Star Guards, he had to help Hila build up her prestige in the Star Field. Hadavy was a classic meat shield, and his attacking strength was low. With Hila's current strength, she would be able to fight Hadavy for some time without losing, and this was the best chance to build up her prestige.

The galactic reporters by the side all grew excited. Ever since the rumors began to spread in the outside world, this was the first time that Black Star had appeared in public. Thus, all their attention was placed on him.

"You finally came out!" Hadavy's eyes lit up. This was the result that he wanted to see. "Do you still remember me?"

"How can I forget you?" Han Xiao said with a tinge of interest. "Aren't you a member of Bloodshed Land? Are you coming to my headquarters to provoke me?"

"I have already left Bloodshed Land, and I am here to represent myself only," Hadavy explained.

"Oh... then what do you want?"

"I wish to issue you a challenge!" Hadavy suddenly said loudly. "I am willing to use myself as the stakes for this battle!"

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment, and doubt could be seen in his eyes.

"What exactly do you want?"

"If I lose, I will join the Black Star Army and fight for you like I once fought for Bloodshed Land. If I win..." Hadavy paused for a moment. "If I win, I want you to be my subordinate."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao could not help but laugh in his heart. He had already seen through Hadavy's true thoughts.

This fellow has probably come here because I became a Beyond Grade A Super. For him to insist on challenging me even after knowing that I have become a Beyond Grade A Super, he probably has two motives. First, he wants to spar with a Beyond Grade A Super and thinks that I won't kill him on account of the fact that we are old opponents. Second, he wants to join me after losing to me.

Hadavy had always wanted to become a Beyond Grade A Super, and his heart was becoming itchy after witnessing Han Xiao becoming a Beyond Grade A. Thus, Hadavy wanted to join Han Xiao so that he could seek help from him. However, although Hadavy was tempted by such a thought, he was not willing to directly join the Black Star Army because of his pride. He did not want to lower his head before his old opponent directly and thus chose to put on a show and use the excuse of losing the battle to join the Black Star Army.

Defeat was not humiliating to Hadavy, but lowering his head was.

After thinking for a moment, Han Xiao nodded and agreed without exposing Hadavy.

When they were opponents, Hadavy was truly annoying and was a sh*t stirrer. However, if this meat shield wanted to join him, he would be a rare treasure in Han Xiao's eyes. After all, there were very few Beyond Grade A seeds.

Putting on a show to gain a powerful fighter—such a deal was very much worth it.

Furthermore, Han Xiao felt that he could make use of this chance to display his strength to the Star Field. The influence of him becoming a Beyond Grade A could only be utilized if he admitted it personally.

He had already constructed a new army, and he was able to display the strength of a Beyond Grade A. Furthermore, the Tyrant would not allow him to drag things on for too long.

Han Xiao was extremely clear about the thoughts of his enemy. If he continued dragging on as such, Klent would then announce to the world that he did not dare to reveal his strength because he was afraid of Heber. They would then be able to suppress his influence while boosting the Tyrant's prestige.

He had stayed silent for half a month already, and Klent was already showing signs of doing so. He decided to avoid such a situation before Klent took action.

Han Xiao shook off all these thoughts and looked at Hadavy. "Come."

Boom!

Hadavy stomped on the alloy ground and shot toward Han Xiao's chest like a cannon.

The muscles on his arms bulged up, and an explosive strength burst forth.

However, Hadavy's fist was stopped ten centimeters before Han Xiao, and the immense strength of the attack generated a powerful gust of wind. However, Han Xiao did not even blink.

At this moment, his arm, which was covered in the Battle Tiger suit, grabbed onto Hadavy's throat. Hadavy's powerful attack could not even shake Han Xiao's arm, and Hadavy was not able to move forward even an inch after being grabbed by Han Xiao's arm.

Advancing to Beyond Grade A and the boost from the Evolution Cube had largely increased Han Xiao's attributes and allowed him to completely suppress a Calamity Grade Super. Even Hadavy, who was famous for his body's strength, was not an opponent for Han Xiao.

"This..." Hadavy's eyes narrowed.

Before he could even react, the mechanical suit on Han Xiao's arm began spinning around rapidly and sent a powerful shockwave into Hadavy's body through his arm.

The special sound wave attack flowed through Hadavy's skin and echoed in his flesh and bones. Hadavy heard a ringing sound as though all the noise in the world had been pumped into his ears.

Tiger Roar!

With the target's body as a medium, the special shockwave attack would pass through all forms of armor and echo within the target's body. If this attack was used in a vacuum, it would only be effective in close-range battle. This was an attack that Han Xiao had created by mimicking Stephanie's Esper Ability.

"Pu!" Hadavy spat out a mouthful of blood. Because it was not True Damage, he was not immune to it.

Following which, Han Xiao slammed him into the ground.

Bang!

A crater was created, and Hadavy was stuck in the crater.

Not waiting for him to get up, Han Xiao placed his hands together, and his body lit up with brilliant bolts of electricity. The Mechanical Force that he gave out then combined with the alloy ground.

Boom!

The next moment, the alloy ground sprang into action, and the alloy ground transformed into a whirlpool to trap Hadavy in the center. The alloy ground then began spinning upward and formed a small spinning mountain.

Hadavy could not move an inch.

"Pa!" Han Xiao then clapped his hands, and two cannons were revealed behind him. The barrels of the cannons were aimed straight at Hadavy. If Han Xiao shot at Hadavy, who was currently in the air, his cannon would shoot toward outer space and would not destroy the headquarters.

The barrels of the cannons lit up, and the frightening energy being gathered made everyone's hair stand on end.

"My destructive force isn't the same as before," Han Xiao said slowly. "You may become paralyzed if these two cannons hit you. Admit defeat."

Hadavy gulped in horror, and his heart was shaken.

He had challenged Han Xiao because he wanted to verify the difference between the Beyond Grade A Black Star and the Black Star from before. In the end, he realized that the gap between them had widened to the point where he did not have the ability to make Han Xiao get serious.

Was this the difference in a Beyond Grade A? Hadavy felt his heart burning.

"I... admit defeat." Hadavy took a deep breath and admitted his loss.

Han Xiao had already expected this and said, "Hila, bring him down."

Clank!

The alloy mountain then collapsed. and Hadavy fell to the ground. Hila immediately walked forward and slapped a pair of electromagnetic handcuffs on his wrists. The handcuffs were not very useful and were only for show. Hadavy was then led into the headquarters of the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao then turned around and looked at the numerous spaceships in the surrounding area. With a simple shake of his head, he connected to the quantum network.

The reporters on the spaceship were currently recording the scene before them and writing about how Han Xiao had easily taken care of Hadavy. All of a sudden, Han Xiao's face appeared on every screen in the spaceships, and all the reporters were startled.

Following which, Han Xiao's voice sounded on the screen.

"I know that all of you have been lingering in the vicinity to hear me admit the recent rumors. Yes, I am already a Beyond Grade A. Please help me spread the news around the entire Star Field!"

After saying what he wanted, Han Xiao's face disappeared from the screen, and the screens returned to normal.

The jaws of the reporters dropped, and they finally snapped back to reality. They immediately jumped to the window of the spaceship and looked toward the Black Star Army satellite, only to see Han Xiao turn around and walk back into the headquarters.

"He admitted it! Black Star admitted it personally!"

All the reporters were overjoyed. After camping for such a long time, they had finally gotten some exciting news.

An official announcement was completely different from rumors being spread around. Rumors were like sparks to ignite the flames of curiosity in the Star Field, but Han Xiao's admission was like pouring hot oil on top of the fire!

The influence of a new Beyond Grade A would reach the peak in a single step!

Chapter 769: Huge Sensation!

Hadavy was led to a room by Hila and tied to a chair. Hila stood with her arms folded by the side, staring coldly at him.

"Wait here. Black Star will arrive in a while."

Hadavy did not struggle as well. After quietly sitting for a while, he seemed to feel that the atmosphere was a little awkward. He looked at Hila and asked, "What's your Esper ability? I've been roaming around the Shattered Star Ring for so many years, yet I haven't heard of you. Someone like you would not be able to mask the news. Which civilization are you from?"

Hila did not even bother to reply, keeping a passive expression.

Seeing that she had no interest, Hadavy could only cough dryly. "Seems like you don't like to converse."

This time, the door opened, and Han Xiao walked in, smiling. "She's from my hometown; we're both from Planet Aquamarine. Because she was learning under Ames, she only appeared recently to help me with my matters."

"The Dragon Emperor's disciple?" Hadavy was stunned, and the look he shot toward Hila changed, filled with admiration and envy.

Planet Aquamarine, a surface civilization, could actually give rise to people like Hila and Black Star. This intrigued Hadavy.

Ka-la!

Moving his hand, Han Xiao freed Hadavy from the restraints. He suddenly had a thought, saying, "Ok, you may leave now."

Hadavy was given another shock, and his mouth gaped open as he said, "You're letting me go?"

"That's right." Han Xiao smiled. "No matter what, we've fought so many times, and I respect your abilities. This time, I'm letting you go. The bet can be nulled."

"No no no..." Hadavy immediately stammered. "I'm a man who keeps his word. Since I've lost, I must accept my promise and work for you."

"Well, such a strong Super like you would not agree to simply being someone's subordinate in such a manner," Han Xiao replied, half-seriously and half-jokingly. "I might have reached the Beyond Grade A level, but to peak-level Calamity Grades such as you, I have my respect and will not force you."

Hadavy was so anxious his face turned red. He had initially thought that his plan would be successful and that he could succeed in his gamble and join under Black Star's flag. He did not expect Black Star to actually reject him, with the reason so moving that even he could not reply to that.

"I... you..." Hadavy was speechless, unable to voice his thoughts.

Should he just say that he wanted to serve Black Star? Hadavy felt that this was a little shameful, and he could not bring himself to do it. However, if he just walked away, that would defeat his purpose of going there. In that instant, he fell into a dilemma, not knowing what to do.

Seeing this situation, Han Xiao smiled. "I won't mess with you any further. If you wish to join the Black Star Army, I'll welcome you with open arms. If you are trying to use such tricks to fool me, we can stop the discussion."

Hadavy's face turned red. "You already knew‽"

Upon having his thoughts seen through, he was so embarrassed that he wished to find a hole to hide in.

For Hila, who was standing by the corner with a passive expression, the corners of her mouth curled up into a barely discernible smile.

Han Xiao raised an eyebrow, leisurely saying, "In that case, I'll formally extend an invitation to you. Hadavy, my legion requires your strength. Are you willing to come under my banner?"

Hadavy found it hard to open his mouth at this time. His mouth seemed to be glued shut, and he applied all his Grade A level strength just to unlock his jaw.

"I... I am willing..."

After saying those three words, Hadavy felt as though his entire body had gone soft. The feeling was as though he had just finished ten consecutive gladiator matches.

"Good." Han Xiao nodded with a smile. "On behalf of my army, I welcome you."

Seeing that Han Xiao was no longer fooling around with him, Hadavy finally breathed a sigh of relief, putting down the embarrassment in his heart. "What role do you require me to take?"

Han Xiao thought about it before pointing to Hila. "You can join the Black Star Guards, which is under Hila."

With Hadavy having a well-known reputation, him joining the Black Star Guards would also increase their renown.

"Black Star Guards?" Hadavy stroked his chin before replying, "That's fine, but I have a request. I hope that you will be able to impart some of your experience in achieving Beyond Grade A to me..."

Han Xiao nodded before shaking his head. "Every Beyond Grade A has a different method for their promotion, and everyone has their own path. I'm unable to pass down my experience to you, but what I can do is spar with you, allowing you to feel the difference between your level and that of a Beyond Grade A to give you more inspiration."

"This..." Hadavy shook his head helplessly. "That works as well."

While this was a little different from his expectations, being able to spar with a Beyond Grade A was also what he wanted. He originally loved to squeeze his potential out through battles.

The average person could not give him much pressure, but facing Black Star would remind him of his fear of the beasts when he was young and weak. This sort of fear would be a catalyst for growth.

Han Xiao waved his hand, allowing Hila to take Hadavy to meet his new colleagues.

He now had a total of five guards, of which Hadavy, Feidin, and Hila were the strongest, all high-level Calamity Grades. The other two were Marian and a Pugilist named Deluno. Both of their combat capabilities were average, not extraordinary in the Calamity Grade, but it was good enough to be a mini-boss. In this manner, all his guards were actually elites.

After dealing with Hadavy, Han Xiao called Sylvia over to talk about the expansion of the Black Star Army.

Since he had personally announced the matter of reaching Beyond Grade A, he would have to start making some big moves, increasing his influence, and making more allies in the Star Field. His plan was to make the Black Star Army reach the level of a true Beyond Grade A force.

But before that, there was still another matter he needed to address.

"Sylvia, help me prepare a fleet. I'm going out."

"Noted. Where are you going, Teacher?"

Han Xiao paused, his tone strange.

"Floating Dragon."

...

The countless interstellar news outlets released the article about Han Xiao personally acknowledging that he had broken into the Beyond Grade A class. At its peak, ninety-five percent of the entire news channels in the Shattered Star Ring were occupied by news about this matter, setting off a new storm of public opinion.

Most of the official news sources had acknowledged this matter, making it a sure bet. During this period, almost all the media outlets in Shattered Star Ring were covering the topic. With so many media channels, this was far larger than compared to the rumor and word-of-mouth influence that had spread earlier. As long as the citizens had internet, there was no one that would not have heard of Han Xiao's name!

Similarly, this sensational news had also been shared by the media of other Star Fields, and their organizations had also learned that the Shattered Star Ring had given birth to yet another Beyond Grade A Super!

The player forums almost detonated from this situation. Although Han Xiao's name often dominated the forums, it was because of the players' discussion. That day, even the players from other Star Fields could also see their news channels commenting on Han Xiao's name!

Those belonging to other Star Fields were shocked. At Version 3.0, players had yet to cross between Star Fields. In their eyes, each Star Field was currently an independent server. Now, the NPC character from the Shattered Star Ring had actually 'broken' this barrier due to his fame!

Since the previous versions, Han Xiao had constantly established his main storyline character position in the Shattered Star Ring. The players from the other Star Fields also knew of his name. This wave of public opinion had generated a strong interest within the player base. Not only was Han Xiao filling up the screen in the Shattered Star Ring news channel, his name was also within the forum channels of the other Star Fields. On all channels, he was within the top three topics.

The official news channels also had their own rules, and the various great organizations of the Shattered Star Ring responded appropriately.

...

The Purple Crystal Civilization was extremely happy now.

They had seen the potential revealed by him more than seven years ago and decided to hedge their bets on him. Finally, Black Star had stepped into the realm of the Beyond Grade A, and the Purple Crystal Civilization now had a Beyond Grade A Super just like Klent. Within the seven Star Cluster level civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring, only two of them had such powerful allies.

Their bet had truly paid off!

Furthermore, Black Star had only spent around twenty years to reach the Beyond Grade A rank, with his total age not even being close to fifty yet. With the lifespan of a Beyond Grade A Super, he was considered an infant, and this spoke volumes of his potential.

The moment Han Xiao admitted his promotion in person, the Purple Crystal Civilization had adopted a variety of measures such as adding a huge investment to the Black Star Army as well as putting out more favorable policies and resource conditions for them. They were committed to building a more stable relationship with Han Xiao as an alliance.

At the same time, the Purple Crystal Civilization also issued announcements to the entire Star Field through their media channels.

"In the name of the Civilization, we congratulate Black Star for reaching the Beyond Grade A rank!"

This sort of behavior expressed their attitude to the entire Star Field and conveyed a message that their relationship was extremely stable. Those outside parties who wanted a share of the pie should just save their energy and get lost.

Godora was unwilling to be left behind and followed suit by having Serbia The Fifth coming out to explain Han Xiao's role in saving Godora, as well as emphasizing that he was the recipient of the Golden Gal Badge. Finally, he represented all Godorans in congratulating Han Xiao on his advancement before revealing that he was planning to add a celebratory festival named Black Star Day to thank Han Xiao for all that he had done for them.

Were it any other civilization that had done this, it would have sounded very much like boot-licking. However, Godora was different, as their ties with Han Xiao ran extremely deeply. Be it the eradication of DarkStar or the Discrimination Transformation Movement, it had a huge impact for their entire civilization. Thus, a festival to thank Han Xiao was nothing extraordinary.

Purple Crystal and Godora quickly took their stand, and to jump on the bandwagon, hundreds of civilizations began to congratulate Han Xiao. This was as though they were attempting to form a trend. Most of these galaxy-level civilizations were half-allies that had chosen the Black Star Army, and they had allowed the army to set up bases on their planets. At this moment, they scrambled to speak up, as though afraid that others would not know they were in an alliance with Black Star.

The behavior of these civilizations was actually understandable. Purple Crystal was the boss of this Star Cluster and thus got the ball rolling. The other civilizations jumped on the bandwagon in order to have a good relationship with this Beyond Grade A faction, but this crazy chain left those on the sidelines speechless and shocked.

The entire Colton Star Cluster was basically standing behind Black Star, shouting and congratulating him. An entire Star Cluster was celebrating for one man!

In such a situation, those on the sidelines could not even reply due to their shock.

The reputation of Black Star in the Star Cluster was so shocking!

Even when the other Beyond Grade As had advanced, they did not receive such a resounding celebration!

At this moment, the entire Star Field remembered the name Black Star. Just like the other four, he turned into an icon of the Shattered Star Ring in everyone's minds, the Fifth Beyond Grade A Seat!

However, it was at this juncture that unexpected events started to appear, allowing the public opinion to skyrocket to unpresented levels.

The Tyrant Heber and Star Pupil Psyker both openly made a declaration of battle toward Black Star!

Heber's reason was because of the secret war. Since the Purple Crystal also possessed a Beyond Grade A now, he would personally act. Because both Beyond Grade As were fighting for different sides, there was no problem with that.

However, Psyker's reasoning caused a huge outburst.

He openly admitted the existence of the Evolution Cube, announced that Black Star had taken the Evolution Cube from his hands, and requested for Black Star to return it!

The Evolution Cube is now in Black Star's hands? Two elder Beyond Grade As are challenging a newborn Beyond Grade A‽

Those two pieces of news caused a stir.

The entire Star Field burst into an uproar!

The Beyond Grade As... were going to fight openly‽

How long had it been since that last happened!

...

Just as the major organizations and those on the sidelines were shocked at all the ongoing news, Han Xiao had taken his spaceship and arrived on Floating Dragon Island.

Chapter 770: Independence

A large fleet appeared not too far away from Floating Dragon Island with Han Xiao's spaceship being at the very front.

Aurora was seated in the pilot's seat with Han Xiao standing behind her with his arms crossed.

Floating Dragon now had three different islands and a second field team in charge of guarding Floating Dragon. Looking out at the scenery, Han Xiao could not help but lament to himself.

"I haven't been back for quite some time, and the changes are truly great. So many years have gone by in just a blink of an eye. I still remember the first time I came to Floating Dragon…"

Du! Du!

Vilna's face appeared on his communicator, and she said, "Your Excellency Black Star, Her Excellency Dragon Emperor is waiting for you."

It seems like she knew that I would come and meet her… Han Xiao nodded.

The second field team opened a path and allowed the Black Star Army fleet to land on Floating Dragon Island.

"Black Star Guards follow me. The others remain here and await my orders," Han Xiao instructed and led Hila and the others onto Floating Dragon.

On the dock, Jenny and the other officers were already waiting for him.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

The various officers saluted him.

Although they had once been colleagues with Han Xiao, Han Xiao was now a Beyond Grade A Super, and his status in the galaxy far exceeded theirs. He was a figure who stood at the same level as the Dragon Emperor, and they could only look up to him.

Even Jenny, who had a terrible relationship with Han Xiao, also had her head lowered with a respectful appearance.

Aesop stepped out from the crowd and said with a complicated expression, "I knew that you would return. This day had to come eventually."

Han Xiao then looked around at the faces of his colleagues before looking back at Aesop. Shaking his head, he said, "Didn't you already start making preparations?"

"I just didn't think that it would be so sudden…" Aesop let out a sigh before turning around to lead the way. "Follow me. Ames is already waiting for you."

Han Xiao followed behind Aesop and entered the palace, only to see Ames seated on top of a floating throne with a calm expression on her face.

"You're here. Black Star, I have been waiting for you," Ames said as though she had already expected his arrival.

Han Xiao stood a few meters away, and Aesop's group walked behind Ames. At this moment, there seemed to be an invisible barrier separating the two groups.

Neither of them spoke immediately; they looked at each other silently instead. The Black Star and Floating Dragon officers who were by the side all could not help but gulp as their hearts tensed up.

The officers of both sides were aware of Han Xiao's intentions and could not help but feel nervous upon seeing the tense atmosphere. They were afraid that the two Beyond Grade A Supers would start fighting because of some disagreement.

The new member of the Black Star Guards, Hadavy, was probably the only exception. He was currently sizing Ames up carefully, looking as though he was eager to test her strength.

After a silent standoff of over a minute, Ames shifted her gaze toward Aurora and Hila, who were beside Han Xiao, and asked, "How have both of you been over the past few months?"

Aurora did not dare face Ames' gaze at this moment and lowered her head with guilt.

"Fine," Hila replied.

Ames showed care and concern for her two disciples but ignored Han Xiao completely. Han Xiao was not too bothered by this and watched silently by the side.

The teacher and disciples chatted for a while before Ames changed the topic. "Are you two going to stand on his side?"

Hila and Aurora's expressions changed slightly, and everyone felt their hearts tightened up slightly.

Before waiting for them to reply, Han Xiao waved to his Black Star Guards and said, "Hila, leave with them. Let me talk to Ames alone."

Hila heaved a sigh of relief. She was not afraid of facing powerful enemies, but she did not wish to be sandwiched between her teacher of ten years and Han Xiao.

Ames tacitly approved of the departure of the Black Star Guards, and upon seeing this, Aesop had no choice but to take the officers of Floating Dragon away as well.

Aesop felt that it was extremely normal for Black Star to seek independence. If he was Ames, he would not stop Black Star but provide his support instead. However, Ames was not like him and tended to act in a willful manner. Furthermore, Black Star was the subordinate who she placed the greatest importance on, and Aesop was worried that Ames' willfulness would ruin matters.

Only Han Xiao and Ames were left behind in the main hall. Ames controlled her floating throne to land, and she walked forward to face Han Xiao with a complicated look in her eyes.

"When I first saw you, I never imagined that you will be standing at the same height as me one day."

Upon hearing that, the scene of how he met Ames floated up in Han Xiao's mind.

Ames had been high above at that time, capable of controlling his life and death with a single thought. In comparison, he had been a small grain of sand in her eyes. Ten or so years later, he was now able to stand face to face with her as equals.

"Anything is possible in this world," Han Xiao replied.

Ames smiled and said, "I know this feeling. A long time ago, I never imagined that I would become a Beyond Grade A Super either."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and did not say a word.

Pausing for a moment, Ames then asked, "Why are you here today?"

"There are three things."

"Three things?" Ames raised her brows. "What's the first?"

Han Xiao took out the Evolution Cube and said, "This treasure is in my hands. I am prepared to allow you and all the officers of Floating Dragon to enjoy the Evolution Cube."

Ames was a little surprised but did not reply immediately. She asked instead, "What's the second matter."

"I request to leave Floating Dragon and allow the Black Star Army to gain independence," Han Xiao said without the slightest bit of awkwardness.

"Humph, this is probably your true motive, right?"

Ames let out a soft sigh but wasn't angry. She was already mentally prepared for this day to arrive but still felt a tinge of discomfort when Han Xiao said it. She then said expressionlessly, "I have something to ask you."

"What is it?"

"Were you planning to leave me from the first day you joined Floating Dragon?"

Ames' gaze was locked firmly on Han Xiao. Ever since she viewed the Black Star Army headquarters a few years ago, she had known that she was not suitable to be Han Xiao's leader. She just wanted to be certain of Han Xiao's thoughts.

"Yes," Han Xiao replied honestly. From the very beginning, he had treated Floating Dragon as a jumping board. Even if saying so would make Ames angry, he did not intend to lie.

"I thought so." Ames shook her head, and a tinge of sadness could be seen in her eyes. "I am not a leader worth following for someone like you."

She had not felt this during the initial development of the Black Star Army, but as the prestige of the Black Star Army overshadowed Floating Dragon, she had understood that a legendary character like Han Xiao was not someone she could keep.

Ames did not hesitate in the slightest and did not bother trying to keep Han Xiao. She was not that weak and said with a resolute voice, "Alright. I understand. From today onward, Floating Dragon is Floating Dragon and the Black Star Army is the Black Star Army. You are no longer my subordinate."

A notification immediately popped up on his interface indicating that he left the Floating Dragon faction.

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

From this moment on, the Black Star Army was no longer a subordinate of Floating Dragon and was now an independent organization.

"What is the third matter?" Ames asked expressionlessly.

"I hope that the Black Star Army can form an alliance with Floating Dragon," Han Xiao said. "I hope that you will fight alongside me against Heber and Psyker."

Upon hearing that, Ames' face immediately became a little strange. She had already heard about the Beyond Grade A battle that shook the Shattered Star Ring. She was puzzled about Han Xiao's actions.

"Since you want my help, why did you choose independence? You know that I would definitely help you if you chose to remain in Floating Dragon."

Han Xiao smiled and said with a carefree tone, "I know. That's why I gave you a chance to choose."

Ames was stunned for a moment and immediately understood what Han Xiao meant.

The way she saw it, as long as Han Xiao chose to remain in Floating Dragon, he could tie Floating Dragon to him and ensure that she would help him to deal with his enemies for sure. However, Han Xiao did not choose to make use of his identity as a Floating Dragon officer but chose to request help after leaving Floating Dragon.

This meant that Han Xiao did not want to make use of her. If not, he could choose to borrow Floating Dragon's strength to deal with Heber and Psyker before gaining independence. It would be akin to making full use of her before leaving.

In truth, Ames had also considered such a possibility before their meeting. Even Ames herself did not know if she would have rejected Han Xiao if he had chosen such a route. The development of the situation was truly out of her expectations.

"Are you not afraid that I will reject you?" Ames suppressed the surprise in her heart and spoke calmly. "Your life will be in danger if you want to fight both of them alone. Aren't you afraid that you won't be able to pass this tribulation?"

Han Xiao smiled and said, "I believe that you won't reject me."

Ames' face then darkened, and she said coldly, "You are no longer my subordinate, and I haven't accepted your alliance. Do you really think that I care a lot about you, or do you think that you have some chips in your hands that I won't be able to reject? Do you want to make use of the Evolution Cube to persuade me? And go back on your word if I don't agree?"

"My promise is valid regardless of whether you form an alliance with me." Han Xiao shook his head. "That was something I brought up before leaving Floating Dragon. I am providing that benefit to you as an officer of Floating Dragon and do not plan to make use of it as a bargaining chip. You can treat it as my compensation to thank Floating Dragon for taking care of me."

Ames had a strange look in her eyes, and she sized Han Xiao up as though she did not recognize him. "You are not someone like that in my mind."

The way she saw it, the sequence of Han Xiao's requests was completely wrong. He chose to leave Floating Dragon before seeking help and did not wish to use the Evolution Cube as a bargaining chip for their alliance but compensation toward Floating Dragon.

This was akin to surrendering his advantage and leaving the decision in her hands.

"Why?" Ames asked. Han Xiao's current actions had overturned her impression of him.

Han Xiao smiled. "I just feel that there isn't a need for there to have so much scheming between us."

Ames' expression froze in place, and her breathing seemed to have stopped for a second.

She then looked at Han Xiao deeply and took two steps back. "I don't know if the words you have said are true or false, but I can at least see some sincerity."

Han Xiao's lips curled up slightly, and he said, "It seems like we have come to an agreement."

"I agree to your alliance." Ames' eyes shone before she slowly said, "Besides, I have long wanted to have a fight with Heber. Although you are a new Beyond Grade A Super, you definitely won't drag me down with your strength."

"Hahaha, you are still the Ames that I know!" Han Xiao raised out his hand to shake Ames' hand. "Alliance mate, please take care of me in the future."

Ames looked at Han Xiao's hand, which was floating in midair, and snorted.

"Humph, you used to call me Your Excellency Dragon Emperor but call me alliance mate now."

After saying that, she raised out her hand as well.

Both of them shook hands.

Their alliance was set up from this moment on.

After shaking hands, they let go, and Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

When they were shaking hands, Ames had squeezed hard as though she was throwing a tantrum. However, Han Xiao's physical defense was too high, and he did not feel much.

Han Xiao shook his head and looked at the door of the palace. "Still eavesdropping? All of you, come in."

Hila, Aesop, and the others walked out from behind the door with embarrassed looks on their faces.

They had all worried that Ames and Han Xiao would fall out with each other and did not go too far away. They had all been eavesdropping outside the door and were a little embarrassed since they had been caught. In actual fact, all of their actions could not possibly escape from the senses of a Beyond Grade A. It was just that Han Xiao and Ames could not be bothered with them.

Upon seeing the both of them resolving matters harmoniously, the atmosphere in the place became relaxed, and everyone heaved a sigh of relief.

Although the Black Star Army had left Floating Dragon, both parties had formed an alliance, and they were still allies. The barrier between both parties disappeared immediately, especially since the officers of both parties had a good relationship in the first place.

Aesop was extremely relieved that Ames did not lose control of her emotions, and the outcome was much better than what he had expected. For two Beyond Grade A organizations to form an alliance, they would be able to gain a huge advantage in the Shattered Star Ring, and it was extremely beneficial to both parties.

My prediction back then wasn't wrong. Ames will develop better with Black Star beside her, Aesop thought to himself. Back then, he had felt that Black Star would become the Dragon Emperor's right-hand man to support her to the next level. Although his guess was not wrong, he had gotten a small detail wrong. Black Star would not be the Dragon Emperor's right-hand man but an equal to the Dragon Emperor.

"Alright, since you are willing to work together with me, we have to decide how we should deal with Heber and Psyker," Han Xiao said.

"What are you prepared to do?" Ames said with excitement.

"It has been some time since they issued a challenge to me, but I have yet to give them a reply. It is time for me to give them a reply. Since they want to create trouble, we should muddy the waters further. I will issue a joint response with you and shake the Shattered Star Ring even more." Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

He could also make use of this opportunity to announce the independence of the Black Star Army and their alliance with Floating Dragon.

Han Xiao was sure that this would increase his influence to the next level!

"I thought that you'd ask me to keep this matter a secret and give them a good surprise," Ames replied.

"We won't be able to hide it from them, and there isn't a need to do so. Since they challenged us openly, we can also reply to them openly," Han Xiao said. "Since they want to be high profile, we shall accompany them in being high profile!"

Ames revealed a look of interest. "It sounds very fun."

As Hadavy and the others heard that, they immediately grew excited and were agitated to the point they had goosebumps. The Shattered Star Ring had five Beyond Grade A Supers, and four of them were involved in this battle. Only the Magus was left out, and he would probably run over to join the fun. If that was the case, this battle would involve all the Beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring!

This was a one in a hundred years event, and it would definitely go down in the annals of history.

Just thinking of the sight of the five Beyond Grade A appearing together made Hadavy's blood boil.

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly said, "Before that, I have to fulfil my promise."

After saying that, he took out the Evolution Cube and looked at Ames.

"Do I need to make any preparations?" Ames asked.

"You don't need to."

"Alright." Ames nodded.

Although she did not chase after strength, she was extremely curious about the Evolution Cube.

Opening the Evolution Cube, a wave of black particles surrounded Ames, and the gene evolution started.

Han Xiao looked at the other officers of Floating Dragon, and after seeing them nod, he controlled another new wave of black colored energy to evolve their genes.

Only Aesop waved his hands.

"Old man, don't you want to use the Evolution Cube?" Han Xiao asked with doubt.

"Don't need to worry about me." Aesop waved his hands. "I used it a few hundred years ago when this item was still in the ruins. If not for the fact that it was too large and I was too lazy to find someone to shift it away, it would have been mine."

Han Xiao truly did not know what to say.

…

The gene evolution continued for quite some time, and all the officers of Floating Dragon completed their evolution. Their strength experienced varying degrees of improvements, and they all had looks of joy on their faces. Only Ames was still being surrounded by the black particles.

After a few hours, Ames broke out of the 'cocoon' and experienced a huge change.

All the others had gone down to rest, and Han Xiao was the only one left in the hall. He was currently seated on Ames' throne and scrolling through the forums for entertainment. Upon seeing Ames exit, he walked forward to Ames with a look of curiosity.

"How do you feel?"

Ames did not reply, and her brows were furrowed as though she was trying to feel something. Her figure then disappeared suddenly.

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment and extended his senses to feel the undulations of space around him.

At his current level, apart from his five basic senses, he could detect other things such as radiation, energy waves, and so on.

After extending his senses, Han Xiao was stunned for a moment.

He could see Ames making circles around him in the Void Dimension.

"You are able to enter the Void Dimension?" Han Xiao asked with shock and entered the Void Dimension as well.

"It seems like this is my new ability," Ames said excitedly.

Floating Dragon Island was built on top of the skeleton of a Void Dragon, and Ames had consumed the Void Dragon Pith before. Thus, she had a trace of Void Genes in her, which was activated by the Evolution Cube.

Although they were not from the same Beyond Grade A race, they both had Void Genes, and a portion of their genes were similar.

After playing for a while, Ames left the Void Dimension and began testing her new strength.

"The effect of the Evolution Cube is truly amazing. The strength, range, and control of my Force Field have been increased, and my physique seems to have improved."

That is because your attributes have increased…

Han Xiao had some experience with this. Ames did not have an interface and could not see the changes in her body.

Chapter 771: You'd Better Not Run

After both parties formed an alliance, Floating Dragon changed their drifting trajectory and headed toward the headquarters of the Black Star Army. They would work together with Han Xiao during this period.

Since Ames had chosen to fight by Han Xiao's side, she naturally had to bring her personal weapon along. Floating Dragon had another two more islands, and using it to smash others would definitely be more painful.

Han Xiao then got Reynolds to inform the army's logistics department to modify some empty backup satellite fortresses. Han Xiao was prepared to give them to Ames so that she could use them as her weapon. After all, she could not always use her main camp as her weapon.

After using the Evolution Cube, everyone rested for a day before Han Xiao and Ames gathered all the officers together.

This time, it was to reply to the Tyrant's challenge.

Before announcing his response to the world, Han Xiao decided to contact the Tyrant privately.

The secret war had been fought for such a long time, and the two parties had not contacted each other before. The last time they had seen each other was more than ten years ago at the Tyrant's gathering. Back then, he had been only Ames' follower, and Heber had tried to recruit him.

Han Xiao did not have the Tyrant's communicator number, but Ames had it in her communicator. This time, he was going to borrow Ames' communicator to contact Heber, which Ames had no issues with.

Han Xiao then opened Ames' communicator and pulled out Heber's number from the blacklist. Because of Heber's pursuit, Ames had always blocked his number.

Han Xiao then sent a communication request to the Tyrant.

Beep beep!

After a few seconds, the communication request went through, and Heber's image appeared on the communicator.

"Ames? You are finally going to… Hmm? Black Star‽"

Heber immediately frowned. Ames' name appeared on his communicator, and he thought that Ames had finally thought things through and decided to agree to become his partner. However, he had never imagined that the call would be made by Black Star.

"Ames formed an alliance with you?" Heber immediately reacted.

Han Xiao only nodded.

Heber's eyes narrowed, and his expression remained emotionless.

For a few years, many organizations had been spreading rumors about the Black Star Army and Floating Dragon splitting up. When Han Xiao became a Beyond Grade A, Heber knew that both of them would definitely split up, and Heber was hoping that Black Star and Ames would become enemies as a result. The outcome that he did not want to see was the two of them becoming allies.

"It seems like the little tricks of those organizations weren't able to shake your relationship," Heber said calmly.

"You don't seem anxious at all." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"It makes no difference to me," Heber said. "Tell Ames that I will give her a final chance. As long as she stays out of this matter, I can ignore her. I will not show any mercy otherwise."

"Get your head out the clouds. I didn't ask you to show any mercy," Ames said coldly upon hearing those words.

Heber ignored her and said to Han Xiao while shaking his head, "Black Star, I gave you a chance a long time ago. It is a pity that you didn't treasure it and rejected my invitation. If you are contacting me to plead for mercy, it is too late. We are now enemies, and there isn't anything to talk about between us."

"I called you to respond to your challenge. Set a time and place," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

Through his Observer's Mark, Han Xiao knew that Psyker had contacted Heber privately and invited Heber to work together with him. However, the Tyrant rejected and insisted on dealing with Black Star alone but did not stop Psyker from going to view their battle. Thus, both parties had issued separate challenges.

Han Xiao also understood Heber's thoughts from the conversation between the two. Heber did not only want to take revenge but also want to establish his prestige with a new Beyond Grade A Super. Heber wanted to have as many people paying attention to this matter as possible and thus publicly set a time and invited the various organizations to watch the battle.

"Alright," Heber said resolutely. "The time will be set twenty days from now. The location will be in the desolate universe belt between the Colton Star Cluster and Seoul Star Cluster. I will announce the coordinates publicly."

Choosing a neutral region between the two made it convenient for Bloodshed Land to send out their army and create a confrontation between Purple Crystal and Klent. It was still equivalent to both the civilizations fighting a proxy war.

Heber set the date twenty days from then so that the news would be able to spread throughout the Star Field and attract more people to witness his battle with Black Star. However, he would not drag the battle on for too long as he did not want to give Han Xiao too much time to prepare. He also did not want the matter to die down and wanted to establish his prestige when Black Star's influence was at the peak.

If Black Star wanted to back out of the battle, Heber would not lose out either. Heber could just say that Black Star was afraid of him and did not dare appear for their battle. He would also be able to build up his prestige as well and have a reason to visit the Black Star Army headquarters.

"Alright, you'd better not run when the time comes," Han Xiao said without much hesitation.

Han Xiao then hung up without waiting for Heber to reply.

"This fellow is still as domineering as usual. How annoying," Ames said with her eyes narrowed and her force field energy being gathered in her palms. Every time she saw the Tyrant's annoying face, she had the urge to smash her Floating Dragon down on him.

"In any case, the time and location have been decided. We just have to show up when the time comes." Han Xiao looked at all the officers. "You lot heard the conversation, right? Announce it to the public in the name of the Black Star Army."

"Understood." Sylvia nodded and started a long-distance conference. As the Chief Administrative Official, public relations was her job.

"There's still twenty days…"

Han Xiao's eyes glimmered. It seemed like this would be all the time he had for preparations.

…

The challenge given out by the Tyrant and Star Pupil created a huge commotion in the Shattered Star Ring, but Black Star had not given an official response. Many individuals had their appetites whet and were looking forward to the development of the matter.

Because of the storm created by the battle, many Supers who wanted to join the Black Star Army controlled themselves and waited to observe what happened. Thus, there were not too many who applied to the Black Star Army during this period. However, Han Xiao was also aware about this and thus did not start his recruitment.

Seven days after the challenge was issued, the Black Star Army finally made a response.

Black Star accepted the challenge!

Not just that, the Black Star Army had also announced a shocking piece of news.

From that day on, the Black Star Army would leave Floating Dragon and gain independence!

Many organizations had intentionally spread rumors that led many to believe that the Black Star Army would cut off all ties with Floating Dragon after gaining independence.

However, the truth had shocked many. The Dragon Emperor Ames had actually chosen to form an alliance with Black Star and deal with the Tyrant and Star Pupil!

This was something that no one had expected. Black Star had to fight alone originally and face the challenge of the Tyrant and Star Pupil single-handedly. Many individuals could not help but break out in cold sweat for this newly ascended Beyond Grade A. However, the interference of the Dragon Emperor immediately leveled the playing field.

A total of four Beyond Grade A Supers had entered the fray!

This was like a stimulant that caused the entire Star Field to blow up with excitement!

Regardless of whether they were ordinary citizens or members of large organizations, everyone was extremely clear about one thing.

A huge show was about to erupt in the Star Field!

…

In the Palace of Hidden Spells, Austin looked through a report on his communicator and thought to himself, Black Star accepted the challenge officially? He's even taking the Dragon Emperor…

It was now a two-on-two battle, and the Shattered Star Ring had five Beyond Grade A Supers.

This meant that his presence would influence the direction in which this matter developed, and everyone else knew that as well.

"It seems like there will be people looking for me very soon." Austin shook his head.

Beep beep!

Just as he thought that, Psyker called him.

Austin let out a helpless chuckle and accepted the call, hanging up after chatting for a short while. Just when he hung up, another call arrived. It was Han Xiao this time.

"It has been a while since I last saw you. You didn't disappoint me indeed, Black Star."

"I actually have to thank you." Han Xiao smiled.

"Thank me for what?"

"If not for you telling me about information regarding the Evolution Cube, I may not have been able to obtain this item."

"Oh, I see." Austin smiled and said straightforwardly, "I know why you called. Psyker called me before this."

Han Xiao's eyes glimmered, and he did not beat about the bush. "Since you already know our intentions, what do you plan on doing?"

Both parties wanted to attract Austin to their side.

Austin's eyes narrowed, and he said, "Although I have some ties with Psyker, he never agreed to lend me the Evolution Cube. Now that he's lost the Evolution Cube and this chip is in your hands, are you prepared to use it in exchange for my help?"

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded. Austin was no fool, and there was no need for Han Xiao to waste his time explaining it to Austin.

Unexpectedly, Austin shook his head and said, "I am very willing to provide compensation for using the Evolution Cube, but I cannot agree to this matter."

Han Xiao's heart sank.

However, Austin added, "Don't worry, I don't intend to help Psyker either."

"You want to remain neutral?" Han Xiao was surprised.

Austin smiled and said, "The silent Shattered Star Ring has been stirred up again after so many years. How can I allow this wonderful show to end prematurely because of my interference? Hahaha!"

This darn old man just wants to watch the world burn… Han Xiao gritted his teeth.

Austin wanted to be a spectator and watch the show by the side. Furthermore, he felt that there would be a chance to use the Evolution Cube in the future based on Black Star's character. Thus, Austin was not prepared to join any side this time.

To a Beyond Grade A Super like him who was used to maintaining his neutrality, he was willing to give up some benefits to remain on the sidelines and watch the show. At his current level, he did not have to restrain his own personality and preferences.

Furthermore, both parties were Beyond Grade A Supers, and he would offend the other party if he chose to get involved. Austin was no fool; remaining neutral was the best choice for him.

Austin's attitude was resolute, and it would be impossible for Han Xiao to persuade him. Thus, Han Xiao hung up after a short casual conversation.

Although he did not manage to bring Austin to his side, Han Xiao was not too disappointed. He had never planned to have Austin on his side from the very start. It would be a pleasant surprise if he could succeed, but his failure was well within expectations. At the very least, Psyker also did not manage to pull Austin over to his side.

The situation was already clear, and the division of the Beyond Grade A Supers would not change. If that was the case, Han Xiao could only find aid from other organizations.

…

In the Crimson Dynasty embassy on the mother planet of the Klent Kingdom…

"Ah, Klent wants us to help them deal with Black Star?"

Within the office of the embassy, the Crimson Dynasty envoy Zoel looked at the Klent emissary with a smile.

"That's right. Black Star is in the Purple Crystal faction and killed a few dozen of our Calamity Grade Supers, dealing a huge blow to our high-level combatants. Now that Black Star is a Beyond Grade A Super, he will become a bigger obstacle to us. Our strength is limited, and we hope that the Crimson Dynasty can provide us with some aid," the Klent emissary said respectfully.

Zoel tapped his fingers on the table and looked at the party silently without talking.

He was the envoy that the Crimson Dynasty had sent to Klent, and he had been there for many years. He was also the envoy who Han Xiao had met at the Tyrant's gathering many years prior.

The life span of the Crimson Dynasty race was extremely long, and ten years was not much to them.

Over ten years ago, when Klent openly submitted to the Crimson Dynasty, Zoel had surfaced from the dark and built an embassy on the Klent mother planet. This represented the diplomatic ties between the Crimson Dynasty and Klent.

At the same time, he had the authority to mobilize any army that the Crimson Dynasty stationed in the Shattered Star Ring.

The three Universal Civilizations had their own secret factories in every Star Field, and the army that they had stationed in every Star Field was enough to start a war with two to three Star Cluster Civilizations at the same time.

The authority to control the secret armed force of the dynasty was enough to show how high a status Zoel had in the Shattered Star Ring. He was the individual with the highest authority in the envoy party.

Zoel thought for a while before saying, "I will consider Klent's request. Please leave for now."

Upon hearing that, the Klent emissary could only take his leave.

"Black Star…" Zoel muttered.

Zoel naturally had some understanding toward this new Beyond Grade A Super who had created a huge commotion in the Shattered Star Ring recently. In truth, Zoel had been constantly updating Black Star's shocking battle record in the dynasty's database over the past ten years.

Klent did not wish for Purple Crystal to have a Beyond Grade A ally and requested for the Crimson Dynasty to help them get rid of Han Xiao completely.

As an envoy of the Crimson Dynasty, Zoel's sights were naturally set at a very high level. It was not that he was being full of himself. Even if there were many Beyond Grade A pillars in the Crimson Dynasty, he would not underestimate other Beyond Grade A Supers. It was because he understood the strength of a Beyond Grade A Super that he knew that a Beyond Grade A should not be provoked easily.

It was not that Zoel did not want to help Klent deal with a local Beyond Grade A Super but that he had an interest in Black Star.

"He completed his Beyond Grade A journey in twenty years, and he is the first in history to accomplish such a feat. He still has a long life ahead of him, and his potential is immeasurable."

Furthermore, such a character had snatched the Evolution Cube, which was hidden by the Arcane Church.

Perhaps I can find the opportunity to interact with him.

As for the thoughts of Klent… As an envoy of the dynasty, why did he have to give a Star Cluster civilization an explanation?

Right at that moment, his communicator rang, and the face of his subordinate surfaced.

"Your Excellency Zoel, a special individual wishes to speak with you. Should I patch the communication through?"

"Who is the other party?"

"Black Star."

He actually took the initiative to find me?

Zoel paused for two seconds before nodding.

"Patch him through."

Chapter 772: Negotiations and Hidden Currents

After waiting for a while, Zoel's figure appeared on his communicator.

Han Xiao raised his brow.

Since the Crimson Dynasty embassy did not reject his communication request, it meant that they were interested in negotiating with him. This was a good opening as the Crimson Dynasty was an important part of his plans.

With a smile, Han Xiao said, "It has been many years since I last saw you, Envoy Zoel."

"That's right. It has been more than ten years since we last met, and you were participating in the Tyrant's gathering beside the Dragon Emperor back then. I still remember you trying to persuade Ames to join the Crimson Dynasty. Although you didn't manage to succeed, I have a very deep impression of you," Zoel said with a smile.

His good attitude toward Han Xiao was not only because Han Xiao was a Beyond Grade A Super but also because of how Han Xiao seemed to lean toward their dynasty.

"It turns out that you still remember." Han Xiao smiled. "Back then, I felt that it was extremely likely for the Crimson Dynasty to win the Flickering World, and history has proven my prediction correct."

Zoel's smile became brighter upon hearing that.

Over ten years ago, Black Star had predicted that the Crimson Dynasty would successfully take control of the Flickering World; Zoel's impression of Han Xiao immediately rose.

"You are truly able to see far ahead."

Of course, I doubt anyone can look further into the future than me… Han Xiao thought to himself.

This was the benefit of being familiar with the storyline. Before even eating today, he knew what kind of sh*t he would have tomorrow.

After pausing for a while, Han Xiao got to the purpose for his call.

"My thoughts have not changed since ten years ago, and the Black Star Army has already left Floating Dragon. I do not need to persuade anyone, and I can make the decision myself."

Zoel's eyes lit up, and he said, "If I didn't understand those words wrongly, you wish to join the Crimson Dynasty?"

"That is the reason for my call today."

Han Xiao nodded.

Because of his advancement, the Black Star Army had the right to be called a Beyond Grade A organization. However, the upper limit of his organization would be dependent on his resources and network. In the galaxy, the three Universal Civilizations were the largest possible backers, and he would be able to obtain a huge amount of resources as long as he joined one of them.

At the same time, he also needed a strong ally to protect the Evolution Cube. Psyker and the Arcane Church definitely would not give up on the Evolution Cube, and the Federation of Light might even choose to intervene. All the large organizations in the universe would have their eyes set on the Evolution Cube, and it was impossible for the Black Star Army, which was still at the Star Cluster level, to defend against all these ill intentions.

Among the three Universal Civilizations, the Crimson Dynasty was the most ideal ally to Han Xiao. He would be able to gain early access to the Flickering World and also foil Klent's plan to obtain victory in the secret war.

Those were all important factors affecting his benefits.

Of course, there was another reason beside this.

Han Xiao had been part of the Crimson Dynasty faction in his previous life, so he had more information regarding the storyline and chance encounters in the Crimson Dynasty. Among the three Universal Civilizations, he admired the Crimson Dynasty the most.

The history of the three Universal Civilizations could be traced back to the origin era, which was before the exploration era, and these three civilizations were not born during the same period. The Federation of Light was the oldest, followed by the Arcane Church, and then the Crimson Dynasty. The time period of their uprising was separated by a few thousand years.

The origin era was the most chaotic era and lacked historical records. At that time, there was not a single powerful civilization to unite the galaxy, and the different Star Fields were not connected to each other. All the civilizations were alone and explored the dark universe on their own.

At that time, the three Universal Civilizations had not reached their current heights, and there were other civilizations in their Star Field that exceeded them in terms of strength. After many years of development, they finally eliminated all their opponents in their various Star Fields and obtained the rights to rule over a Star Field. They then began to explore the desolate universe belts.

The Central Galaxy where the three Universal Civilizations were located was the starting point of these three civilizations, and they were all neighbors of one another. They naturally discovered each other's presence and wanted to get rid of each other. As such, war broke out between the three Universal Civilizations, and this became a turning point between the origin era and exploration era. The three Universal Civilizations then worked together to start a new era.

During the exploration era, the three Universal Civilizations fought each other while exploring the outside world. With the Central Galaxy as the core, the flames of war spread toward the outside with more and more Star Fields being discovered. During the process of exploring these new Star Fields, more and more civilizations were forced to join the battle, and the war became extremely ferocious. Many civilizations were destroyed because of this war.

The war that spread throughout the entire galaxy was extremely miserable. In fact, a few desolate universe belts in the present galaxy were originally Star Fields. They were Star Fields that had been reduced to a desolate universe belt because of the flames of war.

Back then, the three Universal Civilizations did not have their current strength, and there were a few powerful civilizations at the same level as them. The Evolutionary Civilization was one of them. If these civilizations had survived, they would very likely have become Universal Civilizations as well. However, it was a pity that they were wiped out during the wars in the exploration era. Only the Federation of Light, the Arcane Church, and the Crimson Dynasty had managed to survive. They then consolidated their authority and stopped the war to allow themselves to catch their breath.

After many years of peace, the Federation of Light and Arcane Church had begun to display signs of stagnation in their development. Only the Crimson Dynasty did not fall in times of peace and maintained their ambition and development.

Thus, Han Xiao thought highly of the Crimson Dynasty. A civilization full of ambition would always create the opportunity for development. Forming an alliance with the Crimson Dynasty would definitely give him a brighter future.

"Hmm…"

Upon hearing Han Xiao's response, Zoel did not reply immediately but fell into a deep thought.

He had originally intended to probe Black Star to understand his intentions but never imagined that Black Star would immediately request to join the alliance.

It was not anything new for a Beyond Grade A Super to join a Universal Civilization, but it was definitely a matter out of his authority. Thus, he had to report the matter to his superiors.

Zoel secretly estimated Han Xiao's value.

Black Star's strength and potential are undeniable. Since more than ten years ago, he's leaned toward the dynasty and definitely isn't an opportunistic individual. Furthermore, the Black Star Army has a sizable influence in the Shattered Star Ring, and it would be advantageous to the exploration of the Flickering World. Furthermore, he still has the Evolution Cube in his hands… Right. I need to have a good talk with him about the Evolution Cube.

The Evolution Cube originally belonged to Psyker and was protected by the Arcane Church. Now that it was in Han Xiao's hands, it was an important bargaining chip.

Thinking about this, Zoel said, "I need to be clear about something. How are you going to deal with the Evolution Cube?"

A bright smile could be seen on Han Xiao's face.

"This item will naturally be a part of the conditions. We can use a sharing method to deal with the Evolution Cube. The Crimson Dynasty will support me in keeping the Evolution Cube, and you guys can send an unlimited number of individuals to use the Evolution Cube."

This was the cooperation method that Psyker and the Arcane Church had opted for. However, he was not prepared to have an exclusive contract with a Universal Civilization like Psyker.

Psyker used the exclusive contract to get the Arcane Church to give more support to his Star Pupil Holy Race, but Han Xiao did not have a race to bring up. The benefits from sharing the Evolution Cube with other civilizations would be greater.

"Hmm, not bad." Zoel nodded. This was within an acceptable range. "The upper echelons of the dynasty will probably accept this condition. We can help you deal with some obstruction on the outside. Apart from this, do you have any other conditions?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. This was the time for them to negotiate about benefits.

"I have a few requests," Han Xiao said with a serious expression. "First, I hope that the Crimson Dynasty will provide resources to me and the Black Star Army."

"No problem," Zoel replied without any hesitation. "With the Evolution Cube, we will be willing to provide more resources."

"Second, I hope that the Black Star Army can join the Flickering World exploration squad."

"Haha, I think that the dynasty would have requested that you go even if you didn't mention this matter."

Han Xiao only nodded.

That's right, the Shattered Star Ring is the nearest to the Flickering World, and if the Crimson Dynasty needs a vanguard force, the organizations in the Shattered Star Ring will be their first choice.

The entrance ticket to the Flickering World definitely would not be a problem.

"Third, I hope that the Crimson Dynasty will not speak on behalf of the Klent Kingdom with regards to the secret war."

Zoel frowned upon hearing that.

"This is a decision for the upper echelons and not within my authority. I cannot give you any assurance on that."

This request was not something that he had expected but was still reasonable.

After fighting for so many years, it would not be strange if Black Star wanted to obtain victory. However, Klent was also an ally of the Crimson Dynasty, and this was a question of which party had greater value. Even Zoel could not guarantee what the upper echelons would decide.

"No problem." Han Xiao waved his hands. "These are my three greatest conditions."

"Hmm, I will report the matter up."

Zoel then suddenly said, "Right, I heard about the conflict between you and Heber. Do you need me to mediate on your behalf?"

Since Black Star was about to form an alliance with the Crimson Dynasty, the Tyrant and Black Star could be considered allies as well. Their battle was akin to friendly fire between both parties.

Although the public challenge could not be rescinded, they only needed to announce that Black Star had joined the Crimson Dynasty. At that time, both parties naturally would not fight.

"That isn't necessary," Han Xiao rejected.

Zoel thought for a while and came to a realization. He then said with a smile, "You're right. I was the one who lacked consideration."

It would not be good for Black Star's image if the Crimson Dynasty came out to resolve the conflict between the two. The outside world would think that Black Star had chosen to join the Crimson Dynasty because he could not escape the Tyrant.

"If you don't have anything else to add on, I will report your conditions to my superiors."

"Right." Han Xiao suddenly thought about something, "I have a small request. I hope to obtain some Mechanic Cutting-Edge Knowledge within twenty days."

The Crimson Dynasty naturally had the entire set of class knowledge, and Cutting-Edge Knowledge was not that precious to them. Perhaps he would be able to activate the skills of the Emperor Mechanic before the battle.

With Han Xiao's current construction speed, twenty days was enough for him to build a large number of machines with his new knowledge.

Zoel nodded. If it was Ultimate Knowledge, the upper echelons might still need to consider the matter, but Cutting-Edge Knowledge was nothing to them. After all, the other party was a Beyond Grade A Super who was about to join their alliance. This could be considered basic treatment.

"Alright, await my reply."

This was only their initial negotiation, and the exact outcome would be determined by the upper echelons of the Crimson Dynasty.

At the same time, in some region of the Shattered Star Ring, Psyker was rushing toward the Colton Star Cluster.

"Since the Dragon Emperor has decided to intervene, it seems like this matter won't go so smoothly…"

Psyker was not in a good mood.

Heber insisted on fighting Black Star alone and refused to join hands with him. Thus, Psyker could only issue a separate challenge to Han Xiao. However, Psyker had also found a good opportunity from this.

Since Black Star was maintaining the Evolution Cube in its portable form, Black Star would definitely take the Evolution Cube around with him. During the day of the battle, Black Star would reveal some flaws when fighting Heber. At that time, he would have an opportunity to snatch the item back from Black Star.

At that time, it would be useless for the Tyrant to reject him. As long as the Tyrant and Black Star began their battle, he would be able to join the battle anytime, and no one would be able to stop him.

He would not have to clash head on with Black Star if he wanted to seize such an opportunity, and the odds of his success were pretty high. Psyker's final objective was the Evolution Cube, not dealing with Black Star. He was not bothered about the views of others. For the development of his race, losing a bit of reputation was nothing.

Originally, this plan of his could not have gone wrong. Black Star was due to be fighting alone, and while his focus was on the Tyrant, he would definitely not be able to deal with another Beyond Grade A Super.

However, Ames' interference had foiled his plans.

Since Black Star had an ally, Ames would definitely stop him if he wanted to launch an attack. It would then be impossible for him to snatch the Evolution Cube from Black Star using such a method.

Unless… someone could restrain Ames.

The best candidate was Austin, but that darn old man only wanted to watch the show by the side and refused to help.

Thus, he could only look for other helpers.

Thankfully, he had a powerful ally.

"It seems like I can only seek help from the army that the Arcane Church stationed in the Shattered Star Ring. They should be willing to take action if it is to restrain a Beyond Grade A Super…"

Psyker's eyes lit up brightly like a lightbulb.

Chapter 773: Star Field Trend

After the time and location of Black Star and Tyrant's challenge was announced to the outside world, a huge storm was ignited throughout the Shattered Star Ring.

All of a sudden, spaceships that numbered in the billions flew toward the Colton Star Cluster, where the battle was going to happen.

Regardless of whether they were free galactic residents or from large organizations, none of them were willing to miss out on this rare event in the Star Field. They all rushed to the battlefield to witness the battle for themselves.

As the party involved in the battle, Bloodshed Land led their troops to the desolate universe belt near the border of West Wind and demarcated the battlefield. Purple Crystal resolutely decided to support Han Xiao and led the Section Zero troops to the battlefield as well.

The Black Star Army did not remain idle either, and under the orders of the various officers, numerous armed satellite fortresses rushed over from various Star Systems to support their Army Commander.

Bloodshed Land and Section Zero began a standoff with each other, and the gap between them formed the demarcated battlefield.

There were numerous spaceships piloted by the galactic residents who went to join in the fun from all around the Star Field. Numerous spaceships of different models were packed tightly and formed a huge ocean of spaceships that one could not see the end of.

Looking at the ocean of spaceships, a nebula seemed to have been formed from the lights of the spaceship.

It was an extremely majestic sight!

Furthermore, there were more spaceships arriving every day, and the size of the audience was growing by the second.

The different galactic media groups had also arrived at the destination of the battle and adjusted their broadcasting equipment.

It was still too early for the battle, and all the Beyond Grade A Supers had yet to arrive. However, a huge crowd had already formed, and many were already excitedly anticipating the arrival of the battle.

This was not just a clash between Beyond Grade A Supers but also a once in a lifetime event for the Shattered Star Ring.

Beyond Grade A Supers had an exalted status in the hearts of the galactic residents, and they were like superstars that every family knew about. Everyone wanted to personally witness their strength.

The twenty days of preparation time allowed the commotion of this event to be blown up even greater with over sixty percent of the galactic citizens discussing the event.

As the battle drew nearer, the anticipation of the galactic residents also grew greater.

...

The various betting groups in the galaxy would not let go of this huge business opportunity, and they all sprang into action.

Very quickly, the betting ring for the Tyrant and Black Star's battle was opened up, and a huge number of bets were made.

The various betting groups had a different payout rate, but Heber's payout was generally lower than Han Xiao's. This proved that the majority had more confidence in the Tyrant.

Although both were Beyond Grade A Supers, Han Xiao was a newbie after all and only had a single battle record with another Beyond Grade A Super. However, the Tyrant was different. He was an old powerhouse with a long history.

As a Beyond Grade A Super who had only been around for a month, Han Xiao's status in the Shattered Star Ring was naturally not as high as the Tyrant's.

Most of the mercenaries were gamblers, and although their boss was the one fighting, the warriors of the Black Star Army could not help but place their bets as well. Even the officers were not immune to gambling.

Herlous took the most and bet it all on Han Xiao. Most of the officers also placed their bets on Han Xiao but only bet a small amount to show their loyalty and trust.

There were only a few exceptions.

"You placed all your bets on the Tyrant‽" Sylvia glared at Reynold with disbelief.

Reynold said with a solemn expression, "According to probability and my calculations, the Tyrant's odds of victory are more than thirty percent higher than His Excellency Black Star."

Sylvia shook her head helplessly. "Don't you believe in our teacher at all?"

"I only believe in science," Reynold said expressionlessly.

Rossellin, who was lazing around by the side, listened to the conversation with interest while drinking some wine.

Rossellin was now the teacher of the Black Star Army and was in charge of building up a culture within the army to increase the sense of belonging of the soldiers.

At this moment, Rossellin smiled and said, "According to what I know, our vice commander also placed his bets on Tyrant. Furthermore, he placed quite a large bet."

"LAGI!" Sylvia flew into a rage and charged out of the door.

She was the Chief Administrative Official and had a great deal of authority in her hands. Although Lagi was the vice commander of the army, Lagi pretty much ignored all the affairs of the army, so Sylvia had the courage to confront Lagi. To think that he had placed his bets on the enemy as the vice commander. This was too outrageous!

Reynold's expression also changed slightly as he heard that.

"Oh no. Lagi also placed his bets on Tyrant. The winning chance of our Army Commander will be increased by ten percent at least."

Rossellin laughed. "Hey hey hey, I thought you only believed in science."

"Magic is also a part of science..." Reynold said with resignation.

However, regardless of how he placed his bets, he still hoped that Black Star would win.

...

Because of Black Star and the Tyrant's battle, the secret war also came to a halt, and the players did not have any battles to fight in.

Even the Main Storyline mission was stopped because of this event. To the players of the Shattered Star Ring, this was the largest event in the three versions.

Black Star was already the leader that all the players had recognized, and his status was elevated further after he entered Beyond Grade A.

Although Han Xiao did not issue any faction missions, all the players located in the various regions followed the forces of the army and arrived at the battlefield to support their Army Commander.

This was not the first time that the Black Star Army had held a collective event, but the number of players participating in this faction event was the highest in history!

The forums were filled with threads regarding the cause and effect of this battle, and one of the threads received huge approval from the other players. The thread said that this battle would be a turning point for the destiny of the Black Star Army.

The Black Star Army was the main faction in the hearts of the Shattered Star Ring players, and Black Star had been the main character NPC ever since Version 2.0. Together with the growth of the faction, the benefits that the players could receive also increased, and almost all their needs in terms of missions, levels, skills, knowledge, equipment, and so on were fulfilled.

A single faction was better than the addition of many different factions in other Star Fields. Thus, the players in the Shattered Star Ring did not need to waste any time farming favorability with the other factions. As such, the Black Star Army was treated like a special existence that only the players in the Shattered Star Ring could enjoy.

Many of the players had tried to analyze the future of the Black Star Army. According to the experience of the players from the other Star Fields, some were worried that the Black Star Army would not continue to exist forever and would suffer from some irreparable damage during the later versions. At that time, all the benefits that they currently experienced would be gone, and they would have to join different factions like the players from the other Star Fields.

Could they really remain in the Black Star Army forever? No one knew.

Such a question had always existed but was not mentioned very often. Most of the players could not be bothered to make such wild guesses, and only the players who enjoyed diving deep into the storylines analyzed the question. Summer Night Flower was one such individual.

In the intense discussions on the forums, this battle became an important factor to predict what happened in the future. If the Black Star Army could achieve victory, the Black Star Army would soar to greater heights, and their faction would go up to the next level, still appearing in the next version.

But if the outcome of this battle did not go as planned, the feelings that the players had toward the army would also undergo a subtle change.

Bun-Hit-Dog was affected by the topic being discussed on the forums. The Black Star series videos were his most popular series, and he was the one who wished for the successful development of the Black Star Army the most.

"I must gather enough material this time to make an explosive video," Bun-Hit-Dog swore to himself.

...

In the Aquamarine Federation, Bennett placed down the communicator in his hands, and a look of concern could be seen on his face.

News of the battle between Black Star and the Tyrant had spread throughout the Shattered Star Ring. Now that Planet Aquamarine was connected to the galaxy, everyone was able to view the galactic web, and the events in the galaxy were no longer a secret to those on Planet Aquamarine.

"This is probably the strongest opponent that you have faced, right?" Bennett lamented.

Nero, who was doing his homework, raised his head and asked curiously, "Daddy, what are you talking about?"

Bennett waved his hands, and Nero sat down on Bennett's thighs obediently.

"Your godfather is being dragged into a dangerous storm. A powerful opponent challenged him, and he chose to accept the challenge..." Bennett briefly described the situation. Nero was still a child, so Bennett skipped many details and only told him that Han Xiao was in danger.

Nero was Han Xiao's godson, and Bennett was prepared to hand his child over to Han Xiao.

"What should we do?" Nero rubbed his head. "Daddy, will you help godfather?"

Bennett laughed helplessly and said, "Your godfather doesn't need my help. You will understand all this when you grow up."

They were too far away in terms of realms, and he did not even have any intention of contacting Han Xiao as he did not want to disturb Han Xiao.

Bennett hugged Nero and looked up at the sky above. He knew that Han Xiao was in some part of the galaxy and prayed for Han Xiao.

"Old friend..."

...

The large fleet that set off from the Black Star Army headquarters met up with Floating Dragon and flew toward West Wind together.

A few days later, Zoel took the initiative to contact Han Xiao to inform him of the Crimson Dynasty's response.

"The dynasty accepts your requests, and I welcome you to our alliance on behalf of the dynasty."

Zoel said these words with an official tone before smiling and adding, "We are now one big family."

Han Xiao clenched his fists and was truly excited.

"May we have a pleasant working experience."

"Don't worry. Our dynasty has plenty of experience in this regard and will always treat a Beyond Grade A Super with sincerity. You can rest assured," Zoel said with a smile.

The three Universal Civilizations were at odds with each other, and every Beyond Grade A Super ally was an important deterrent. Thus, they would not bully their Beyond Grade A Supers for sure.

The moment their alliance was confirmed, the Universal Civilization would treat their allies with the utmost respect in order to keep them.

"The Crimson Dynasty is now taking care of matters regarding the Flickering World and will pass by the Shattered Star Ring along the way," Zoel said. "It shouldn't take too long for the resources from the dynasty to reach your hands. However, we can only work together officially after your battle with the Tyrant comes to an end. During this period, the dynasty will send the contract to me, and we just need to sign it when the time comes."

Although a contract was not very restrictive to a Beyond Grade A Super, this was a way for the government to officially confirm their alliance, and it had a political meaning.

Han Xiao nodded upon hearing that.

Joining the Crimson Dynasty was the way for him to achieve greater heights, and the benefits of his decision would slowly begin to show. Currently, he had to deal with the Tyrant first before he had time to deal with the development of the Black Star Army.

"The dynasty also has a request for you. The dynasty hopes that you can make a trip to the Central Galaxy. The upper echelons would like to meet you and introduce you to the other Beyond Grade A allies of the dynasty."

For him to appear in the Central Galaxy with the status of the Crimson Dynasty's ally, this was akin to the Crimson Dynasty showing off to their neighbors their new chip.

He did not have anything against this. Since he was willing to accept the support of the Crimson Dynasty, he naturally had to play his part.

Although this meant that many organizations would label him as part of the Crimson Dynasty and draw the attention of the dynasty's enemies, his own scope of operations was mainly in the Shattered Star Ring, and the other organizations would not casually make trouble for him.

Han Xiao shrugged. "No problem."

"Hmm, there is something else. My intelligence net noticed that the Arcane Church's forces have been mobilized and are moving toward the location of the battle. They may be there to provide backup for Psyker," Zoel said. "I will mobilize the Crimson Dynasty's army to be present on the day of the battle as well. This is what we have agreed upon, and we will help you fend off other powers."

"You guys are also going to watch the battle?" Han Xiao stroked his chin. "Is this alright? Won't people suspect you?"

"Of course not," Zoel said. "After all, the Tyrant is also our ally."

Han Xiao almost burst into laughter upon hearing that.

That's right. The Crimson Dynasty can use Heber as an excuse to mobilize their forces, and no one will suspect them. Not a single person will be able to guess that they are actually there to help me.

The Crimson Dynasty would not intervene in the battle between Han Xiao and the Tyrant. This could be considered an internal battle. Although, the Tyrant was still in the dark regarding this.

However, Psyker was not one of their allies and was a latent threat.

The Arcane Church's goal was naturally the Evolution Cube, and the Crimson Dynasty would not allow anyone to snatch the Evolution Cube.

"One more thing," Zoel added. "Your request for Cutting-Edge Knowledge has been approved. I will send you the data later."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Compared to the resources that he had yet to receive, this was a much more practical benefit.

There were nine Cutting-Edge Knowledges for the Mechanic class, and he had learned four from Purple Crystal. There were five more that he had not grasped, and he had sent a list to Zoel previously.

"How many Cutting-Edge Knowledges will the dynasty give me?"

"How many? Do you have some misunderstanding about Universal Civilizations?"

Zoel laughed.

"We will give you everything."

Chapter 774: Spending Potential Points Sure Is Comfortable

They are truly a wealthy bunch!

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

A Universal Civilization naturally would not be petty with a Beyond Grade A Super. Apart from Ultimate Knowledge, they would be able to freely give him all the knowledge from basic up to cutting-edge. In his past life, Han Xiao had needed to farm for contribution points in order to obtain new knowledge, but things were completely different now.

The conversation then ended after chatting casually for a while. Not too long later, a file was sent to him.

Looking at the file, joy filled Han Xiao's face.

Han Xiao had already obtained the Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Controllable Annihilation Weapons] from the Armed Branch, [Abnormal State Energy] from the Energy Branch, and [Advanced Space Application] and [Quantum Network Matrix] from the Control Branch.

The file that Zoel sent over contained the last five Cutting-Edge Knowledges.

Armed Branch: [Cutting-Edge Material Science] and [Ultra-Composite Mechanical Architecture Technology].

Energy Branch: [Beyond Visible Energy Transfer] and [Activation Theory].

Control Branch: [Spacetime Dimension Exploration].

"The entire set is now complete!" Han Xiao was extremely excited.

He belonged to the Control Branch, and learning a Cutting-Edge Knowledge required four points. However, learning the knowledge of the other two branches required twelve points each.

Han Xiao saved a large amount of Potential Points when he advanced into Beyond Grade A. Although it was not enough to level all the knowledges up to their maximum level, it was enough to level all the knowledge up by one.

It was impossible for players to be so extravagant and in Han Xiao's previous life, the players could only choose one or two Cutting-Edge Knowledge to learn. However, Han Xiao was different.

He had a large sea of experience points to level up his skill and he was able to farm for plenty of Potential Points. Thus, it wasn't impossible for him to learn all the Cutting-Edge Knowledge.

"Heber probably thinks that twenty days is too short. Hehe..."

Han Xiao chuckled in his heart.

Compared to other Mechanics, the interface was his biggest advantage. As long as he paid the relevant Potential Points, he would be able to rapidly learn new knowledge and save a large amount of time. Thus, he was able to achieve rapid growth during the limited time before his battle with the Tyrant.

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao spent his Potential Points to learn all five Cutting-Edge Knowledges.

Mechanic class Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Spacetime Dimension Exploration] detected. Do you wish to spend 4 Potential Points to learn it?

Learning in progress. Do not cancel.

9%... 24%... 57%...

Success! You have learned [Spacetime Dimension Exploration]!

Mechanic class Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Cutting-Edge Material Science] detected. Do you wish to spend 12 Potential Points to learn it?

Learning in progress. Do not cancel.

Success! You have learned [Cutting-Edge Material Science]!

Mechanic class Cutting-Edge Knowledge...

A large amount of information flowed into his brain, but with Han Xiao's current Intelligence, this load was negligible.

The new knowledge that entered his brain was broken up and reorganized before being stored in his memory palace.

After spending fifty-two Potential Points to learn the five Cutting-Edge Knowledges, the names of these Knowledges lit up on his knowledge tree with an orange light. In the class knowledge tree, Basic Knowledge was white in color, Advanced Knowledge green, High-End Knowledge purple, Cutting-Edge Knowledge orange, and Ultimate Knowledge gold.

Right at this moment, a few notifications popped up on his interface.

Prerequisite requirement fulfilled. Your skill [Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel] has been activated!

Prerequisite requirement fulfilled. Your skill [Secondary Dimension Army] has been activated!

Prerequisite requirement fulfilled. Your skill [Mechanical Force—Emperor's Power] has been activated!

The three Emperor Mechanic skills, which were originally grayed out, had turned green to indicate that they could be used.

The new knowledge that he had acquired fulfilled the prerequisite knowledge for these three skills, and only the final skill, [King's Mentor], had yet to be activated. Not only did this skill need [Activation Theory], it needed a higher level Ultimate Knowledge.

Because [King's Mentor] was a skill to help nurture his strength in the long run, this skill would not be able to help him much for the battle in ten days. Thus, Han Xiao was not too anxious about activating it and planned to find another chance to activate it in the future.

"With the Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel, my mechanical army will be able to engage in long-range battles and enjoy the boost from my Mechanical Force even without my appearance. This means that my mechanical army now has the ability to go on a long-distance mission on their own, and the Secondary Dimension Army skill means that I no longer have to use army boxes. I can receive reinforcements at a much quicker speed and bring around a much larger force with me..."

Han Xiao was extremely satisfied.

The skills of an Emperor Mechanic were extremely powerful, but that was not all he had gained.

Following the changes in his knowledge tree, the new knowledge also brought him new skills.

You have learned [Active Mechanical Force]!

You have learned [Advanced Machinery Construction]!

You have learned [Fine Material Refinement]!

You have learned [Legendary Enhancement]!

You have learned [Machinery Fusion]!

Han Xiao raised his arms to release Mechanical Force, and the Mechanical Force in his palms experienced a change in color. A light golden color could be seen amid the blue bolts of lightning, and it looked extremely luxurious.

This was the effect of [Active Mechanical Force], which came from the knowledge [Activation Theory]. It is a passive skill that could increase one's Machinery Affinity by 150% at level one and 280% at the max level.

[Advanced Machinery Construction] was the upgraded form of [Basic Machinery Construction]. It largely increased the speed of construction, and as long as the raw materials were sufficient, raw materials could rapidly be transformed into spare parts before being assembled into machines.

This skill could also increase the effect of [Waste Modification]. Originally, machines could only be recycled for four times, but the upper limit had been increased to eight. The original twenty percent decrease in a machine's attributes had fallen to ten percent.

[Fine Material Refinement] and [Legendary Enhancement] were the upgraded abilities of a Mechanic's basic skills. They increased his ability to work with new materials and also strengthened his machinery.

Both [Machinery Fusion] and [King's Mentor] came from [Activation Theory] and were used to strengthen his soldiers.

They bestowed a mechanical soldier with the ability to swallow other machines and decompose the target to snatch the target's armor and equipment. This was a way for a mechanical soldier to evolve and grow.

The two skills did not overlap. [King's Mentor] increased the energy of a mechanical soldier whereas [Machinery Fusion] improved the hardware of the mechanical soldier. Explaining it simply, [King's Mentor] was used to increase a mechanical soldier's energy whereas [Machinery Fusion] increased a mechanical soldier's body strength and basic stats.

Both skills were complementary and could increase the strength of a mechanical soldier when used together.

These skills are extremely important to increase my strength in this phase, Han Xiao thought to himself.

Using the Evolution Cube resulted in a ten-month experience penalty, and Han Xiao was not planning to waste his extra experience leveling up during this period of time. He was prepared to use it to increase the level of his skills instead of increasing his chances during the battle with the Tyrant.

After looking through his new skills once and raising most of them to the max level, Han Xiao closed the interface.

These new skills should be used on his mechanical army, and his strength would definitely reach a new peak after the next ten or so days.

Han Xiao passed all the miscellaneous tasks over to his officers and remained in the workshop to construct his new machinery. The others knew that he needed to prepare for battle, and even Ames did not disturb his seclusion.

...

The date for the battle soon arrived.

The desolate universe belt outside of West Wind was bustling with activity and had become a sea of spaceships.

After travelling for twenty days, numerous spaceships rushed over from all the different regions, and there seemed to be a never-ending sea of spaceships.

In every Star Field, Star Cluster, Star System, and planet, the number of people watching the live broadcast of the event was many times that of those present.

The battlefield had become the stage for the trillions all over the galaxy.

Not a single Beyond Grade A Super had arrived at this moment, and everyone was waiting excitedly for the main characters to arrive.

Bloodshed Land and Section Zero's fleets were currently in a standoff with each other, and both Klent and Purple Crystal had sent out their official fleet to maintain order. The atmosphere was extremely tense, and the secret war looked as though it was about to erupt and become a war between two civilizations. However, both parties had extremely good self-control and had a tacit agreement to not escalate the conflict.

"There are truly too many people..."

In one of the Star Diamond Grade Flagships, Ralph looked out at the sea of spaceships. Even with his authority and status, he could not help but feel nervous at such a majestic scene.

The number of spectators was probably in the trillions!

"It would be impossible for us to maintain order if chaos breaks out." Ralph felt his heart thumping. "When will Black Star arrive?"

"The Black Star Army headquarters just sent a message and said that His Excellency Black Star's fleet will arrive soon."

Ralph felt his palms drenched in cold sweat as he tried to imagine what would happen next. He had not brought the Purple Crystal fleet over for fun and was prepared to provide reinforcement for Black Star when needed.

After finally gaining a Beyond Grade A ally, Purple Crystal was not willing to give up on Black Star. If the battle was to Black Star's disadvantage, Purple Crystal would reinforce him even if it meant an all-out war. Since the secret war was already in a stalemate, Purple Crystal was not afraid of flipping the table. Furthermore, the authority to mobilize the fleet was in the hands of Ralph and a few other military commanders. Thus, Ralph truly had a heavy feeling in his heart.

In the Section Zero camp, the Black Star Army fleet was in the most prominent spot with tens of thousands of spaceships present. The players were present within the Black Star Army fleet, and they looked out at the scene before them.

"The battle is going to begin today..."

Frenzied Sword clenched his fists tightly.

All the players around him had looks of curiosity, anxiety, excitement, agitation, and many other different emotions.

The scale of this gathering was one that they had never witnessed before and the largest event in the three versions of Galaxy. None of the players wanted to miss out on such an event.

In the Bloodshed Land faction, there was also a batch of players present. They were the 'traitor army' with Summer Night Flower in the lead.

Summer Night Flower looked at the Black Star Army fleet with a complicated look on his face.

I was once a part of them...

The way Summer Night Flower saw it, the battle between the bosses of Bloodshed Land and the Black Star Army was his final chance to prove himself.

The Mercenary League had sent their forces and occupied a VIP spot.

"How many years has it been since such a majestic event took place in the Shattered Star Ring?"

The bigshots of the Mercenary League were chatting casually, and Gureja could not help but lament. He was the leader of Sky Ring and one of the upper echelons of the Mercenary League.

"The last time Beyond Grade A Supers publicly challenged each other was 276 years ago. It was Austin fighting one of the powerhouses from the previous generation, right?" another Army Commander said.

"More than two hundred years ago. Heh, I was still a small guerrilla captain back then," Underworld Feather said while chewing on some snacks.

"I bet you definitely didn't have such a weird fetish two hundred years ago." Gureja could not help but look at the dry meat in Underworld Feather's hands.

"What weird fetish? I am a gourmet." Underworld Feather rolled her eyes.

Gureja shook his head and ignored her. "Since Black Star has already become a Beyond Grade A Super, regardless of the outcome of the battle, I will invite him to become the chief of our Mercenary League. All of us will be able to find more development opportunities if we are under him."

All the Army Commanders nodded, and no one disagreed.

The Mercenary League could be considered a large organization in the Shattered Star Ring, and the Black Star Army was one of the founders. None of them minded Black Star becoming the nominal leader of their organization as it would bring them a brighter future.

There were many other organizations that Han Xiao had cooperated with before present as well.

Right at that moment, a blue whirlpool-like transportation door suddenly appeared in the middle of the battlefield and expanded rapidly.

"They're finally here!"

At this moment, the crowd erupted in a huge commotion.

The excitement that everyone had been suppressing was ignited once again!

Chapter 775: The Battle Begins!

Everyone in all the spaceships stopped talking, and their gazes were fixed on the transportation door in the middle of the battlefield.

The wormhole-like transportation door enlarged continuously as though it was limitless. The largest spaceship present currently was the armed satellite fortress of the Black Star Army, but the size of the transportation door had already exceeded that of an armed satellite fortress. The radars of all the spaceships began ringing as they detected a large energy surge.

The next moment, a majestic castle covered in a colorful magical shield floated out from the transportation door. The complicated engravings on the spherical shield looked like exquisite decorations, and they shimmered as though they were breathing.

The treasure of the Hidden Red Robe Abbey, Palace of Hidden Spells!

"Austin is here!"

"He actually brought his entire base over. He is truly too high profile."

"Is he here as a spectator or to help one of the parties?"

Although the first Beyond Grade A to arrive was not involved in the battle, the spectators were still extremely excited. Since Austin had made his appearance, this meant that all five Beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring would gather there!

"This fellow is also here to join in the fun?" Ralph was startled and was worried that Austin would spoil his plans.

The commander of Bloodshed Land, Jorde, also felt nervous.

"I wonder if Austin is an enemy or ally..." Jorde gulped nervously. Psyker was the one who had contacted Austin in private, and thus, Jorde was not clear of Austin's intentions.

The Palace of Hidden Spells very quickly completed its descent, and the transportation door shrank rapidly before disappearing with a flash of light. Austin's main camp was a Beyond Grade A Universal Treasure Mage Pagoda, and he had engraved a large number of teleportation formations on the pagoda so that it could engage in long distance travel.

Numerous mages living in the Palace of Hidden Spells walked out of the castle and gathered together on one of the balconies to munch on snacks as they waited for the show to start. Austin then appeared on top of the castle with his Forbidden Sorcerer squad and controlled the Palace of Hidden Spells to find a good spot beside the battlefield.

"Tsk, why am I the first one here? Youngsters these days don't have any sense of time," Austin lamented.

He had rejected both parties' requests to form an alliance and was there to watch the battle. In order to ensure that he could watch the show comfortably, he had even shifted his entire house.

Just when the spectators were discussing Austin's intentions, a commotion broke out from afar.

A gigantic fleet approached the battlefield, and all the spectators who saw the insignia on the fleet could not help but make a path for them in shock.

The insignia on the outside of the spaceship was one that everyone could recognize. It was the insignia of a Universal Civilization, the Arcane Church!

The Arcane Church had made an appearance as well!

This was a small portion of the fleet that the Arcane Church stationed in the Shattered Star Ring. The frigate was composed of a special Arcane Church model, which had a thin disc-like shape with the entire body covered in black and dark purple. Three gigantic empty holes could be seen on the body of the spaceship in a triangular formation with a dark-red energy ball floating in the middle of the holes. It served both as an energy furnace and annihilation weapon.

The flagship was of the butterfly model with a ball in the center and a few hundred butterfly wings connected on both sides. These wings were currently in their closed form and looked like a single pair of wings. Although the spaceship was made from metal, it was made from a special alloy and had a soft, silky texture. When the flagship entered battle, all the butterfly wings would open and slide along the surface of the ball in the middle to form a sun-like shape.

The Arcane Church fleet entered the battlefield without any obstruction, and a spaceship flew out from within the fleet. When the hatch of the spaceship opened, Psyker flew out from the spaceship. He was the second Beyond Grade A to arrive.

His body floated in front of the Arcane Church fleet, and his gaze was fixed on the Purple Crystal and Section Zero fleet far away. Despite being a tiny ant compared to the gigantic fleet, the attention of all the spectators was gathered on him.

Everyone took a deep breath.

"Psyker has arrived!"

"The Arcane Church has actually sent a fleet with him. Is this the attitude of a Universal Civilization?"

It was no secret that the Arcane Church was behind the Star Pupil Holy Race, but the Universal Civilizations had not displayed an official stance with regards to this matter yet. For them to appear at this moment, it meant that they were about to interfere in the battle. This was something that all those present did not expect.

Regardless of whether they were the spectators present or those watching the live broadcast, everyone was shocked.

They originally thought that this battle was only a conflict between Beyond Grade A Supers. However, the appearance of a Universal Civilization meant that the situation had become a lot more complex.

"Things aren't looking good. The Arcane Church is here to help Psyker!" Ralph immediately felt as though a huge enemy had descended.

The fleet sent by the Arcane Church was extremely powerful and was comparable to the fleet of both Purple Crystal and Section Zero. Furthermore, how would Purple Crystal and Section Zero dare fight a Universal Civilization?

On the other side, Jorde became wary.

Because the Star Pupil Holy Race was too far away from the battlefield and could not send a fleet to support Psyker, everyone had thought that Psyker would come alone. However, the appearance of the Arcane Church meant that Psyker was the one with the most powerful backing out of everyone who is present. The special position of a Universal Civilization made all the organizations present tremble slightly.

However, before everyone could accept the changes before their eyes, another fleet descended.

Upon seeing the incoming fleet, everyone present was dumbfounded!

The Crimson Dynasty!

Yet another Universal Civilization‽

The technological skills of the Crimson Dynasty were obviously extremely different from those of the Arcane Church. The spaceships of the Arcane Church had a mystical and magical style while the spaceships of the Crimson Dynasty had a heavy industry style. The spaceship had a solid metal beauty and emanated a tyrannical pressure even from afar.

The Crimson Dynasty squeezed into the battlefield and stopped beside Klent, entering the face off with the Purple Crystal fleet as well. They looked as though they were there to support Tyrant.

Ten days prior, Zoel had agreed to Klent's request for them to send a fleet to support the Tyrant. Upon seeing their backing arrive, Jorde immediately became relaxed, and he looked at the Black Star Army camp with a sneer.

Do you see that little brother? Do you have any backing?

We have two on our side!

On the Star Diamond Grade Flagship, Ralph's face was completely pale, and he felt his legs turn to jelly.

He had never expected that things would turn out as such. The situation was not just bad at this moment. It was hopeless!

If both parties broke out in a conflict later, they would not be able to hold their own against two Universal Civilizations.

Right at that moment, all the spectators finally snapped out of their stupor.

"Both the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church have arrived!"

"Two Universal Civilizations are standing against Black Star‽"

"Black Star only has Purple Crystal behind him, and his situation truly looks pathetic..."

"A new Beyond Grade A Super actually has to face such a situation, huh? I think his luck just ran out."

In the eyes of the spectators, both Universal Civilizations were going against Black Star together. The alliance of the Tyrant and Star Pupil was far too powerful, and Black Star was definitely on the losing side.

At the thought of Black Star's predicament, cold sweat slid down the spectators' backs. At the same time, the bets placed on the Tyrant rapidly surged up like mad. The various betting rings only planned to stop accepting bets after the arrival of Black Star and Heber but were forced to immediately stop accepting bets.

All the players in the Black Star Army camp could not help but feel anxious. This was the first time that they witnessed the peak characters of the universe, but they were all enemies of their faction.

"It seems like our Army Commander is in trouble..." Maple Moon clenched her fists tightly.

Frenzied Sword also could not help but worry, and his fists were clenched tightly as well.

Although the Black Star Army was the main camp in the hearts of the players, the brainwashing of the three versions had made all the players believe that the Universal Civilizations that had existed for a long time were the true tyrants of the galaxy. Originally, there were plenty of players who were optimistic about the battle, but the changes in the situation made it such that the players could not even force out a smile.

Many individuals could not help but be shaken. The next few versions would definitely revolve around the Universal Civilizations, but their Black Star Army had become an enemy of the Universal Civilizations. This was not a good sign at all...

On the contrary, Summer Night Flower was overjoyed.

The reason behind his inclination to the Bloodshed Land was because the Bloodshed Land would give them a path to join the Universal Civilizations. On the other hand, the Black Star Army only had the Purple Crystal Civilization above them. The appearance of the Crimson Dynasty was like an injection of confidence, and Summer Night Flower began to regain confidence in his belief.

"Do you see that? This is what I meant by a limited faction growth," Summer Night Flower said with a face full of smiles. "I have emphasized this point since the start; we cannot be dazzled by the short term benefits placed before our eyes like the players of the Black Star Army. We should look far into the future and make the right choice instead."

At the same time, many of the officers in the Black Star Army flagship had bitter looks on their faces.

Lagi then said with a sigh, "It seems like I will die here today..."

The other officers would usually tease Lagi about his pessimism, but no one replied that day.

Even they could not help but feel pessimistic.

They had not forgotten that their Army Commander had to face two different challenges!

Even if he could hold his own against the Tyrant, there was still a Psyker who wanted to force Black Star to give up the Evolution Cube. No matter what, they felt that it was better for Han Xiao to give in and take the initiative to hand over the Evolution Cube. There were two Universal Civilizations eyeing up the Evolution Cube, and their strength just could not hold a candle to Universal Civilizations.

They truly could not understand how their army could keep the Evolution Cube.

One of the Calamity Grade officers could not help but say, "Well, if he chooses to behave stubbornly..."

"Shut up!" Sylvia glared at him hatefully, "Our job is to obey the orders of our commander. What do you want to say‽"

Everyone could not help but look at each other helplessly.

"Hopefully Black Star doesn't lose his rationality..."

Right at this moment, a Bloodshed Land spaceship flew over from afar and came to the center of the battlefield. Heber had finally arrived.

He was equipped with a set of heavy armor and floated in the middle of the battlefield like a small mountain. All the spaceship's radars began to ring after detecting his frightening energy.

Heber then turned around to glare at Psyker, warning Psyker not to interfere with his plans.

Psyker retreated a distance expressionlessly.

"The Tyrant is here as well. Only Black Star and the Dragon Emperor are left."

"Eh, they're here."

All the spectators turned around to look, only to see a Black Star fleet arriving together with the Floating Dragon Island. Because the Floating Dragon Island could not travel at a high speed, Han Xiao and Ames were the last two to reach the battlefield.

The surrounding spaceships made a path for the humongous Floating Dragon to enter the battlefield.

"Everyone is finally here!"

The spectators' excitement had reached the peak.

Ames floated up into the air, and Han Xiao also flew out from his spaceship, looking at Heber and Psyker from afar.

Han Xiao had filled the empty Mechanic slot, and the five Beyond Grade A Supers of the Shattered Star Ring were different classes. The spectators could not help but feel as though a ceremony was going on, and they were all witnessing this once in a lifetime ceremony.

Han Xiao turned around to look at Ames, and both of them nodded to each other. He then glanced at the huge crowd, and his face could not help but contort.

"Aren't they afraid that I may accidentally kill a few lucky audience members?"

Han Xiao then looked at the Palace of Hidden Spells and shook his head helplessly. Finally, his gaze landed on Heber.

After sizing Heber up for a while, Han Xiao connected to the Tyrant's communication device, and his voice sounded in Heber's armor.

"I am here, Little Ty-Ty. How do you want to fight?"

"... What did you call me‽" Heber was stunned for a moment.

"Heh, I will call you whatever I like." Han Xiao chuckled.

Heber could not be bothered to reply and said, "Black Star, I've thought highly of you since over ten years ago. This proves that my foresight wasn't wrong. It is a pity that you rejected my invitation and made the wrong decision. I gave you a chance before, but you didn't know how to treasure it."

Han Xiao curled his lips and said, "Don't talk about such useless things. Don't you want to make use of me to establish your prestige?"

"That's right." Heber did not bother hiding anything. "You are only alive today because you didn't have any value for me to uproot before, and you really didn't disappoint me. I let you keep your life until today so that I can use your fresh blood to paint my throne."

At the Beyond Grade A level, one was only able to gain fame by killing another Beyond Grade A Super, and this had always been the Tyrant's goal. In his eyes, as long as he could increase his prestige, more and more talents would come under him.

However, the other three Beyond Grade A Supers were not easy to deal with, and he did not have a reason to take action. Even Ames, who had her abilities countered by him, had impressive lifesaving abilities. Thus, he had decided to rear up a Beyond Grade A enemy and get rid of the fellow before he could grow up fully.

Han Xiao was the target whom he had chosen.

Upon hearing those words, Han Xiao couldn't help but shake his head.

Since you like rearing pigs so much, you'd better be careful not to get squashed by the pig.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao's interface lit up.

_____________________

You have triggered S ranked mission ['Tyrant' Heber]!

Mission Introduction: A Beyond Grade A Super stands at the peak of the galaxy, and Heber is one of them. Are you sure you want to battle him?

Mission Requirements: Last for as long as possible under Heber's attacks. (Battle method isn't restricted. You can only leave battle mode for 30 mins at most. There are no restrictions to the number of times you can leave battle mode.)

Reward: You will be able to attain the corresponding reward by fulfilling the corresponding requirements. (Only 1% of the time out of battle mode will be counted toward the mission.)

Last for 10s: 100,000,000 Experience

Last for 30s: 230,000,000 Experience

Last for 1 min: 450,000,000 Experience

Last for 2 mins: 700,000,000 Experience

Last for 3 mins: 900,000,000 Experience, +1 Legendary Point

...

Last for 7.5 mins: [Character Summon Card - 'Tyrant' Heber], 3,000,000,000 Experience

...

Last for 20 mins: The opportunity to draw one of the Tyrant's abilities or talents, 8,500,000,000 Experience, +1 Legendary Point

_____________________

"To think that it is actually such a mission." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

A Beyond Grade A Super was a true boss and an unscalable mountain. Even if the players had his current level, they would not be able to defeat a Beyond Grade A Super with a body full of Molding Talents. The only difference was the amount of time they could last. In his previous life, there were some players who had challenged Beyond Grade A Supers, and a portion of them triggered special S rank missions like this one. It had given them rewards based on the amount of time they could survive.

In his previous life, it was incredibly difficult for most of the players to last even a minute. The only method they had was to leave combat mode and escape to the best of their abilities. Because only one percent of the time was calculated, this meant that only eighteen seconds would be counted toward the mission at the very most. If the players wanted to earn the reward for lasting twenty minutes, they would have to leave combat mode more than sixty times at least. Furthermore, they had to ensure that the Beyond Grade A Super would not catch up to them for thirty mins. This meant that they needed to escape from the Beyond Grade A Super for more than thirty hours. It was a mission that was almost impossible to complete.

Han Xiao had challenged a Beyond Grade A Super before, and his best record was only a few minutes.

However, the interface's judgement of a mission rating was on the basis of the player's strength, and Han Xiao was an exception.

He did not need to leave combat mode and could choose to fight head on!

With his endurance, twenty mins would only be a warm up!

Han Xiao let out a deep breath, and his bluish-gold Mechanical Force burst forth.

Behind him, a large mechanical army appeared, forming an endless wave of black!

Emperor Mechanic! Secondary Dimension Army!

Upon seeing that, Heber cracked his neck, and his body exploded with a ball of fire.

The next moment, the mechanical army welcomed a shooting-star-like figure.

Chapter 776: The Battle

In the past ten days or so, Han Xiao's mechanical army had gained millions of members, and the enhancements of all the models were completed. The enormous army stood before Heber, firing at him with all kinds of ranged weapons.

The psionic particle cannons' dark energy annihilation beams formed a bright rain of light.

The Pugilist flames all around Heber's body expanded into a huge golden light sphere thousands of meters wide, forming his protective energy layer. His tiny mountain-sized body charged forward, carrying a long tail of flames behind, and headed right into the wave of machinery like a meteor.

The storm of attacks crashed onto Heber's protective shield, leaving clusters of explosions on the path behind him.

Facing the focus fire head-on, Heber dashed right into the formation of the mechanical army, penetrating the defenses of the mechanical soldiers layer after layer, heading right toward Han Xiao.

He decided to use his strength against the enemy's weakness—to quickly defeat Han Xiao in close-range combat!

"Horrifyingly tanky, as expected for a Beyond Grade A Pugilist..."

Han Xiao glanced at the combat information and raised his brows.

Heber's level, attributes, and health were all question marks. The interface showed that many of Heber's Molding Abilities were triggered. There were [Low Damage Immunity], [True Damage Immunity], [Fixed Damage Reduction], and many other damage reduction abilities. These abilities and his Beyond Grade A Pugilist energy shield reduced the strength of Han Xiao's attacks tremendously!

Heber was immune to True Damage as well as any damage that did not exceed a certain level, and only the portion that exceeded that level would be calculated. If the damage immunity limit was 100 and the raw damage was 110, Heber would only take 10 damage. A part of that 10 damage would then be reduced by his protective energy shield, and the remainder would be reduced once again by his resistance talents...

The damage would only count for Heber after so many layers of reductions!

The most terrifying thing was, Heber's recovery ability was pretty good, too. Although not as powerful as Han Xiao's, it still gave him a lot of sustainability.

This was the true Beyond Grade A Tank!

Han Xiao's eyes focused. He had known long ago that this would be a tough battle.

Hadavy had True Damage Immunity and Low Damage Immunity as well, but as he was an Esper, his attack was not very high. In comparison, Heber was clearly more comprehensive as a Beyond Grade A Pugilist that excelled in both attack and defense.

Hence, Han Xiao had no interest in fighting a Beyond Grade A Pugilist with his body. Even though he was quite tanky, the difference in a Beyond Grade A's main attribute and sub-attribute was way too huge; fighting Heber in close range combat was basically looking for a beating.

Seeing that Heber was heading right toward him, he immediately knew that Heber wanted to end this quickly. His lips curled up.

Although this was the right strategy for a Pugilist to use against a Mechanic, this also meant that the Tyrant was very confident in his offense and clearly ignored his 'Indestructible Body' nickname.

"You think it'd be this easy?" Han Xiao snorted. He casually threw a Luck Curse on Heber. Doesn't matter if it works, use it first.

Different strategies had to be used against different opponents. Han Xiao quickly changed his strategy into moving around with his speed and surrounded Heber with his mechanical army.

The mechanical army was more powerful after receiving Beyond Grade A bonuses. With the bonuses that he currently provided with his Machinery Affinity, just a few thousand normal mechanical soldiers would be able to fight a normal Calamity Grade. Furthermore, he had the sustainability given by [Advanced Machinery Construction], so he was not afraid of the battle dragging on.

Most importantly, a huge portion of his mechanical soldiers could penetrate Heber's defenses. Despite the damage dealt being reduced tremendously, given the sheer size of his army, they were able to deal rather considerable damage to even Heber. This was indeed the strength of the Army Style against any class—the Human Wave Tactic would always be a threat.

Han Xiao knew that there were no shortcuts against an opponent like the Tyrant, the only thing he could do was slowly reduce his health.

The energy of the mechanical suit flowed into the thrusters. Han Xiao turned into a stream of light and moved swiftly through the battlefield. The wide battlefield gave him more than enough space to distance himself.

Energy flames erupted with Heber's every movement, like a Fixed Star exploding, shattering tons of mechanical soldiers. However, the shattered machinery quickly reformed under Han Xiao's Mechanical Force and kept intercepting Heber in changing formations.

As a Beyond Grade A, Han Xiao had all kinds of devices that gave him mobility. His speed was higher. Although Heber was not slow, he was much bulkier comparatively, so he could not close the distance.

Heber broke a Giant Soldier into pieces and frowned. The battle will drag for too long this way.

There had been no Beyond Grade A Mechanic in the Shattered Star Ring for many years, so Heber did not have much experience fighting a Mechanic of the same grade, but he knew that the source of a Mechanic's strength came from their knowledge and time.

It had been less than two months since Black Star became a Beyond Grade A, so he had extremely limited time to learn knowledge and did not have enough chances to expand his machinery. This was the time when he would be the easiest to deal with.

Therefore, what Heber wanted was an overwhelmingly one-sided victory, not a protracted battle.

I have to use more energy... Heber took a deep breath, not of air but the dark energy that was everywhere in the universe. Every single one of his cells absorbed the dark energy like a bottomless hole and quickly split open.

The next second, his mountain-sized body expanded, instantly destroying his armor and turning into a tall giant dozens of meters tall. He had entered the second stage directly.

He was a unique Beyond Grade A species. Furthermore, Pugilists Beyond Grade As basically all had one specialty—their Gene Limiter was removed.

In other words, his body strength 'theoretically' had no limits!

Heber extended his palm, aimed at Han Xiao far away, and shook his head.

"You're talented indeed. If you had enough time, you might've become someone like Manison in the future... Pity."

The next moment, everyone's vision was filled with white light.

A blinding light sprayed out from Heber's palm. This Shockwave Blast was extremely fast, and it was not just shot out but could be controlled remotely by Heber.

Han Xiao dodged dozens of times but was still hit by the beam. His entire body showered in the red-gold Pugilist flames.

However, this Shockwave Blast did not explode like expected but solidified into energy like a long tentacle, grabbing Han Xiao.

Judging Energy Level... Judgment failed.

Your Energy Level is lower than the opponent's.

You have entered [Energy Locked] state. You can no longer use energy.

Han Xiao was shocked. The Pugilist flames around him formed a restricting force, making the Mechanical Force in his body entirely quiet and trapped in his cells. His link to his mechanical army was cut.

He tried to break away from the Pugilist flames but was faced with terrifying resistance. His body movements were extremely slow. It was almost as if he was fixed in the beam of light.

"This is..."

Han Xiao's pupils constricted.

"Come here!" Heber quickly pulled with his hand. The red and gold light beam shrank and pulled Han Xiao toward him at a high speed.

Energy was the extension of the body for Pugilists. In terms of the strength of energy, Pugilists were the master among the five Super classes.

To Pugilists, the so-called abilities were just different techniques. There were trillions of Pugilist styles in the universe and countless abilities.

This ability was the compression of Pugilist energy, forming a special force field when hitting the target, suppressing the target's energy with his own energy. It was like deploying a barrier around the target, forcing the target's energy in his body.

This could only be avoided if the target's Energy Level was higher or equal to Heber's. Heber was a senior Beyond Grade A Super who had lived for many years; he knew many energy training techniques, and his Energy Level was unfathomable.

The mechanical army focused fire on Heber under the control of the artificial intelligence. However, without Han Xiao's Mechanical Force enhancements, they could not even penetrate Heber's defenses.

Han Xiao's brain worked quickly.

I need to think of a simple method to get out of this. Heber will definitely use this more than once. The cooldown of Void Hyperdrive is too long. It will work once but not twice...

Suddenly, he had a flash of insight. He activated the talent that he had not used for a very long time—[Chaos Entity - Release]!

He turned into a cluster of gray fog and became a Chaos Body, then immediately followed it up with Void Hyperdrive, getting out of the red-gold light beam before returning to human form.

Void Race's talent... Heber had read Han Xiao's information before and was not surprised.

The intelligence showed that Black Star's Void Travel could not be used for a few minutes. As he had used it now, it meant that he had lost one trump card.

However, what the intelligence did not know was that if Han Xiao used Void Hyperdrive type talents as a Chaos Body, the cooldown would be reduced to just more than ten seconds!

This was the talent of Chaos Observer. Back then, he had not been as famous as he was now, and he rarely showed this ability to anyone!

Han Xiao reconnected with the mechanical army and breathed a sigh of relief in his mind.

Initially, he wanted to fight the Tyrant with his own strength. Now, however, he realized that there was indeed some distance between himself and Heber. Given how tanky he was, his life would not be in danger, but the situation would definitely be bad for him.

Since this battle was witnessed by countless people, Han Xiao did not want to just have the lower hand throughout the entire fight.

I wanted to save this, but apparently, I won't be able to...

Han Xiao licked his lips. He opened the interface and activated an item.

Character Summon Card—Reynold!

Perfect Mechanical Sense!

Han Xiao's eyes widened instantly; his pupils were filled with lightning.

The Mechanical Force flowing inside the mechanical soldiers became blinding. Blue and gold light overflowed from the gaps of the machinery.

At this instant, Han Xiao's Machinery Affinity rocketed. The 1.4 times increase made his mechanical army immensely stronger!

Heber's movements paused for a second, and he looked confused.

It feels a little different.

...

"This is the power of a Beyond Grade A. Amazing..."

The audience stared at the two of them in shock. Many people only had an idea of what Beyond Grade As were, but never had they witnessed any battles between Beyond Grade As. They were all dazzled.

"His Excellency Tyrant is marvelous during battle." Jorde's face was filled with excitement.

Most of the Pugilist officers of the Bloodshed Land had personal admiration for the Tyrant. Seeing the Tyrant showcase his strength, the people of the Bloodshed Land were exhilarated.

On the other hand, the Purple Crystal Civilization and the ally organizations of Han Xiao were all nervous.

Ames did not interfere with their duel. As long as Han Xiao did not say anything, she had no need to fight the Tyrant.

Ames was not closely staring at Psyker. Han Xiao had told her that as soon as Psyker did anything, it was best to stop him instantly.

Psyker glanced at Ames then looked at the battlefield again, narrowing his eyes.

Black Star is stronger than when he fought me, but he's still no match for Heber. The Tyrant getting the upper hand is certain...

Psyker shook his head in his mind. The current situation was within his expectations. He had a very clear idea of how strong the Tyrant was. Black Star being able to fight him evenly did not mean that he could do the same against the Tyrant.

Psyker was not afraid of Heber because psychic attacks happened to be the Tyrant's weakness, just like how he feared the Tyrant's raw strength. Hence, they minded their own business and never messed with each other. However, Black Star could not make use of the Tyrant's weakness like he could, and the Tyrant's raw strength was clearly stronger than a new Beyond Grade A's.

If it was an ordinary new Beyond Grade A, the Tyrant might really kill him. However, having fought Black Star before, Psyker currently had the most knowledge of Black Star's strength, but he did not share this with Heber.

Black Star also has a very tough physical body even among Beyond Grade As, not much worse than Heber's. He should be able to last a very long time. They're still not going all out. When they're more worn out, only then it will be the time for me to make a move...

Thinking of that, Psyker glanced at the Arcane Church flagship behind him.

He knew that in the command room of the flagship, the commander of the fleet was waiting for his signal.

At this time, a meteor-like shadow flashed past the edge of his vision right into the Bloodshed Land's formation not far away, shattering a few spaceships.

Psyker turned and looked over, soon becoming shocked.

The one that was blown away was the Tyrant‽

Psyker was a little stunned. As he quickly turned around and looked at Han Xiao, the look in his eyes gradually changed.

It seems I still underestimated you...

Chapter 777: Sudden

The energy Han Xiao was giving off had become much stronger. The power of the mechanical army had increased instantly. Not expecting this, Heber had been blown away by the countless particle cannon attacks.

Heber's continuously growing momentum was broken, which shocked countless spectators.

"Black Star hid such power..." The look in Psyker's eyes slightly changed.

The energy that Han Xiao was giving off surprised him. He was certain that Black Star had not been this strong when he fought him more than a month ago.

Is this his trump card?

Ames could not help but glance at Han Xiao. A tint of shock flashed through her eyes.

Seeing their own boss penetrating their formation, Jorde's expression changed for the worse. The excitement of the Bloodshed Land officers was instantly extinguished.

Although Heber had merely taken a small hit, the Bloodshed Land officers had initially thought that the Tyrant would have the complete upper hand as the opponent was just a new Beyond Grade A Super. The current turn of events shocked them.

The mechanical army chased after Heber. By this time, Heber had already stabilized himself. His face was grave. Having been taken by surprise, he was a little angry.

His fist charged forward, shooting a thick Pugilist impact wave toward the mechanical army.

The mechanical soldiers responsible for defenses moved from the back to the front, forming an enormous psionic protective shield in front of the army.

The Star Shaking Fist crashed onto the shield. The blinding red and gold light quickly expanded, exploding like a supernova, filling everyone's vision with white light.

As the mechanical army was stopped by the Star Shaking Fist, Heber took the opportunity and dashed out. He made a turn and pulled the battlefield away from the Bloodshed Land's forces. Han Xiao followed right behind and chased him with his mechanical army.

With the enhancements of Perfect Mechanical Sense, the mechanical army was tremendously stronger be it in terms of offense of defense. The millions of mechanical soldiers surrounded a single person, the light of psionic energy flashing nonstop within the battlefield.

Suddenly, Heber slowed down. He endured the focus fire and explosions with his body and launched another [Energy Lock] Shockwave Blast toward Han Xiao.

However, this time, Han Xiao had experience. He quickly escaped from it with his Chaos Body and Void Hyperdrive. Heber was astounded—he had thought that Han Xiao's Void Hyperdrive was still in cooldown.

"The same ability won't work again on me."

Having realized that he had judged it wrong, Heber frowned. Now that this ability no longer worked on Han Xiao, he had no choice but to patiently deal with the mechanical army while thinking of another way.

With every punch, kick, and Shockwave Blast, tons of mechanical soldiers were heavily damaged or even instantly destroyed.

Heber, however, was not unharmed. Wounds gradually started to appear on his mountain-sized body.

With his energy increasing his cell vitality, the old wounds kept recovering, but new wounds kept appearing as well. The mechanical soldiers that he had destroyed were repaired time after time by Han Xiao's [Waste Modification] and [Advanced Machinery Construction].

Feeling the flowing Mechanical Force in his body, Han Xiao was thrilled. Perfect Mechanical Sense is really a god-like ability...

The 1.4 times total Machinery Affinity multiplier was a powerful Molding Talent. The damage the mechanical army dealt to Heber was clearly on another level. More than half of the raw strength difference between him and the Tyrant was mitigated by Perfect Mechanical Sense.

Sadly, this Molding Talent came from Reynold's Character Summon Card and was not yet his own. He only had three chances to use it; this was the second.

After fighting for quite some time, Heber's expression gradually became graver.

Initially, he had thought that no matter how talented the new Beyond Grade A was, his combat capability would not be too high. Yet, Han Xiao's current combat capability had shattered this thought directly.

The situation suddenly became even. Heber's plan to quickly end the battle was instantly broken, and he was forced into destroying machinery with his bare hands in a long battle.

Long battles were the strength of Army Style Mechanics. Heber knew full well that the combat had fallen into Black Star's control. If this carried on, it would be bad for him.

What he wanted was to make an example out of Black Star, but if the battle became even, it would be the other way around.

Not only would he fail to build more reputation, he would even lose it and become a stepping stone for Black Star's name. Black Star was a new Beyond Grade A who lacked fundamentals. Being able to fight him, a known senior Beyond Grade A, evenly would definitely be beneficial for Black Star.

Furthermore, he was the one that had demanded this battle. If he turned out to be unable to defeat Black Star, he would definitely be extremely ashamed.

Close combat was the strength of Pugilists. Although Heber also knew ranged abilities such as the Star Shaking Fist, a Beyond Grade A Mechanic like Black Star had way too many ways to block ranged attacks. In order to heavily damage Black Star, the only chance was to get close to him.

Heber's close-range damage output was horrifying. Among all the Beyond Grade As in Galaxy, no one would remain unharmed after a close-range explosive combo of a Beyond Grade A Pugilist, not even Heber himself.

He did indeed have one ability that could instantly get close to Black Star. However, he could only use it every once in a very long time. Black Star had many dodging and fleeing abilities, so he would be able to easily get away from him again if he failed. Heber was rather troubled.

Slippery guy. Heber frowned. The window of opportunity to get close to Black Star would only last for an instant; he had to wait for a chance.

...

Heber fought intensely with the mechanical army. The explosions lightened up the sights of all the audience. Almost all the spaceship radars of the spectators were repeating alarms continuously.

"High energy reaction detected! Please get away immediately! High energy..."

If the battlefield was a planet, it would have been destroyed long ago.

"It seems even..."

"I can't believe it. Black Star is matching up to the Tyrant."

"The Tyrant seems to have the lower hand now."

Countless spectators were stunned. Their impression of Black Star was continuously refreshed.

Seeing that Han Xiao stood his ground, the Black Star Army players were thrilled.

"Black Star gained control of the battle using the kiting strategy. The Tyrant's only way of breaking this is to get close. However, he seems to be unable to get across the mechanical army." Inside the battleship of the army, Hao Tian analyzed the battle. As a pro player, despite his level not being high, his PVP senses were still very sharp.

"Pugilists are good at explosive power at close range," Frenzied Sword said. "As long as the captain maintains this kiting, he will not be defeated... given that the mechanical army can last that long."

"That's what I thought." Bun-Hit-Dog nodded.

However, at this time, a sudden change occurred in the battlefield. Hao Tian, Frenzied Sword, and the others' expressions changed drastically.

"Not good!"

...

The focus fire of the mechanical army created blinding explosions and obstructed the audience's vision.

At this time, surrounded by the mechanical army, Heber suddenly disappeared.

The next instant, he appeared behind Han Xiao immediately.

As expected. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He had expected this. He had known that Heber would have a teleportation type Pugilist ability, so he had prepared for it long ago. However, he had to admit that Heber had picked a great opportunity.

Just as Han Xiao was about to dodge with Void Hyperdrive, all the abilities on his interface became gray.

_____________________

Heber has used Racial Talent [Giant's Gaze] on you!

You have entered [Forced Silence] state. All abilities are frozen. Duration: 0.3 seconds!

_____________________

Han Xiao's pupils constricted. He had no way to break free from a forced silence type ability. Heber had waited so long to use this and surprised him.

This interrupted his Void Hyperdrive and held him in his place.

With a cold expression, Heber punched right through the psionic shield and onto the Battle Tiger mechanical suit. An impact wave flew into Han Xiao's body.

_____________________

Heber has used the ability [Strength Punch—Molecular Vibration] on you!

Judging... Judgment failed. Your STR is more than 1,000 lower than the opponent's.

You have entered [Out of Control] state. You are unable to control your body. Duration: 0.8 second

_____________________

This is bad.

He had been avoiding getting comboed by Heber all along, but Heber's attacks were not easy to deal with. Now he was on the passive side.

The next second, red and gold fists landed on his body like a thunderstorm. The punches created countless afterimages and pits on the mechanical suit.

Dong! Dong!

Heber's every attack was a different Pugilist ability. As soon as he successfully landed the first disabling ability, he would be able to use continuous disabling abilities. Due to his vastly superior Strength and Dexterity, the Judgements for those abilities would usually all succeed.

The terrifying combo damage caused the armor of Battle Tiger and Han Xiao's own health to plummet.

With cold murderous intent in his eyes, Heber went all out without hesitation—he planned to heavily injure or even immediately kill Han Xiao in one combo!

...

The developments of the battle made the expression of countless people change drastically.

"Black Star is in danger..." Austin murmured.

Being controlled by Heber at close range was more than enough to threaten the life of a Beyond Grade A.

Ames could not help but look over.

"Chance!"

At this instant, Psyker moved. He rushed right into the battlefield, straight toward Han Xiao at an extremely high speed.

Distracted, Ames was a second slower to respond. Anger appeared in her eyes.

Just as she was about to drag Psyker back with her force field, the fleet of the Arcane Church suddenly fired. Highly condensed annihilation beams headed toward Ames.

Ames did not expect the fleet to suddenly attack. She hastily turned around and stopped the attacks of the fleet with her force field.

In just an instant, Psyker approached Han Xiao and Heber.

Black Star is being pinned down by the Tyrant. This is the opportunity to grab the Evolution Cube!

The sudden change of situation shocked everyone. In their eyes, it was clear that the Arcane Church had broken the rules, restraining Ames with their fleet while Psyker suddenly attacked Black Star together with Heber!

It was as if Black Star had fallen into a desperate situation in an instant!

"Teacher!"

"Black Star!"

"Captain!"

The expressions of Sylvia, Herlous, and the army officers all changed drastically!

Chapter 778: Counter

"Hmm?"

As another punch landed on Han Xiao's chest, Heber noticed the abnormality. He quickly turned around and stared at the quickly approaching Psyker.

"Want to grab the Evolution Cube?" Heber looked at Psyker with hostility.

Psyker had publicized the information regarding the Evolution Cube, clearly stating his goal. Although Heber was interested in it, he had no means of locating the Evolution Cube.

He refused to cooperate with Psyker because he did not want anyone to disrupt his duel with Black Star and break his plan to make an example. Seeing that the Arcane Church had suddenly attacked to restrain Ames and Psyker was clearly using him, he was enraged.

His eyes were filled with warning as he stared at Psyker.

Expressionless, Psyker continued to charge forward. He had to retrieve the Evolution Cube even if it meant offending Heber.

In his senses, the Evolution Cube was right on Han Xiao. His psychic energy had already shot toward Han Xiao. As soon as he got the Evolution Cube, he would retreat and not waste energy fighting him.

Seeing that Psyker had ignored his warning, the hostility in Heber's eyes became stronger. However, there was no way he was going to let Black Star go and turn around to attack Psyker.

Psyker had publicly stood against Black Star by demanding a battle with Black Star just like he did, which means that they were on the same side. If he gave up on the opportunity to heavily damage Black Star to stop his supposed 'ally', the situation would go out of control. Psyker had already tied him up using his standpoint.

Due to many factors, Heber had no choice but to watch Psyker approach, unable to stop him. He was enraged.

With a gloomy expression, Heber decided to get back at Psyker after he finished dealing with Black Star.

At this moment, to his shock, his punch was suddenly stopped!

His eyes quickly moved away from Psyker and back to Han Xiao. Shocked, he realized that Han Xiao, who was supposedly unable to move, suddenly regained control and stopped his fists with his hands.

Instantly responding, Heber's muscles expanded. A powerful surge of energy flowed into his arms. Just as he was about to forcefully break away from Han Xiao's block and disable Han Xiao again, he was stunned.

A terrifying power came from Han Xiao's arms that matched his own!

What's going on‽

Heber looked at Han Xiao's face with shock. Half of Han Xiao's mechanical suit helmet was broken, showing half of Han Xiao's face and his calm eyes.

"Really horrifying damage, almost took half of my health..." Han Xiao licked away the blood at the tip of his lips and grinned. "Sadly, we have fought for far more than twenty minutes!"

The mechanical army had stalled the Tyrant for long enough, so he had obtained the Tyrant's Character Summon Card long ago!

[Character Summon Card—'Tyrant' Heber]. Usages: 1/3. Effect: +4,000 STR. Duration: 40 minutes!

With the increase in his Strength, he became immune to Heber's disabling abilities!

The next second, Han Xiao clenched his fists and grabbed Heber's hands. Surging power filled his body. With a turn of his waist, he lifted Heber and threw him right at Psyker!

"What‽" Disbelief appeared in Heber's eyes.

I lost to a Mechanic in a battle of strength‽

Are you kidding me‽

This made Psyker's expression change dramatically as well.

Black Star had obviously been pinned down by Heber; he did not expect him to be able to escape it that fast and with raw strength!

The mechanical army far away regained its Mechanical Force bonuses and fired at Heber and Psyker. Psyker had no choice but to stop and block the attacks with his psychic shield while grabbing Heber and helping him regain balance.

The violent attacks exploded on the psychic shield. The expanding light obstructed their sight.

Before the two of them could make the next move, they suddenly felt a sense of pressure. Turning around, they saw an enormous satellite penetrating the attacks outside the psychic shield and crashing directly toward them.

Not having the time to think about anything else, Heber rapidly absorbed dark energy and turned his body into a giant. His fists launched toward the armed satellite, hoping to stop its impact.

However, the difference in size was too huge. Heber and Psyker were both slapped onto the surface of the satellite.

Ames' eyes were flickering with a green light. Her force field pushed the armed satellite forward like a marble, drawing an arc and crashing toward the Arcane Church's fleet.

The attacks of the Arcane Church fleet had caused her to be unable to stop Psyker in time, which made Ames quite displeased. Luckily, Black Star had gotten out of the dangerous situation himself. Without hesitation, she immediately backed Black Star up and set the Arcane Church fleet as a target as well.

Facing the enormous armed satellite, the Arcane Church fleet fired without hesitation. The storm of dark energy blasts fired on the armed satellite and destroyed it.

This was the biggest explosion since the start of the battle. The strong light caused by it made the eyes of countless spectators hurt and forced them to close their eyes. Only stronger Supers could barely open their eyes.

As the aftershock of the explosion dissipated, only then did everyone see the current situation.

Han Xiao and Ames stood in the middle of the battlefield together, while Heber and Psyker endured the explosion and hovered before the Arcane Church's fleet. Four Beyond Grade As on two sides stood against each other.

The situation had taken too quick a turn, and the people could not react immediately. Once they figured out what happened, their eyes gathered on Han Xiao.

The situation earlier had been dire for Han Xiao, but Han Xiao had used raw strength to fight back against Heber. He had used the most direct and straightforward method to break the situation of being surrounded by Heber and Psyker!

"Hu..." Sylvia took a deep breath—she had been really startled earlier.

Hila's fists opened, and her tense body relaxed.

The audience calmed down and once again focused on the battle.

"Psyker and Ames both acted. It's probably not a duel but a battle now."

"The Arcane Church interfered. Not just the Beyond Grade As, even the fleets of two sides might start fighting!"

"The Crimson Dynasty will definitely respond as well; this might cause another war."

"I feel like we should back off a little more..."

Countless people were feeling nervous. The Arcane Church's involvement changed what was initially a duel between Beyond Grade As. The situation became complicated.

Just in terms of forces, Heber's side with the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church had the complete upper hand. If the fleets took part in the battle, Black Star's side would definitely be at a disadvantage.

Psyker's expression was not looking good. After his failed attempt, his plan was shattered. Since he had already acted, he would not be able to watch from the side anymore. He could only snatch the Evolution Cube head-on, which would be much more difficult.

He turned around, looked at Heber, and saw that Heber was looking at him with sharp eyes as well.

Psyker knew that he had offended the Tyrant due to what he had just done. He sighed in his head before speaking to Heber with psychic energy.

"Ames has joined the battle; you won't be able to duel Black Star anymore. They will fight you two on one, so you need help. We'll settle what happened earlier in the future. Let's work together first. I have the Arcane Church; you have the Crimson Dynasty. Using our fleets, help me retrieve the Evolution Cube, and the Arcane Church and myself will give you more than enough benefits."

Heber frowned. His plan was messed up, and he really wanted to suffocate Psyker. When Psyker asked him to work together, he had suggested a similar plan. Back then, he had rejected it, and he still did not want to agree.

He did not invite the Crimson Dynasty; they had made a certain deal with Klent, which Heber did not know the details of. However, since the Crimson Dynasty had come, they were there to back him up. He did not want a duel to turn into a full out war—it would be far off from his initial intentions.

At this time, the Crimson Dynasty's fleet suddenly moved, attracting everyone's attention.

The Crimson Dynasty fleet turned around, aiming their countless cannons at the Arcane Church's fleet. Before anyone could react, the Crimson Dynasty fleet suddenly fired!

Countless particle cannon beams blasted into the Arcane Church's fleet. Suddenly being attacked from the side, the Arcane Church had no time to react.

At this moment, everyone was stunned!

Wh—What's going on‽

Han Xiao's eyes lit up suddenly.

"Zoel acted!"

Chapter 779: Your Ally Is Not Bad...

What is the Crimson Dynasty doing‽ Jorde was stunned. He could not understand why the Crimson Dynasty suddenly attacked the Arcane Church. Aren't we on the same side today?

Ralph was startled by this sudden turn of events as well. He was at a loss. Both the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church were on the enemy's side, so why did one suddenly attack the other‽

The Arcane Church hastily adjusted their formation to face the Crimson Dynasty. While guarding against the attacks, they tried to counterattack. The Crimson Dynasty was behind the Bloodshed Land formation, so the Bloodshed Land fleet and the Klent fleet were affected as well.

Psyker's expression suddenly changed as he quickly distanced himself from Heber.

"Was this your plan‽"

All kinds of speculations appeared in his mind. Was Heber's sudden betrayal revenge for his earlier interference, or was this planned long ago? Could it be that Heber was so mad that not only did he want to make an example out of Black Star but him as well?

Could it be that the Crimson Dynasty wanted to use this opportunity to get rid of him, an Arcane Church ally in the Shattered Star Ring?

Psyker could not help but to make many guesses. However, he realized that Heber looked puzzled as well, as if he did not know why the Crimson Dynasty had suddenly attacked.

Heber had no time to care about what Psyker was thinking. He turned into a meteor and flew back to the Bloodshed Land formation, entering the closest spaceship and borrowing their communicator.

"Jorde! Contact the Crimson Dynasty's men and ask them what they're doing!"

"Your Excellency Tyrant, their commander told us to attack the Arcane Church with them and did not mention the reason!" Jorde hastily replied in the communication channel.

"Then contact Klent's men. Tell them to ask the Dynasty Emissary Zoel for the reason."

"O—okay," Jorde replied. "The officials on their mother planet are trying to contact Zoel."

Zoel had been staying in the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Building on the Klent Mother Planet all along. He had only deployed the Crimson Dynasty garrison but did not go to the scene personally.

The two Universal Civilization garrison fleets had fired at each other. Many nearby observers were affected and blasted into pieces.

The other observers backed away in panic. Countless spaceships turned around and escaped from the battlefield.

The situation became chaotic in an instant. Everyone was busy dodging stray bullets, and no one paid attention to the main participants.

The Black Star Army and the Purple Crystal's fleet on the other side were not affected. Seeing that the enemies were in chaos, they were confused. Han Xiao did not publicize becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally, so Han Xiao and the Crimson Dynasty were the only ones that knew about it.

Due to the sudden change, both Heber and Psyker's attention was diverted, and they had no time to care about Han Xiao. Han Xiao and Ames, who were in the middle of the battlefield, did not chase after them. They looked at the battle between the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church from far away.

Han Xiao suddenly smiled.

"With the Crimson Dynasty's attack, this should end soon."

"This is your doing?" Ames turned to look at Han Xiao, and then it occurred to her. "You've joined the Crimson Dynasty."

She did not know about this either. Before this, she had thought that she was Han Xiao's most powerful ally there.

"The Tyrant wants to step on me to increase his reputation, and Psyker wants to take back the Evolution Cube," Han Xiao said slowly. "I also want to use this opportunity today to increase my influence. I'm a new Beyond Grade A Super, so I need to achieve many deeds to have a reputation like the Tyrant's, which will take too long. An opportunity for the Tyrant is also an opportunity for me; I can use this battle to obtain a ton of reputation and fame."

Ames raised her brows and said, "It sounds like you don't need my help to deal with the dangers today, or did you think I'm not good enough?"

"Don't misunderstand, I'm just used to having more than one plan." Han Xiao smiled with resignation.

...

The Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church did not turn out to fight a full out war. Very soon, both sides stopped firing and distanced themselves from one another. The atmosphere was tense.

Still puzzled, the observers all focused on the Crimson Dynasty's fleet from far away. Everyone wanted to know why the Crimson Dynasty had done what they just did.

At this time, the trillions of spaceships at the scene all received a message from the Crimson Dynasty. This was an announcement made in the official civilization public communication channel—a channel shared by the civilizations above the Star System level, only used to make official announcements. Any message sent using this channel would be received by all devices within a certain area.

"This is the Crimson Dynasty Shattered Star Ring Garrison K-004 Fleet Commander, Sciurio, hereby sending a warning to the Arcane Church...

"Firstly, this battle is monitored by the Crimson Dynasty. Any organization breaking the rules will be firmly stopped by us. Your interference has violated the rules.

"Secondly, the Black Star Army is the Crimson Dynasty's ally. The Evolution Cube currently belongs to the Crimson Dynasty. Any organization planning to snatch it will be seen as the Dynasty's enemy!"

After hearing this announcement—be it Klent, the Bloodshed Land, the Purple Crystal Civilization, even the Black Star Army, or any other observer—everyone's eyes widened with shock.

When did Black Star become the Crimson Dynasty's ally‽

So, the Crimson Dynasty is actually not here to help the Tyrant but Black Star!

Everyone was stunned.

Heber's expression changed drastically. "Why didn't I know about this‽"

Jorde's mind was blank.

The Bloodshed Land was the Crimson Dynasty's ally, and now the Black Star Army had become the Crimson Dynasty's ally. Did that not mean that they were now on the same side‽

The two sides had fought for a decade, but they had become allies‽

"What the f..." Summer Night Flower's expression stiffened, and his face turned pale.

Initially, he had thought the Bloodshed Land's biggest advantage was having the Crimson Dynasty as their backer. Now, however, the Black Star Army had the same thing.

As his last shred of hope shattered, Summer Night Flower's heart was filled with regret.

Suddenly, his vision was blocked by a shadow. He turned around and saw that the players around had surrounded him with unfriendly expressions on their faces.

...

"The Black Star Army has become the Crimson Dynasty's ally. When did this happen‽"

Ralph was astonished.

Comparatively, all the players of the Black Star Army were overjoyed by this news.

Opposing the Crimson Dynasty was not optimal. They had initially been worried about the Black Star Army's future. They had never expected the army to become the Crimson Dynasty's ally!

The millions of army players were relieved immediately. Becoming an ally of a Universal Civilization meant that the Black Star Army had a channel for even more growth and that its potential was even greater!

Many players' previously shaken beliefs became firm once again, and they were more confident in the army now than ever!

"Sh*t, I thought it was the end of us."

"The captain somehow got to the Crimson Dynasty. The term 'Black Star Networking Group' is definitely accurate."

"It seems that our army will most likely last for many versions."

"Amazing, I'm going to be famous again." Bun-Hit-Dog recorded footage with a huge grin on his face.

Inside the Black Star Army flagship, the many Calamity Grade officers breathed a sigh of relief, followed by joy.

"The captain made a backup plan long ago!"

With the Crimson Dynasty backing them, the Black Star Army was no longer an ordinary Beyond Grade A organization!

The many officers were thrilled and glad that they made the bet years ago to become a pillar of the army!

They did not make a mistake in believing in Black Star!

Inside the Palace of Hidden Spells, Austin's eyes sparkled.

"I see. Not only did you showcase your power by fighting the Tyrant, but you also publicly announced your support from the Crimson Dynasty, enhancing your reputation and indirectly solving your battle with the Tyrant. You single-handedly turned this feast today into an event to increase your fame. Heber and Psyker both fell right into it. You're the biggest winner this time..."

A strange smile appeared on Austin's face.

"Good, a person with ambition. The Shattered Star Ring is finally going to become boisterous."

...

"No wonder you were so calm. You joined the Crimson Dynasty using the Evolution Cube..."

Psyker had a complicated feeling. Now that the Crimson Dynasty had their hands on the Evolution Cube, the difficulty in snatching it back was beyond his abilities.

Seeing the situation, he sighed and sent a message to the Arcane Church Fleet Commander.

"Retreat."

With the Crimson Dynasty expressing their standpoint, no matter what the Bloodshed Land and Klent were thinking, the Crimson Dynasty would be part of this. Since Black Star and the Tyrant stood on the same side and he had become their common enemy. The Arcane Church fleet would not be able to do anything by staying there.

After considering both the pros and cons, Psyker felt retreating was the best choice. Hence, even though he was very displeased, he still made a decisive decision.

Under the eyes of the crowd, the Arcane Church fleet slowly retreated and left the battlefield, turning into a stream of light and disappearing. The Crimson Dynasty did not stop them; their goal had been to make the Arcane Church retreat all along.

"The Arcane Church has retreated!"

"Psyker left, too."

Countless people turned to look at Heber. With one of the people that demanded a duel with Black Star leaving, the Tyrant was the only one left. The direction of the situation was in the Tyrant's hands.

Originally, everyone had thought that the Tyrant and Black Star were enemies, but they had just discovered that they were allies. This duel had become an internal conflict between the Crimson Dynasty's allies.

Hence, the Tyrant was in a very awkward position. Heber's earlier confusion looked sincere, so most people believed that Heber did not know about this.

If that's the case, will he still insist on fighting Black Star now?

The situation had taken many turns, and no one knew what was going to happen next.

The Bloodshed Land remained at the ready. Heber did not return to the battlefield to continue fighting Han Xiao immediately. He narrowed his eyes and looked at Han Xiao from far away, and Han Xiao was looking at him.

As Heber did not make a move, the battlefield had entered a strange silence.

Inside the spaceship, Heber asked Jorde in a deep voice, "Did Klent respond?"

"They're still talking to the Crimson Dynasty..." Jorde could hear that Heber's tone was unpleasant.

...

At the same time, in the Crimson Dynasty embassy on the Klent Mother Planet...

"Envoy Zoel, what is the meaning of this? Didn't the Crimson Dynasty agree to fight Black Star together with us? Why did you accept Black Star as an ally?"

The outcry of the Klent high-level officials sounded from the communicator. Zoel raised his eyelids and slowly replied, "I don't think I ever agreed to this request. I dispatched the garrison to the venue and only said that it was to back up our ally. Klent is our ally, as is Black Star. Our target is just Psyker and the Arcane Church backing him up. You misunderstood, that's all."

"But you did not notify us about Black Star becoming your ally!"

"Oh?" Zoel raised his brows. "Does the Dynasty have to notify you every time we gain an ally? Do you also want the Dynasty to give you all of our military secrets?"

Chapter 780: Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation

"I did not say that. But you knew Black Star is our enemy, yet you did not tell us about it. Doesn't that go against our agreement? If we'd known that Black Star was on our side in advance, we definitely would've told the Tyrant to cancel this duel, and the joke today wouldn't have happened."

"You're exaggerating it." Zoel was not angry and smiled. "Hiding this news was Black Star's request, and I agreed personally. I dispatched the garrison to the scene to prevent the situation from getting out of hand. Furthermore, didn't the results of what happened today turn out to be beneficial? The entire Star Field now knows you people and the Black Star Army have become allies, which is beneficial for both of you. Overall, not only did you guys not suffer any damage, but you actually benefited from it. After all, such a grant occasion like this rarely happens."

The Klent official clenched his teeth and smiled. "... Looks like we misunderstood you."

"That's right. Sigh, but I am indeed responsible for this. How about this? I will confess my wrongdoings to the Dynasty superiors and request for resources compensation for you. What do you think?" Zoel said with a smile.

"There's no need for that. We misunderstood you in the first place; you've done nothing wrong."

"Alright then. Nonetheless, to express my apology, please accept the resources compensation."

"Okay."

As Zoel ended the communication, the smile on his face disappeared instantly. He nodded with satisfaction.

Klent is smart, good.

...

Not long after, the Bloodshed Land received Klent's message at the scene.

"Your—Your Excellency Tyrant, Klent has responded," Jorde stammered.

"Speak."

"They said that Zoel was the one that agreed to make Black Star an ally. Klent told us to stop the duel and re—retreat immediately..."

Klent knew that they had been tricked by the Crimson Dynasty, but what could they do? They still wanted a piece of the Flickering World, so it was impossible for them to rescind the agreement. They could only swallow it up.

Black Star's chips were too attractive. Klent knew clearly that the Crimson Dynasty would certainly not reject the Evolution Cube, so they could only accept it. Fortunately, the duel was mainly the Tyrant's idea; Klent did not suffer much damage, so they had quickly compromised.

Heber closed his eyes.

After a while, he then reopened his eyes and squeezed out a word between his clenched teeth.

"Retreat."

The order sounded from the Bloodshed Land's commanding channel. The many Bloodshed Land officers all became spiritless, like they had lost all their energy.

Jorde's face twitched with resentment, but there was nothing he could do.

The Crimson Dynasty, Klent, and the Bloodshed Land's fleets left one after another, leaving only Purple Crystal and the Black Star Army's people at the scene.

"The Bloodshed Land retreated, haha!"

In the countless battleships, the warriors of the Black Star Army cheered with joy.

Influenced by the atmosphere, many players followed along in the cheering.

Ames smiled.

Although Han Xiao keeping this a secret made her feel a little unhappy, seeing Heber getting tricked by them made her feel very pleased.

The expression on Han Xiao's face under the helmet was filled with mockery. "Tyrant? Hehe."

As their battle had been stopped, a winner was not decided. However, during the battle, he had fought the Tyrant on even ground, so no one would think that he had joined the Crimson Dynasty because he was afraid of the Tyrant.

On the other hand, despite being the one initiating this duel, the Tyrant had left in the end. This meant that Heber had become his stepping stone, defining his position in the Shattered Star Ring. He would no longer be underestimated by some people because he was a new Beyond Grade A.

At this time, a Legendary Point notification popped up on the interface.

You have received 3 Legendary Points.

Star Field Legendary Point (Shattered Star Ring): Battle Against Tyrant—Your battle with 'Tyrant' Heber is known by all of the Shattered Star Ring. This battle will be passed around by one after another across this Star Field, along with your name.

Star Field Legendary Point (Shattered Star Ring): Ally of the Crimson Dynasty—Universal Civilizations are the biggest forces of this galaxy. You have become an ally of one of them, the Crimson Dynasty.

Star Field Legendary Point (Shattered Star Ring): Star Field Signature Character—Your name echoes through the entire Star Field as one of the signatures of this Star Field. From this day forth, whenever the Shattered Star Ring is mentioned, your name will be linked to it.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Star Field Legendary Points' bonus to experience was much higher than that of Star Cluster Legendary Points, and they were extremely difficult to obtain. He had received three at once, which meant that his plan to command respect through this duel had been very successful.

When what had happened spread throughout the universe, his reputation in the Shattered Star Ring would certainly rocket once again.

At this time, Ralph sent a communication request.

Han Xiao knew what Purple Crystal's reaction to this would be, so he had thought of what to say long ago.

"Black Star..."

The communication connected. Ralph's face appeared on the tactical screen under the mechanical suit helmet. Ralph looked hesitant.

"I know what you're going to say." Han Xiao spoke first. "Becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally was my idea. As you guys know, the secret war is not looking good for us. In order to destroy Klent's plan, the only way is to do it through people with a high position. Using myself as the chip, I exchanged for their stand regarding the secret war. This was the method to win the secret war I told you about."

Ralph opened his eyes with a complicated expression.

He had initially thought Black Star would abandon Purple Crystal. Once he heard what Han Xiao said, he felt much better.

Luckily, Black Star still remembered Purple Crystal's support and requested the dynasty to give them some benefits. At least he was not someone to abandon them even after accepting so many resources from them.

"You and the Crimson Dynasty, sigh..."

"I know you guys hope to maintain the neutral ground of the civilization, but I'm different. I'm Purple Crystal's ally, too, like a bridge between you guys and the Crimson Dynasty. This will be beneficial to a certain extent for all three of us.

Ralph nodded. This was indeed true.

He knew what Han Xiao meant—he wanted to be the Crimson Dynasty's ally while continuing being Purple Crystal's ally.

Of course, Purple Crystal was not satisfied with this. They had funded and supported the Black Star Army for close to a decade, all because they wanted to be the biggest partner of a Beyond Grade A. However, a Universal Civilization had gotten to Han Xiao first. Ralph was unsatisfied.

However, after more thought, he could only feel resignation. After that fight, the Black Star Army would become even more powerful. If Purple Crystal rescinded the agreement, the Black Star Army would not be afraid since they had an even better ally. In the end, the ones suffering the most losses would be Purple Crystal.

The best solution currently was to continue the partnership and share the profit brought by the Black Star Army.

After investing so much resources for so long, Purple Crystal was not willing to gain nothing.

"Understood. I will report this to the upper echelons..." Ralph calmed his emotions down and secretly admired Black Star's guts.

"Wait for the good news." Han Xiao smiled.

If he was just an ordinary Beyond Grade A, he might not have been able to make the Crimson Dynasty change their standpoint on the secret war. However, with the Evolution Cube in his hands, things were different.

Han Xiao ended the communication and secretly felt relieved.

Things were going great. Han Xiao felt relaxed. Having become a Beyond Grade A, he had truly entered the top circle of Galaxy. Most of the restrictions he had once faced as a Calamity Grade were now gone, and the weight of his name had become tremendously heavier.

This time, a teleportation gate opened beside Han Xiao and Ames. Austin, who had been observing from the side, walked out from it.

"Hehe, congratulations, Black Star," Austin said with a smile.

"Hehe..." Han Xiao replied with a smile as well.

"This isn't a good place to talk. Let's chat again during the next Tyrant Party." Austin did not say much.

Then, he teleported back to the Palace of Hidden Spells and activated the spells on it. The palace flew into the teleportation gate and disappeared.

"Tyrant Party..."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He wondered if the Tyrant would invite him to the next party.

"Since things are settled, I shall get going." Ames waved and flew back to Floating Dragon. Floating Dragon slowly left.

Han Xiao watched Ames leave. He then returned to the Black Star Army's flagship and entered the command room, where the army officers gathered. As soon as he walked in, everyone looked at him with admiration in their eyes.

"Sylvia, Herlous, announce the fleet to return," Han Xiao said.

"Roger!" Sylvia's face was filled with excitement.

"Also, using the Black Star Army's name, issue a recruitment order to the entire Star Field. It's time for those who have been observing to make a choice." Han Xiao smiled.

Due to the Tyrant's invitation to the duel, the Black Star Army had been keeping a low profile. Since the matter had been dealt with, it was time for the Black Star Army to expand and officially become a Beyond Grade A organization!

Many officers were exhilarated—this was what they had been waiting for!

Han Xiao turned and looked at Feidin. He had yet to complete the mission to draw the Tyrant's ability because he wanted to touch Feidin for some luck.

Patting Feidin on the shoulder, Han Xiao gave everyone a few words of encouragement and sent all the officers away, saying that he needed to rest.

Han Xiao returned to his room alone and opened the interface to claim the reward.

You have received the reward: Draw Heber's one ability/talent.

Tip: Heber is a Pugilist. Part of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing... complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Phantom Combo]—Ability: +75% close-range attack speed. Duration: 7s. Cost: 80 Energy. Cooldown: 18s

[Star Tossing Power]—Ability: Use energy to enhance your cells, +600 STR. Duration: 20s. Cooldown: 120s

[Weakness Observation]—Ability: +30% close range Critical Chance. Duration: 15s. Cooldown: 180s

[Close Range Killer]—Talent: +40% close-range attack and attack speed. +2 levels to all close-range combat abilities.

[Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation]—Ability: A secret technique the Tyrant uses to cultivate his energy. Current Effect: +500 Energy. Training Times: 0/650. This must be used on a Fixed Star. The effect of every training session depends on the time spent on the Fixed Star. Maximum effect per training: 25 Energy. Minimum: 0. Cost: 6,000,000 Experience per training session.

Scanning through the first four options, Han Xiao was a little disappointed. Beyond Grade A Pugilists had many abilities, so the chance of getting something good was exceedingly low. The first four options all had very limited effects.

However, the last option made Han Xiao surprised.

This is what Heber uses to train his energy?

This is good stuff.

Some of the Pugilists' powerful energy came from talents and some came from cultivation type abilities.

When someone reached Beyond Grade A and wanted to continue becoming stronger, they would start searching for all sorts of abilities to train their energy. The longer one had been a Beyond Grade A Super, the stronger one's energy would usually be.

His current health-energy cycle had reached an obstacle. This was because of his energy number—compared to his two million or so health, he only had fifty thousand energy, and this became a restriction to how tanky he was.

Although [Radiation Absorption] increased his energy, it required a very long time. Even if he searched for Energy Training Techniques like the other Beyond Grade As, it would also be highly time-consuming. Heber's Energy Training Technique, however, was the shortcut he needed at the moment to increase his strength. A high-grade secret technique created by a Beyond Grade A would have a considerable effect on increasing his energy.

As for the experience cost that was enormous for the players... Han Xiao happened to have the experience penalty for more than ten months, so there was no need for him to level up.

The other four options were not very useful, so Han Xiao selected the last option without hesitation.

You have received [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation]!

Han Xiao closed the interface with satisfaction.

"The biggest problem is temporarily settled. Next is the expansion of the Black Star Army. Plans regarding the Flickering World need to be brought forward as well. Speaking of which, when the army stabilizes, I will need to visit the Central Galaxy once..."

...

At the same time somewhere in the Central Galaxy, a broadcast of the duel in the Shattered Star Ring was playing on the screen. It had come to an end, and people started leaving.

Beep.

The broadcast was shut down, and EsGod's face was reflected on the dark screen.

"Contact Black Star."

Chapter 781: EsGod's Suggestion

The viewers at the scene and in front of their screens could not calm down for a long time, watching as the Black Star Army's fleet left.

At this instant, in their hearts, the position of the Black Star Army had risen to that of the Bloodshed Land, deeply carved into their hearts.

During the return journey, Han Xiao made a detour and stopped by a fixed star in order to test out the effectiveness of [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation]. He told the fleet to pause for a moment whilst he flew over to the surface of the Fixed Star.

Without donning his mechanical suit, the strong infrared radiation and high temperatures directly hit his body. The closer the distance, the higher the intensity.

When he had reached a certain distance, the words [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation] on his interface lit up, signaling that it was able to be used.

After spending millions of experience, Han Xiao began his first cultivation session.

The energy in his body boiled up instantly, frantically absorbing the energy that was radiated by the star. His skin turned red, and the brightness continuously rose.

That's right. I should activate [Radiation Absorption] as well.

At this moment, a stream of radiation shot out from the fixed star straight toward Han Xiao, resembling a crimson tsunami. Han Xiao did not avoid nor retreat but rather allowed the fixed star radiation to engulf him. His HP dropped a notch.

Under the high temperature, his HP decreased without stopping, but it very quickly filled up once again using his energy. The effect of the Stellar Furnace Cultivation would depend on the length of his stay on the star. The reason it was classified as a high-level cultivation method was because there were practically no Grade As that could survive on a fixed star, but with the current fleshly body of our Great Mechanic Han, he could live on this fixed star till he died of old age.

"This is literally taking a bath among the stars." Han Xiao played with a lump of stellar energy from the fixed star, rolling it on his chest like bubbles as he roared in laughter.

After enduring for half an hour, the interface indicated that the effect of his cultivation had reached its limit. Only then did Han Xiao leave the fixed star. The count on his Stellar Furnace Cultivation now read 1, which added an extra 25 Energy to him.

For every half an hour, I get 25 energy. If I practice it 650 times, which is to completion, I will receive a total of 16,000 energy, which converts to almost 80,000 HP.

Han Xiao was in a good mood. Having reached Beyond Grade A, increasing his strength had become more difficult than before. The opportunity for him to improve so much was rare, thus making him feel that this was some peerless divine technique.

After finishing his test of the Stellar Furnace Cultivation skill, Han Xiao returned to the fleet. After settling the affairs of his army, he would have the free time to practice this Energy Training Technique.

...

"The Black Star Army has allied with the Crimson Dynasty, and the Evolution Cube is now under the ownership of the Crimson Dynasty, forcing the Arcane Church to retreat."

"Black Star became famous in his battle, causing the Tyrant to voluntarily retreat!"

"Our field reporters were all unfortunately killed, and according to the incomplete statistics, the casualty rate of the spectators reached tens of millions..."

The dust from the battle had settled, but its impact had spread like a tornado throughout the entire Shattered Star Ring, making headlines on every major news channel.

This event had attracted the attention of too many people. The five Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring had all gathered, and while the process was not long, the situation had changed again and again. For everyone, Black Star was the greatest protagonist in this event, having fought with the Tyrant. The most shocking thing was that the Crimson Dynasty had gone against expectations and announced the joining of Black Star in a high-profile manner. This was something no one had expected.

Everyone knew that this signified another Beyond Grade A gaining a solid foothold in Galaxy. With a hegemon as a backer, and that day's matters being enough to be recorded in the history of Shattered Star Ring, it was a signal that the flow of the Star Field was about to change.

The day after the battle, the Black Star Army issued a recruitment order to the entire Star Field.

For a period of time, countless people who had only been watching felt an urge to respond.

With the Crimson Dynasty as a backer, the Black Star Army naturally did not lack resources, and their leader Black Star was even a Beyond Grade A who had proved his abilities. Such a new-born force had an immense future, and the benefits they provided would be many.

The Black Star Army recruitment order was like a deep-sea mine, setting off a huge wave in the Shattered Star Ring. Only a day after the order was issued, spaceships had already set off from the various Star Clusters, heading directly toward the headquarters of the Black Star Army in the Colton Star Cluster.

A multitude of applicants gathered. This was the largest recruitment in the history of the army. Phillip received tens of millions, or even hundreds of millions, of resumes and application forms every day.

Many organizations in the Shattered Star Ring also threw out olive branches to the Black Star Army.

...

"You want to merge under my name and let me be the chief of the Mercenary League? That's not a problem, but you must continue to be responsible for the daily affairs... Yes, that's roughly what it means. We can do it this way. When the time comes, we'll jointly declare to the Star Field that the Mercenary League is now anchored under my name."

After ending the call with Gureja, Han Xiao pinched the bridge of his nose. He had already lost count of how many organizations had contacted him over the past few days and proposed such requests.

Some of his mercenary allies wanted to take advantage of his renown, but this mainly went for organizations that were closer to him. For example, Serbia the Fifth of Godora had called the day before, explaining that he wanted to organize another political visit. He hoped that the Black Star Army would not relocate its headquarters as well and stay near Planet Golden Gate.

Because of the existence of the Black Star Army, Planet Golden Gate had ushered in a period of explosive development in its recent years. With its original purpose as a transportation hub as well, the economy had become extremely prosperous.

Serbia the Fifth also wanted to invite Han Xiao to become an honorary officer of Godora, but the intention behind this was too obvious, and he was directly rejected by Han Xiao. A Golden Gal Badge was good enough for him, and the position of honorary officer would affect the position of the Black Star Army.

A Star System level Civilization could not satisfy Han Xiao's appetite. With a godly support tool like the Evolution Cube in his hands, he had to watch which civilizations he chose to integrate with. Thus, it was not suitable to take such a clear stand with Godora.

The many civilizations in the Colton Star Cluster had also contacted him, of which a majority were those whom he had received mining rights from. Now that he had established his position through the battle with the Tyrant, those civilizations were trying to deepen the connection they had. In addition to gaining a Beyond Grade A as an ally, it was more because they lusted for the Evolution Cube.

Their alliance contract had a change in terms, which included expanding the mining area of the resource planet, allowing them to establish more branches and so on. To summarize, each civilization basically took out a large slice of their own benefits and distributed it to Han Xiao, accepting him as a high-level power in Galaxy.

However, regarding the agreement on the Evolution Cube, Han Xiao had left the other civilizations on hold and did not lock it down immediately. With something as good as the Evolution Cube on his hands, he did not intend to rush into obtaining benefits immediately. Since he had the seller's advantage, he might as well take his time to decide.

Another issue was that many small organizations were requesting to merge with the Black Star Army. There was no shortage of organizations that were helmed by Calamity Grades. There were even several organizations in Section Zero that wished to become members of the army. After all, the temptation of the Crimson Dynasty was too great.

The last group consisted of all the financial groups actively investing to cover the cost of the expansion of the organization. Money had an extraordinary strength, and the expansion of the Black Star Army could be proportionally related to how much investment they obtained from the financial group.

Before he even got to rest a few minutes, his communicator rang once again. It was Zoel calling.

"Black Star... no, I should be addressing you as Your Excellency Black Star now." Zoel smiled.

Han Xiao replied sarcastically before asking, "Envoy, why have you called me today?"

Upon getting to the main topic, Zoel no longer bothered with the pleasantries, immediately saying, "Now that we've already announced our alliance, we have to plan for our future cooperation. As for your alliance, the Dynasty has decided to first settle the matters of the Shattered Star Ring, which is your secret war."

Interesting. Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

"Klent is preparing to submit a proposal during the Galaxy Central Civilization Court, asking for a complete reshuffling of the Colton Star Cluster and Seoul Star Clusters, which will be mediated and decided by the three Universal Civilizations."

The Galaxy Central Civilization Court was the most formal place where the three Universal Civilizations had agreed to mediate disputes. It covered all Star Clusters, Star Field, and Star System Civilizations, with some special ethnic groups even having seats inside it, uniting the vast majority of civilizations in the universe to discuss and resolve their problems. It was an extremely formal process.

"Since Klent is also your ally, what do you plan to do?" Han Xiao asked.

"We plan to talk to Klent in private, asking them to give up the idea of submitting a proposal." Zoel nodded. Because Klent was also their ally, the Dynasty could not be too harsh in dealing with them. They would not sit idly by and allow Klent to submit the proposal.

In fact, Klent's scheming for the territory of the Purple Crystal Civilization was not the intention of the Crimson Dynasty but something Klent had decided on themselves to satisfy their own ambitions using the banner of the Dynasty. This sort of thing was too common, and as long as they did not exceed certain boundaries, the Crimson Dynasty would turn a blind eye to this matter. However, since they now had other considerations, they had the authority to put a stop to Klent's plans.

Of course, the Dynasty would definitely give some sort of compensation, such as giving Klent more territorial benefits in their division of the Flickering World.

"Klent is very knowledgeable, and they know that it will be useless for them to disagree. The Arcane Church was also hit by us and will definitely obstruct Klent's proposal to get back at us. Without us opening our mouth, the proposal will not pass." Zoel waved his hands.

"That's true as well." Han Xiao nodded. He did not feel that the Arcane Church would be one to swallow this injustice silently; they would look for a place to vent. The political stage would be one such area.

"Now that your Black Star Army and Bloodshed Land are our allies, we will work together to open up the Flickering World in the future. Thus, after solving the problem of the secret war, you guys have to have a good talk with each other, turning from enemies to allies," Zoel said.

The Crimson Dynasty valued the development of the Flickering World, and their two allies in the Shattered Star Ring were the pioneers for exploring it. Naturally, the dynasty did not wish to see its two allies affect the exploration of the new Star Field because of mutual misgivings. Even if it was only a superficial reconciliation, they wanted to see some effort put in by them.

"That's alright with me. However, I'm not sure what Ty-Ty will say." Han Xiao shrugged in response.

Hearing this, Zoel also helplessly smiled. The party that had lost the most this time was the Bloodshed Land, and he would definitely have quite a lot of say.

After pausing for a while, Zoel said, "As for the last matter, the Dynasty will soon send the first batch of people to undergo the Evolution Cube transformation. When I know the exact time, I'll inform you once again."

Han Xiao nodded in response. This had already been discussed in their contract; the Crimson Dynasty had the right to utilize the Evolution Cube.

While he did not know who would be within the first batch of people from the Crimson Dynasty, they would naturally be elites. Maybe Han Xiao would see some 'familiar faces' within.

After exchanging a few more pleasantries, Han Xiao then ended the communication. Just as he hung up, his communicator rang once more. It was an unknown number this time.

Pausing for a moment, he answered the call, and his expression changed.

On the screen was the ugly face of EsGod.

"Black Star." The corners of the EsGod's mouth were curled up in a strange smile as it greeted him.

Han Xiao only stared at the screen and did not talk. He did not expect EsGod to actually contact him. Toward this reputedly fierce Beyond Grade A brute, he still had his reservations.

"I have a deal to discuss with you."

"What is it?"

The EsGod smiled. "Rest assured, I won't snatch your Evolution Cube. You're different from Psyker, and you're not as stubborn as him."

"What are you trying to say?"

"Now that the Evolution Cube is in your hands," EsGod leisurely said, "let's make a deal. Let me use it once, and I'll help you with one matter."

Han Xiao immediately narrowed his eyes. EsGod's claim that he would not snatch the Evolution Cube was something that Han Xiao did not believe. Furthermore, making a deal with EsGod was akin to trying to scheme against a tiger for its skin.

Before he could reply, EsGod said, "I understand that your alliance with the Crimson Dynasty has just started, and you have your reservations. However, for someone like you who is bound by the rules of order, there will be a point when you require a lawless thug to help you achieve something... You don't have to be in a hurry to answer me. When you've thought it through, you can call me again to give your answer."

Smiling, EsGod shut off the communication.

Han Xiao furrowed his brows, his finger stopping at the option to delete the encrypted number of EsGod.

After pausing for a long time...

His finger swiped down.

EsGod's number was placed in his blacklist.

He did not delete it.

...

Spaceship after spaceship landed on Planet Aquamarine, carved with various insignias belonging to different financial groups. All of them were material transport ships carrying a large amount of resources.

Bennett, together with the Aquamarine Federation, stood at the dock as they watched the mechanical workers moving the supplies one by one.

As the hometown of a Beyond Grade A, they had received even more investment and support from the financial groups.

Bennett could not help but turn his head, looking outside the door of the hangar to the huge black statue erect at the center of the city. There was a touch of relief and gratitude in his eyes.

Chapter 782: Interlude, an Unexpected Guest

The headquarters of the Black Star Army started to get lively.

In the following half a month after the recruitment order was issued, countless spaceships flew into the headquarters to pay them a visit. All of them were candidates that had been vetted by Phillip and the alliance, and they went to the headquarters to meet Black Star and await the final review of the Army Commander.

While the fleet that had gone for the battle had yet to return to the headquarters, all the new members were orderly lined up in the satellite base's outer layer, awaiting Black Star's arrival. If one looked up from the surface of Planet Golden Gate, they would be able to see another ring somehow materializing around the Black Star Army's headquarters. The headquarters seemed to have a ring of stars that consisted of spaceships shining like bright mist.

"Yet another batch of new recruits is coming in." Within one of the metal strongholds in the headquarters, the drill sergeant, Brock, who was supervising the training of the reserve members looked out at the spectacular sight outside the porthole and could not help thinking back.

Brock had joined the Black Star Army more than a decade ago. He had witnessed the history of the Black Star Army, how it had grown from an ordinary mercenary group into the behemoth that was allied with a Universal Civilization.

With DarkStar having long been annihilated, the problem with discrimination in Godora was also beginning to settle down. The mixed Godorans were gradually returning to the embrace of the Godoran Civilization. With no goal to fight for, Brock thus buried his past and decided to conceal his identity as a DarkStar spy, completely devoting himself to the Black Star Army.

Brock, however, was unaware that Han Xiao had known of his identity since the beginning. However, with DarkStar having vanished, there was no need to settle debts with this 'obedient' spy, so he had left him to his work.

While working in the Black Star Army was tough, after abandoning his identity as a DarkStar member, Brock's attitude became more relaxed. He began to fall in love with the process of grooming batch after batch of warriors and soldiers. Under the care of Han Xiao, he had served for a decade as a drill sergeant and had long become accustomed to his role.

He could be considered a veteran in the Army and was also the top person in the Godoran faction within the army. Due to the popularity of the Black Star Army in Godora, many of the Godorans chose to work in the army and formed a Godoran faction, which was just one of the many factions in the army. With the current size of the Black Star Army, there were naturally many smaller factions within.

Just as he raised his head to observe the spaceships hovering in the air, there were also three passengers in a ship staring intently at the headquarters of the Black Star Army within the huge group of spaceships outside the headquarters.

This was a small, standard spaceship commonly found in Galaxy, completely unassuming.

"Can we really blend in with them? The Black Star Army personnel won't be so negligent, right?"

A man with thick eyebrows and big eyes had a hesitant tone as he spoke. He was a humanoid species, with smooth and bright silver skin, wearing a black cloak. Inside the black cloak, his exposed skin could be seen, covered in complicated and delicate magic lines.

"Other than that, there's no other way about it. If we want to see that person, we can only enter the Black Star Army headquarters," another person said. This person was a mixed race, with red, dragon-like scales on both his cheeks. He was a burly man about four meters tall, wearing a simple metal vest that exposed the knotted muscles on his arms.

"Relax, even if we really get exposed, we can masquerade as people trying our luck to join the Black Star Army. They'll at most chase us away. There won't be any danger."

The last person leaned against the wall as he spoke. He wore a tight combat suit, with two pairs of arms extending from his shoulders. One of his upper arms was placed behind his head like a pillow, while the other played around with a silver alloy dagger. The lower arms were placed akimbo on his waist, giving him a lackadaisical air.

These three were not new members of the Black Star Army like the others. They had different objectives, and they seemed to be led by the silver-skinned guy who had spoken first.

At this moment, in the starry sky outside the porthole shone a sudden stream of light approaching them and stopping over Planet Golden Gate. It was the Black Star Army that had returned to the headquarters.

"Wow, so many new members." Seeing the ring of spaceships, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"This is only the first batch of recruits. They're all waiting here for you, Master, hum..."

In Han Xiao's neural connected quantum network, Phillip started to bubble. His small body was lying at the extremes of Han Xiao's field of vision, with only his head popping out in his vision.

"Humph, I suggest sending a mechanical army to test the actual combat capabilities of these new members. Unqualified people will not be eligible to join the troops of my master!"

On the other side, the usually quiet and solemn Artificial intelligence Sparta also revealed his body. He was wrapped in heavy armor, and his face could not be clearly seen. Only a single cold looking eye was revealed, and his voice was husky and powerful.

With Han Xiao's [Virtual Technology] skill tree having been completed, he had studied the data structure of Risda and given his Artificial intelligence the ability to think for themselves, as well as unique personalities. This would be used to improve his computing power, as his brain would be connected to them through the quantum network at any time. This would allow him to supervise the dynamics of the Artificial intelligence without the fear of accidents happening. It was similar to taking care of a pet, just that it did not require someone to clean up their sh*t after them, and the AIs would not flare up, even helping in his daily life.

Would there be a better pet than the one stated above‽

Within the quantum network, Han Xiao's thoughts turned into a stream of data, flowing into Phillip's eyes. He instructed, "You can open the hangar of the headquarters now. When I dock, let all these new members come and meet me."

"Roger, hum..."

The hangar for the headquarters opened, and the Black Star Army fleet slowly descended, sliding into the empty hangars. As for the new members who had waited for many days, they also received the notice and started to descend.

The huge spaceship ring around the headquarters split into a few dozen streams, pouring into the various hangars. Numerous mechanical assistants were activated to receive all the new members.

The majority of the new members would be directed to the spacious lobby of the headquarters. When everyone had gathered, they would meet up with Han Xiao together. As for the new members in the Calamity Grade, they would receive special treatment and would proceed to the conference room in advance to meet with Han Xiao and his officers personally.

Leading his officers, Han Xiao entered the conference room. Within were more than ten people, and their gazes all shot toward him the moment he entered. All of them stood up immediately.

"Your Excellency Black Star!"

"Army Commander!"

They all saluted, excitement filling their faces. They were the first batch of Calamity Grades to be admitted, coming from different Star Systems. This was the first time they had personally laid eyes on their new Beyond Grade A leader, which made them extremely emotional.

In the eyes of the ordinary, reaching the Calamity Grade was already something unbelievable, but when faced with a Beyond Grade A, the majority of the Calamity Grades had the same feeling as when an ordinary person faced them. Furthermore, there was also another layer of yearning and longing.

Han Xiao smiled. "Hello, everyone."

After becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, not only had he advanced in strength, his horizons had also widened. In the past, if there were over twenty Calamity Grades who wished to join his Army, he would have been smiling from ear to ear, but right now, he was actually very calm. He could at least endure till there was no one around before he burst into laughter.

While the fame of a Beyond Grade A was appealing, a Calamity Grade could also be considered a high-end combat power. Many of the Calamity Grades were unwilling to join under other forces. Even though he was a Beyond Grade A, Han Xiao would never look down on Calamity Grades. Recruiting more than a dozen high-end combat personnel this time was the highest record ever for the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao chatted with the dozen or so Calamity Grades, motivating them. These recruits were the top combat force and would be his officers in the future.

Because the size of the army was too huge, Han Xiao did not have the time to check the attributes of every single new member. Thus, he only focused on the stronger newcomers, which were precisely these Calamity Grades.

After quietly looking through the interface properties of everyone, he secretly nodded.

While none of them have any Molding Talents, the strongest has reached the level of A+ and can be considered a mini-boss.

Turning back to look at Hila, Han Xiao said, "The Black Star Guards will serve as my elite unit, with the Calamity Grade as the threshold for entry. Hadavy is also a member of the Black Star Guards, and this is my Guards Captain, Hila. Because the Guards were only established recently, it needs to be expanded. The quota is known by Hila, and she as well as the other Black Star Guards will test your abilities and pick a few of you to enter the Black Star Guards."

The eyes of the Calamity Grades lit up. The Black Star Guards were obviously the bodyguards of Black Star and would follow him around. The temptation of this position was not little at all, and compared to the benefits they would obtain as ordinary officers, they looked forward more to learning from the experience of a Beyond Grade A, allowing themselves to be stronger. After all, earning money at their level was pretty easy, and the attraction of material enjoyment was quite limited. What they pursued was more of a promotion in realms.

The Black Star Guards took the ten or so Calamity Grades away, and Han Xiao led the rest of his officers to welcome the new members. However, Phillip suddenly started emitting bubbles again.

"Master, hum... I discovered a spaceship with no verification. There are three people on board the spaceship who do not have an invitation. They're not new members joining our army, nor is their data present in the database. Their identities are unknown, and they are situated in Hanger No.6. Do you want to look through their information?"

"Oh, they might be here to fish in murky waters and try to be accepted into the army. You can just chase them..." Before Han Xiao could finish, the image of the trio was transferred to his mind, and he suddenly paused, his eyes growing wider.

Seeing that Han Xiao did not reply, Phillip tilted his tiny head to the side, prompting him. "Master?"

"Hu..." Han Xiao let out a long breath, his eyes flashing as he changed his order. "Don't stop them. Let them enter and pretend you are unaware of their identities. Just activate the surveillance within the army and constantly lock onto their positions."

"Roger that, hum..."

After disconnecting from the quantum network, Han Xiao stroked his chin, his eyes narrowed.

"To think that these three thugs dared to show up in my territory at this moment... Hmm, it seems that the butterfly effect I'm causing is spreading. There's an eighty percent chance that they're here for her..."

The spaceship entered and stopped at the dock. The trio—Silverskin, Dragonscale, and the four-handed man—set foot on the crowded dock, looking around.

There were none of the anticipated alarms, no mechanical assistants waiting to confirm their identities, and no one coming over to escort them.

They had entered so easily!

"The Black Star Army's security measures are too lousy, as good as nonexistent." The four-handed man pouted. "Even my mother star that is about to be destroyed by the crazy scientists is safer."

Silverskin was a little uneasy, softly saying, "We'll blend in first before looking for a chance to split off and act. Don't get caught."

"Ok." Dragonscale nodded.

Silverskin then squeezed his fingers as he murmured, "Hopefully, we can find the rumored Rossellin here..."

Chapter 783: Celebrities of the Future

All the new non-Calamity Grade members gathered in the main hall of the headquarters. It was filled with people.

The roof of the hall suddenly opened. The army officers descended from the sky and landed on the most conspicuous stage in the hall. They stood in a row and looked around at the millions of new members below.

"That's the army's Chief Administrative Official, Sylvia. Beside her is the Fleet Chief Commander, Herlous. They're both seniors under Black Star's command."

"That's the army's Vice-Captain Lagi. They say he's the strongest person under Black Star's command."

"Hadavy became one of Black Star's guards some time ago. He should be the strongest."

"Why aren't the Black Star Guards here?"

In the many years of fighting the secret war, the various officers of the Black Star had earned a name for themselves. The new members in the hall all recognized these officers.

This time, a flash of light appeared on the stage. Han Xiao walked out of the Void Dimension and nodded at the millions of new members.

The people under the stage focused. Facing a Beyond Grade A, most people were both excited and nervous.

"Welcome to the Black Star Army..."

Han Xiao scanned through the hall filled with people and started his speech while his thoughts drifted to the three unwelcome guests. While presenting his welcome speech, he watched the images on the surveillance cameras and focused on the whereabouts of those three people at the same time.

They had already found Rossellin.

...

Rossellin was special among the army officers. She was the Cultural Instructor. Due to her unique ability, she rarely appeared in public and usually gave people lessons in the army training camp.

After returning with the fleet, she did not follow Han Xiao to show herself in front of the new members but directly returned to her room in the training camp in the headquarters. However, on her way, she was stopped by three people.

"What do you want?" Rossellin slightly raised her brow.

Rossellin sized up the silver-skinned man, the man covered in dragon scales, and the four-armed man.

"Let me introduce myself. My name is Edmond, and these two are my friends. The buff one is Kayde, and the four-armed one is Haywal," The silver-skinned Edmond said.

The man covered in dragon scales, Kayde, nodded as a greeting. The four-armed Haywal waved his hands.

Rossellin narrowed her eyes and suddenly said, "You're not members of the army, are you?"

"Yes, but we mean no harm. We just hope to have a talk with you." Edmond lowered his voice. "You'll definitely be interested."

After a period of silence, when Edmond felt a little anxious, Rossellin slowly nodded. "Okay, follow me."

Then, she turned around and led the way. Delighted, Edmond took his two friends and followed behind.

When they came to a corner with no one around, Rossellin stopped and turned around.

"Tell me, what do you want to talk to me about?"

"The three of us are from the Sea of Star Spirits. We're planning to build a career, and we hope to invite you to join us." Edmond got straight to the point.

"Interesting. You came to the Black Star Army's headquarters and tried to recruit a Beyond Grade A's officer. You have some guts," Rossellin mocked. "Tell me about your so-called career. Don't disappoint me."

Edmond licked his lips, lowered his voice, and said, "We want to overthrow the three Universal Civilizations."

Rossellin's smile stiffened.

"...Allow me to confirm something." Rossellin's lips twitched. "You're not mental, are you?"

"I know this sounds unbelievable, but this is indeed my aspiration." Edmond's tone started to get a little elevated. "The three Universal Civilizations have ruled the galaxy for way too long. In order to maintain their ruling position, they toy with the rules that they set under the name of maintaining order, eliminating the future of countless races."

Rossellin frowned. "But it's also thanks to those rules made by the three Universal Civilizations that the universe is as peaceful as it is today. If they disappear, countless civilizations will start a war to become the ruler that will spread across the entire universe. Quintillions of lives will be lost in the flames of war, only for new rulers similar to the three Universal Civilizations to be born in the end. What's even worse is that maybe all civilizations will be destroyed. Don't you know that?"

"I do. This is the price for overthrowing the current rules, but..." Edmond took a deep breath. "That's what a revolution is."

"A revolution is to create a better era, but the era now is peaceful—lives are decent. Since people can still live well, why do you want to revolutionize? If... and I mean if, you really overthrow the three civilizations, can you promise the future will be better than now?"

"No one can promise what will happen in the future. Whether a revolution will create a better era or not, I don't know. But I'm not willing to deliberately ignore the problems of today because I can't let go of the peace and watch the wrong things continue to exist without doing anything." Edmond shook his head. "In this era, resources are rich—more than enough to feed everyone even if they choose to do nothing in life, have no motivation, act like walking bags of meat... The basic resources are no longer our reason to start a revolution."

Rossellin narrowed his eyes. "Then what do you fight for? For those races you said are oppressed? Or for your own ambition?"

Edmond shook his head. "Neither... revolution itself is my aspiration."

Rossellin sized up Edmond carefully again. He looked ordinary, but his guts were anything but ordinary. With the three Universal Civilizations' position, this was equivalent to going against the gods!

"If the revolution succeeds, what will you do? Take over the three civilizations?"

"I don't know," Edmond answered truthfully.

"... Why me?"

"In order to overthrow the authority that the three civilizations have in the hearts of countless people, we need your ability. Furthermore, we heard about what you did," Edmond said softly. "You were once a reformer with great aspirations, too, weren't you?"

Rossellin closed her eyes and did not speak.

After a long silence, she reopened her eyes and slowly asked, "How many of you are there now?"

"Just the three of us."

"You haven't even built your organization, and you already want to recruit me‽"

Rossellin's tone was filled with disbelief.

Edmond bowed and said with a sincere tone, "Yes, but my sincerity is true in every sense. I hope to gather those with the same aspirations and beliefs and create something together. Rossellin, I hope you can consider my request."

This time, it was as if Rossellin saw Black Star's shadow on Edmond.

Both were big swindlers!

"I will consider it. Give me your communicator number."

After a lot of hesitation, Rossellin did not make a decision instantly.

After exchanging communicator numbers, Edmond's face was filled with joy. This time, Kayde, who never interrupted, suddenly spoke.

"Since the matter is settled, we should quickly leave the Black Star Army headquarters and not let ourselves get discovered."

Edmond nodded continuously. He bade farewell to Rossellin and hastily left with the other two.

Rossellin opened her mouth, but in the end, still did not tell the three of them. They thought that they had snuck in here, but Black Star Army's surveillance system had undoubtedly discovered the three of them long ago. In the headquarters, nothing could be hidden from Black Star.

She just did not know why no one had gone to catch these three all along.

This was why Rossellin had been curious since the start—did Black Star purposely let the three of them in?

Beep!

At this time, Rossellin's communicator suddenly rang, and Phillip's voice sounded.

"Master wants to see you, hum..."

...

When Edmond and the other two headed to the port, the inspection in the hall had ended as well. All the paths were filled with people, and it became boisterous.

The three of them were relieved. With the crowd as a disguise, they felt that the chance of them being discovered was much lower.

When they passed by the hall, Han Xiao had yet to leave. The three of them gave him a quick glance and immediately looked away, not daring to attract Han Xiao's attention. They then left along with the crowd.

They came to the dock, retrieved their spaceship, and left the Black Star Army. Only then did Edmond finally relax.

"This doesn't feel right," Kayde suddenly said with a frown. "Our infiltration was too easy."

Even Haywal who complained at the start felt that it was strange. "The Black Star Army's headquarters' defenses can't possibly be this easy to penetrate, can they? If we were killers, we might have already killed a few officers."

The three of them could not figure it out at all. There was no way they would ever think that Han Xiao had deliberately let them in.

From their perspective, they were just a few ordinary people. Why would a Beyond Grade A recognize them?

To prevent any pursuers, Edmond hastily sped up and entered hyperdrive. The spaceship turned into a stream of light and disappeared.

At the same time, in the corridor toward the officer conference room, Han Xiao smiled.

In the vision of the Observer's Mark, Edmond's movements were clearly shown.

The reason he had remained in the hall was to secretly throw an Observer's Mark on Edmond as it was somewhere they had to pass.

I didn't expect to see the leaders of the Silver Revolutionary Army here...

Those three were the founders of the Silver Revolutionary Army, the people that would be the main focus of an entire version in the future!

These future celebrities had yet to reach their potential; they were still at the beginning of their career and had not officially created the Silver Revolutionary Army.

Edmond was a restless revolutionary, a challenger of the authority of the three Universal Civilizations. The him now might have no idea how much he would achieve in his career.

Taking Rossellin in was one of Han Xiao's bets, but to his surprise, this really turned out to attract the Silver Revolutionary Army, the core members even.

Han Xiao decided to watch things unfold and not eliminate Edmond and the others. He had no conflict of interests with the Silver Revolutionary Army. Plus, they might even become one of his chess pieces.

Edmond and his friends were very weak; killing them was a piece of cake for Han Xiao. However, eliminating the Silver Revolutionary Army storyline in advance would not benefit him in any way. If he went to tell the Crimson Dynasty that he had killed a group of people that would one day shake their authority, the Crimson Dynasty's response would just be one word—"Okay."

Hence, Han Xiao did not chase Edmond away. He planned to establish a positive relationship with the future Silver Revolutionary Army. Plus, he had planted an Observer's Mark on Edmond unnoticed, so he had already obtained the upper hand.

When he walked into the conference room, Rossellin was the only one inside. She sat on a chair and looked at Han Xiao.

"I knew it. You let these three in." Rossellin shook her head.

Han Xiao sat down, tapped the table with his fingers, and asked, "What do you think about them?"

"In terms of what?"

"What do you think about their proposal?"

Rossellin smiled and said, "Are you asking if I'm going to betray the army?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "I won't call it a betrayal. You're Reynold's older sister. You're just staying in the army to help. I didn't say I was going to keep you here all your life. I knew you're a restless person long ago."

Hearing what Han Xiao said, Rossellin truthfully said, "The reason I'm staying in the army is primarily the generous salary and reward. No matter what I want to do, I will need the funds. Secondly, my history. You said that as long as I work for you, you will clean up my history. Thirdly... maybe a little bit because I want to repay you for saving me, ahem, but just a little bit."

"I know, don't have to emphasize it." Han Xiao laughed. He paused and asked, "So, what are your thoughts?"

As he had saved Rossellin in advance, he did not know if she would still join the Silver Revolutionary Army like she did in the previous life.

"Humph, there are so few of them, and there's no benefit at all. They really are ignorant for even thinking they could take me away to join their revolution. I'm not interested in those three simple-minded men." Rossellin despised them a little. "However, to be honest, overthrowing the three Universal Civilizations... seems very interesting."

So, you are interested... Han Xiao was speechless.

It was indeed true that one's personality defined one's fate. For a restless reformer like Rossellin, even if she did appreciate what he had done for her, she would still end up walking down the same path.

"If you've made up your mind, come to find me anytime. I will allow you to leave." Han Xiao stood up.

Although Rossellin was very useful, he was not planning to force her to stay. Rossellin would most likely be a pillar of the Silver Revolutionary Army in the future. Having a good relationship with her was equivalent to planting his chess pieces in the Silver Revolutionary Army in advance. Furthermore, through Rossellin, he could let Edmond and his friends know that they had been able to sneak in today because he had turned a blind eye. This way, he would establish a positive relationship with them.

Besides, letting Rossellin go might lead to a chance to trigger missions from Reynold in the future.

The Great Mechanic Han still had not given up hope on Perfect Mechanical Sense.

The Silver Revolutionary Army started to grow quietly in the various Star Fields except for the Central Galaxy, only to erupt when their forces were powerful enough. They had yet to even form, so that would be very far in the future.

It has only been about half a year since the start of Version 3.0, Crimson Tide, and the secret war main storyline is already coming to an end. The development of the Flickering World is around the corner. It's the perfect chance to let those players explore it. The seed of the Silver Revolutionary Army has appeared as well. As the storyline of this version develops, the strength of the players will become more and more apparent.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The plan to expand the leek fields had to be brought forward. He could not be limited by the Shattered Star Ring.

Luckily, to respond to the Crimson Dynasty's summon, he would have to visit the Central Galaxy later. This would be an opportunity.

...

At the same time, in the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Building on the Klent Mother Planet, a secret meeting had already lasted a very long time.

Bang!

Klent Diplomatic Ambassador slammed the table and stood up in a rage.

"Zoel! You're crossing the line! Why is the Crimson Dynasty demanding that we give up submitting the proposal to re-classify the ownership of the Star Cluster? You're telling us to give up everything we've done in the secret war for the past decade! Whose side are you on!"

Zoel wiped off the saliva that had splashed on his face and narrowed his eyes.

"I'm always on the Crimson Dynasty's side."

Chapter 784: Voluntary Retreat!

The Klent Diplomatic Ambassador glared at Zoel and had no words.

"I've already told you the details," Zoel said slowly. "The dynasty has decided not to take a stand regarding this issue. You can insist on submitting the proposal, but the chance of it being approved is very low. The Arcane Church will oppose your request. On behalf of the dynasty, I'm just suggesting that you guys give up on this proposal, not interfering with your choice. If you insist, we won't stop you."

"I don't understand!" the Klent Diplomatic Ambassador said furiously. "Why is the dynasty helping Purple Crystal‽"

"The dynasty's upper echelons have their considerations."

"Is it because of the Evolution Cube‽ Is that why you people suddenly changed your stand‽"

"Let me emphasize again. The dynasty's upper echelons have their considerations," Zoel said with a heavier tone. "Plus, you're wrong. The dynasty only upholds its own position, and this rule has never changed. The dynasty has never shown any support for your plan all along."

The Klent Diplomatic Ambassador clenched his teeth. They did not think much when the Tyrant's duel went south, but they had never expected it to be their turn so soon.

Klent had invested a ton of resources into the secret war. Initially, the Crimson Dynasty approved of this with silence, but now that the Crimson Dynasty had suddenly opposed it, this meant that Klent's investments for the last decade might all go down the drain!

Of course, they were displeased with this.

No matter how the Klent Diplomatic Ambassador thought about it, he felt that this was because of the Black Star Army. Although Zoel did not explain why the Crimson Dynasty had decided to do this, it was painfully clear that this was certainly because of Black Star!

This time, Zoel changed the topic and said, "The development of the Flickering World is about to start. We hope you can dispatch your troops and make preparations as soon as possible. The exploration tasks will be rather complicated and difficult."

The Klent Diplomatic Ambassador understood that this was most likely the Crimson Dynasty's indirect compensation for them—allowing them to obtain more profit in the Flickering World.

After some pondering, he finally said, "Since this is what the dynasty has decided on, we will reconsider the proposal. As for the exploring of the Flickering World, we will definitely send our very best."

Zoel smiled faintly.

After they were done with the business, they chatted for a while before the Klent Diplomatic Ambassador hastily left.

The Klent Diplomatic Ambassador walked out of the Crimson Dynasty Diplomatic Building, boarded a carrier, turned on his communicator, and contacted his superiors to report what had happened. This stirred up intense arguments.

In the end, the upper echelons came to a conclusion—there was nothing they could do to the Crimson Dynasty. No matter how displeased they were, they could only swallow it. Every Klent upper echelon felt wronged. As a civilization ruled by a Universal Civilization, they had no choice but to obey.

The person they hated most was their 'new ally', Black Star.

It could be said that Black Star had single-handedly shattered that decade-long plan!

More than seven years ago, Han Xiao had already vastly expanded his army using his fame as a Beyond Grade A Seed, which had built the fundamentals for him for the years to come. Since he had experience, this time, he used his influence as a Beyond Grade A to its fullest. Furthermore, with the Crimson Dynasty and the Purple Crystal Civilization backing him, most of his opposing forces did not dare make any moves. The expansion of the army met almost no obstacles at all and went extremely smoothly.

Countless free Supers in the Shattered Star Ring responded to the Black Star Army's recruitment, and new members joined the army batch by batch. In just a short time, the size of the Black Star Army skyrocketed. Now there were more than three hundred million members of the Black Star Army across the various Star Systems in the Colton Star Cluster.

There were tens of millions of Grade Bs and more than forty Grade A Supers. Just in terms of high-level combatants, the Black Star Army had already surpassed most of the Star System Civilizations.

With Han Xiao's influence as a Beyond Grade A, the Black Star Army expanded extremely quickly. With the investments from the many financial groups and the support from the Purple Crystal Civilization, Han Xiao had more than enough funds to support this quick expansion.

He threw an outrageous amount of money into the Logistics Department to build more battleships as well as new satellite bases so that he could have more divisions within the Colton Star Cluster.

While the Black Star Army was expanding at an astonishing speed, the galactic residents of the Shattered Star Ring were all paying attention to the aftermath of the duel. What they were interested in was what impact the Black Star Army becoming a Crimson Dynasty ally would have on the secret war.

The secret war had recently entered a ceasefire. After the duel, be it the Bloodshed Land or Section Zero, neither started any conflict. It was oddly quiet.

Countless galactic residents were paying attention to the secret war and saw it as a sign. According to the current situation, the next turn of events in the secret war would indirectly represent the result of the battle.

At this crucial time when everyone was expecting something to happen, a piece of news exploded from the secret war that caused a sensation in the entire Star Field!

Without any battle, without any announcement, out of nowhere, the Bloodshed Land gave up all their strongholds in West Wind, Kaya, Chaida, and the border Star Systems, voluntarily retreating out of the Colton Star Cluster!

When the information spread, all the people that were paying attention to the secret war were shocked.

The Bloodshed Land represented Klent's stand. Retreating voluntarily meant that Klent had given up their invasion plan, given up the results of the past decade... This meant that Purple Crystal had won this war effortlessly.

The secret war, which had lasted an entire decade, had ended just like that‽

No one knew what agreement the two sides had made in secret. In the eyes of an outsider, the Black Star Army becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally definitely had something to do with this.

The most likely situation was that through becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally, the Black Star Army had somehow forced Klent to give up on the invasion, helping Purple Crystal win the secret war!

At its core, the merit all went to Black Star himself!

Advancing into Beyond Grade A, snatching the Evolution Cube away, forcing the Tyrant to retreat, becoming the Crimson Dynasty's ally... this chain of events had flipped the entire situation!

This meant that Black Star had ended the secret war single-handedly!

This was the truth in the eyes of the people of the Star Field!

Before the aftermath of the grand duel even dissipated, the ending of the secret war stirred up a storm in the Shattered Star Ring once again!

Grade S Faction Mission [Secret War: Section Zero] completed.

Mission rating: Unbelievable

You have received 6,000,000,000 Experience, Random Reward * 5, +40,000 Purple Crystal Contribution Points, and +1 Legendary Point.

Star Cluster Legendary Point (Colton Star Cluster): Star of the Secret War—You have contributed tremendously to the secret war. The people of the Purple Crystal Star Cluster will remember you for what you have done.

You have received 2 Political Assets.

Political Asset (2): Purple Crystal Civilization

You are loved and admired by the people of the Purple Crystal Civilization. When trading with Purple Crystal Civilization citizens, you can buy at lower prices and sell at higher prices.

The Purple Crystal Civilization is willing to listen to your requests. You can make suggestions to the Purple Crystal Civilization's government directly. According to the rationality of the request, there's a slight chance that the Purple Crystal Civilization will fulfill your request.

This is a symbol of political influence. Your achievements are praised in the universe. When interacting with certain organizations or characters, +45% Favorability gain rate.

You have valuable experiences. +45% Experience gained from all sources.

Remarks: Your relationship with the Purple Crystal Civilization has to be at [Reverence] for the above effects to take place.

Dungeon Creation: [Secret War]

"Hmm? The secret war main storyline mission finally ended?"

On the closest Fixed Star from Planet Golden Gate, the burning Fixed Star energy surrounded a man.

In the free time he had during the army's expansion, Han Xiao had been training [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation]. He was just taking a bath in the Fixed Star. Only when the chain of notifications popped up from the interface did he finally discover that the secret war had ended.

His mind connected to the quantum network and found the news about the Bloodshed Land retreating in an instant. Smiling, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

"Looks like Zoel carried out the terms and convinced Klent. It's much quicker than I expected..."

Klent was rather decisive in directly letting the Bloodshed Land retreat, but Han Xiao knew that Klent was certainly resentful. They would not dare be displeased with the Crimson Dynasty, so their hatred would most likely be directed toward him. This was unavoidable.

To heal Klent's tiny little heart, the Crimson Dynasty would definitely have made a deal with them secretly, which he would have no way of knowing the details of.

Han Xiao did not care about offending Klent. Despite them being allies on paper, the hatred between them would not just disappear after they had fought for an entire decade. Klent hated him, and he did not forget about Klent's never-ending assassinations in the past decade.

Scanning through the mission reward, Han Xiao was delighted.

A Grade S Mission's rewards were impressive. This was worth his decade of hard work!

Even to a leek farmer like him, six billion Experience was still rather considerable. The five Random Rewards were also more than the three rewarded by [Bloodline] in the past.

One Star Cluster Legendary Point was not bad either. Including the three Star Field Legendary Points that he had obtained through his battle with the Tyrant, his Experience Reward Quota for the players had almost doubled!

The two Political Assets were the most valuable reward. Political Assets were extremely rare and only appeared in outrageously difficult missions. His Experience gain increased by forty-five percent again. With this and the thirty percent given by the Godora Political Asset, he basically had a 1.75x Experience Card activated at all times!

After becoming a Beyond Grade A Super, the Experience needed to level up was on an entirely different level. With the bonuses provided by Political Assets, his efficiency in harvesting leeks would be tremendously increased. After the ten or so months' Experience penalty period was over, he should have a ton of Experience ready for him to level up.

The [Secret War] Dungeon was a sub-product of large main storyline missions, just like the [Six Nations and Germinal Organization] Dungeon. He could cut out some battle that he had experienced during the decade-long secret war and create Dungeon Crystals.

Han Xiao immediately thought of another use for this.

"The players only joined the secret war toward the end. The earlier part of the war was just a background introduction to them. Maybe I can show them what the Black Star Army experienced in the decade-long war through the dungeon. They can personally experience how the army rose and learn more about the army's history. This is beneficial to strengthening the players' sense of belonging to the faction..."

After pondering for a while, Han Xiao felt that this could work and had many thoughts along with it.

"I can even give them internal honorable titles within the army, just to those players that participated in the secret war, signifying that they witnessed the rise of the army and let the new members know they're senior members. They can even enjoy a permanent discount in the army in the future. This will be good in keeping the players here..."

Having thought of that, Han Xiao could not help but open the player forums.

He had obtained the secret war main storyline ten years in advance, so his rating being high was certain. Furthermore, winning the secret war increased the Mission Rating—not just for him but for all the Black Star Army players!

Han Xiao wanted to see how the players on the forums would react to this.

Chapter 785: Forums' Response and Themed Episode

As soon as he opened the player forums, two top posts marked 'hot' entered his sights—the new Galaxy Times episode and Bun-Hit-Dog's video.

Both of those mentioned him, and the Galaxy Times even used his name as the subtitle of this episode. The name of this episode was 'Galaxy Times: Legendary Leader—Black Star'!

"Yo, the Times made an episode about me." Han Xiao was delighted.

The Galaxy Times often introduced large events experienced by the players in the various Star Fields. Sometimes, they would have an episode focused entirely on some grand event or important person.

For example, when Version 3.0 started, the Galaxy Times dedicated an episode to analyze the different storylines the Crimson Tide brought to the players in the various Star Fields. The Shattered Star Ring secret war was just one of them.

If he remembered correctly, although the Galaxy Times had mentioned him many times, this was the first time they had used his name as the subtitle of an episode.

It made sense. He was a renowned character that had existed through many versions, and he was also the first person to advance into Beyond Grade A in the eyes of the players. He deserved to have an episode dedicated to him.

Han Xiao looked at Bun-Hit-Dog's video. Its title was 'Black Star Army Specials: Rising in the Star Field'.

These two videos were the most popular posts at the moment. Han Xiao did not open them immediately. He had a habit of browsing through the other ordinary posts first to see what the other players were talking about.

He looked down, and countless new posts appeared, almost all about the secret war main storyline mission. The other players' secret war main storyline mission had ended as well, which made a lot of players create posts out of surprise. Everyone was talking about this new topic.

"Damn, the main storyline mission ended? A notification suddenly popped out of the interface. I was not prepared for it at all!"

"I just saw the news. The Bloodshed Land retreated."

"The news said that Purple Crystal initially had very slim chances and that it was the captain that turned the tables this time single-handedly, making Klent give up on the invasion."

"Wow!"

"The Mission Rating is so high. Is it because we won the secret war?"

"Definitely. The Mission Rating details said that winning the war would increase the Mission Rating by an entire grade!"

"That's amazing!"

"Captain is the best!"

"I'm crying over here. I went to do the storyline of the Mercenary League. If I'd known about this, I would've joined the secret war too."

"Regret +1."

On the forums, most of the Black Star Army players were overjoyed. This was a Grade S main storyline mission. Increasing its rating an entire grade should have been extremely difficult, but this time, it basically fell right down from the sky.

Only the army players had this benefit. The players were over the moon and liked Han Xiao even more.

As everyone was getting excited, some people thought about Summer Night Flower again and brought his post encouraging the army players to betray the army up to the front page.

"@Summer Night Flower, come out!"

"@Summer Night Flower, how are you feeling? Surprised? Shocked? Overjoyed‽"

"Yo, why aren't you teaching us about the 'right way to play the secret war' now?"

"Didn't you say the Bloodshed Land would win? How did this happen?"

"Very few can understand the truth? Ha!"

Summer Night Flower's speculation had three key points. Today, the truth had proved all of them wrong.

He felt that the Black Star Army had no way up. Suddenly, the Black Star Army became the Crimson Dynasty's ally, and the faction leader, Black Star became a Beyond Grade A.

He felt that the Bloodshed Land would win the secret war. The Black Star Army won.

He said that the Black Star Army had too many members, and the privileges given to each member were limited, which was even more ridiculous. The current army players made a killing, while those 'traitors' that joined the Bloodshed Land were almost going mad from being chased by the army players.

The players kept mentioning Summer Night Flower. Summer Night Flower basically acted as if he was dead and did not appear at all, afraid of exploding from the mockery from the players.

After scanning through the posts for a while, Han Xiao returned to the top posts. He opened the new Galaxy Times episode and watched it.

The opening was still those never-changing male and female hosts, as well as the same old opening speech that even the audience had memorized.

"Hello players," the female host said, "this is Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand game information. Your gaming career is our top priority."

"We have only one topic to talk about in today's episode—the renowned character who's caused a sensation in Galaxy recently—Black Star!" the male host said.

The image changed. It was a screenshot from a certain player, and the background was the duel scene from not long ago.

The perspective of the screenshot was from the Black Star Army formation, which was behind Han Xiao. In the image, Han Xiao's back was facing the player, and before him were countless enemy battleships. As if he was facing countless enemies alone, it looked very cool.

Then, the episode sorted out Han Xiao's life story, introducing the rise of the Black Star Army and the large events experienced by the players.

In the Black Phantom era, he stirred up the Planet Aquamarine structure behind the curtains, starting a war single-handedly, getting his revenge, and eliminating the Germinal Organization.

In the Black Star Mercenary Group, he led the first group of professional players to battles in the universe, joined Floating Dragon, grew at an astonishing speed, and built the fundamentals of the future army...

In the Mutation Disaster era, for the promise he made, he led the Black Star Mercenary Group back to Planet Aquamarine, helping his mother planet fight against the disaster. He then guided the players into the galaxy, officially creating the Black Star Army, helping Godora eliminate the notorious DarkStar, becoming the rare example of an outsider receiving Godora's Golden Gal Badge.

In the secret war era, he expanded and made the Black Star Army grow in the ten years unknown to the players, became a Beyond Grade A, single-handedly turned the tables, and helped Purple Crystal to win the war. He then made the army an ally of a Universal Civilization, the Crimson Dynasty.

The episode narrated Han Xiao's life story from the players' perspective in a rather official tone, accompanied by some Black Star Army sub-storylines recorded in the Galaxy Chronicles. It even played some players' daily life experience in the army and added some interactive factors to the episode, showing how the players grew together with the army.

This episode ended with a conclusive remark.

"In just more than twenty years, Black Star left his mother planet and created an enormous and astonishing base in the Shattered Star Ring. From the once Black Phantom to the Black Star today, we witnessed his growth. He's the first character we have seen advance to become a Beyond Grade A.

"As a leader, he is undoubtedly legendary. His ambitions, abilities, and intelligence are extraordinary, and he's still active today. However, it's as if he always wore a mysterious mask. We never fully understood his beliefs and personality.

"No one knows how much the Black Star Army can achieve under his leadership, but what's certain is that... we're witnessing the birth of a legend."

The video ended there. The Galaxy Times used this episode to summarize what he had done. It was a rather official positive report.

Han Xiao felt that this was quite beneficial. To the old players from Version 1.0 and Version 2.0, he was an old friend, but to the new players in Version 3.0, there were still quite many people that had limited knowledge about him.

This Galaxy Times episode basically introduced him to more new players and brought him some fame.

"Not bad." Seeing that he was on TV again, Han Xiao was glad. He then opened Bun-Hit-Dog's video.

Compared to the Galaxy Times's official tone, Bun-Hit-Dog's video had a strong personal bias—an almost fawning tone.

At the start of the video, the image was pitch black, and a narrative sounded.

Han Xiao's brow suddenly twitched. Bun-Hit-Dog's narrative used the first-person perspective and spoke as if he was him.

The black image coated the deep voice with a layer of mystery.

"When I first stared at the night sky, it was filled with countless stars, bright and beautiful like diamonds. But at the edge of the sky, there were two overlapping stars. The front star blocked the starlight of the back star, making it a pitch-black star."

"At that moment, I thought that maybe, one day, I can also block the light of other stars... so that everyone only sees me."

Chapter 786: Everything Comes at the End of Fawning

"Tsss..." Han Xiao felt a sense of numbness on his scalp.

This guy was still remarkable at fawning, and he had learned new tricks. Han Xiao could guess what this video would be like just by watching the start.

As expected, Bun-Hit-Dog used self-narration at the start to create a mysterious atmosphere. Then, the image changed as he began to describe his history since Black Phantom era. Although the Galaxy Times episode was similar, Bun-Hit-Dog had a completely different style. He used first-person narration most of the time, using material from many older episodes to create a strong sense of storytelling.

The first-person narration made the video strongly immersive. Bun-Hit-Dog described Han Xiao's past using his perspective, creating a sense of personal experience, making the audience feel as if they were there.

Another specialty of the first-person narration was that through speaking his thoughts as 'Black Star', the audiences would have an even stronger impression of him.

Han Xiao always kept his distance when interacting with the players—he only expressed his surface thoughts. Therefore, the players could never understand his true thoughts. Bun-Hit-Dog wanted to use this episode to give 'realness' to the players' impression of Black Star.

His goal was to strengthen his position as the official and authentic Black Star Army video series creator, making this episode a must-watch for anyone that wanted to know about Black Star in the future. Through deduction, analysis, imagination, and the strongly immersive narration, he created a lively image for Black Star, making this character more real in the eyes of the players.

To the players, a character-focused episode like this was not a new concept. They loved giving NPCs more direct personalities. After all, they could portray the NPCs any way they wanted, and the NPCs would never see it.

The basis of Bun-Hit-Dog's analysis was what Han Xiao had done throughout the years. He deduced the reasons and motives for Black Star to do those things through his own perspective, beautifying Black Star's image. A larger portion of the personality was based on speculation and guessing, but the players loved this.

From the Black Phantom era until now, it was as if the players experienced Black Star's thoughts from the first-person perspective. Bun-Hit-Dog used Han Xiao's very few public speeches, giving him a ton of positive personality traits—such as ambitious, loving his mother planet, wise, loyal to his friends, a man of his word, decisive, daring but careful, and many more.

"Damn, that's way too much fawning."

Bun-Hit-Dog made him sound like he was the essence of all virtues. Even Han Xiao himself was embarrassed.

But it felt good indeed...

The image that Bun-Hit-Dog had built was far off from him, but the benefits were obvious. Only players themselves could create a clear image of him this way. With such loyal paparazzi, it was beneficial in increasing his personal charm to the players. There were clearly more comments on this video than on the Galaxy Times video. Tons of people were praising their captain.

In the later part of the video, Bun-Hit-Dog emphasized on the future of the Black Star Army and made a new speculation.

"The secret war is the main storyline in our eyes, but the way I see it, this might just be the surface. The true hidden storyline is the rise of the Black Star Army!

"The secret war is actually the background of Black Star's journey to becoming a Beyond Grade A Super and the rise of the army within the Star Field!"

This speculation gained approval from most of the army players. They remembered when the Black Star Army was far smaller than what it was today. When Version 3.0 started, the Black Star Army became completely different after the war and grew at an astounding speed.

Now that Black Star had ended the secret war, the rise of the Black Star Army felt more like the real main storyline that had snatched the attention from the secret war.

Seeing that most of the army players agreed with this, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

This was an opportunity to carry out his plan to make the history of the secret war into Dungeons.

The next day, the army players received a surprise gift.

For the players that had participated in the secret war, their army assistant in the communicator notified them that due to their involvement in the secret war, they had received the honorable title [Secret Warrior]. This was a title that was displayed on the army resume. It was a form of recognition from the army.

This was a title that was linked to the faction and had nothing to do with their interface. However, all players with this title would forever enjoy a ten percent discount when spending in the army!

The players that participated in the war were overjoyed, not just because of the discount but also because of the honor this title represented. There would only be one secret war, so this title would only be granted once, which meant that it was a faction title that would never be awarded again. This represented that they had witnessed the rise of the army; it was an honor that proved their position as seniors in the army.

At the same time, the faction store put up a ton of [Secret War] Dungeon Crystals that included many wars that spread across the ten years that the players did not experience.

The Dungeons had always been one of the players' favorite activities, and this had piqued their interest. These secret war Dungeons clearly belonged to the same series. Just like the [Six Nations and Germinal Organization], it was suitable for their current level. The players considered this as one of the specialties of a growing faction. After every main storyline, the Black Star Army would create a corresponding Dungeon series. The players were used to it.

Other than farming rewards in Dungeons, the secret war Dungeons could help the players learn about the Black Star Army's journey during the ten-year version update period. Personally experiencing it in the Dungeons was much more enjoyable than words recording the story.

Han Xiao had another motive for doing this. The secret war had ended, so the players had entered the free exploration stage. By giving out a ton of Dungeons at this time, it would give them new things to do to fill the time between the main storylines. When the Crimson Dynasty's order to develop the Flickering World arrived, he would take the Black Star Army to explore the Flickering World. Then, there would be more than enough things to do.

The Flickering World was the storyline of the next version. After the Crimson Dynasty finished their early-stage development, only then would they let the various organizations of the Star Fields take part in the exploration. To players, this would be like a 'World Server'. They would gather there, explore the unknown, and fight for resources. For him, however, he could take the army players into it in advance in Version 3.0.

Currently, all Han Xiao could do was wait and focus on expanding his army, grabbing as much profit from his sudden increase in influence. He kept the Evolution Cube exclusive for the time being, filling the various civilizations of the Colton Star Cluster with temptation.

With the ton of new members joining in, the matters within the army became complicated and more numerous. These matters were dealt with by Phillip and Sylvia, so he did not have to worry.

As half a month passed, most of the members that were willing to join were recruited. The expansion of the Black Star Army gradually started to slow down.

All the departments of the Bloodshed Land returned to the Seoul Star Cluster through stargates.

"Your Excellency Tyrant, what are you going to do?"

Hearing Jorde's careful and cautious question, Heber turned around.

After what had happened to the duel, he had been keeping a low profile, quietly watching the Black Star Army's expansion.

His 'Tyrant' name became Han Xiao's stepping stone, and his reputation had been reduced tremendously. This result was too far from his expectations.

However, Black Star had become his ally on paper, so it would be impossible to make him a target for building his reputation. The Crimson Dynasty had ordered them to make peace.

Heber stayed silent for a while before saying, "On my behalf, send an invitation to the various organizations of the Shattered Star Ring. I'm going to host a new party."

"Then, Black Star..." Jorde's heart beat quickly.

"Since he's the fifth Beyond Grade A of the Shattered Star Ring, of course, he deserves to be invited." Heber did not look at Jorde's expression and turned around.

Chapter 787: Showing One's Face for the Mission

"Heber invited me to his party?"

In the Black Star Army headquarters, Han Xiao glanced with interest at Malekith, who had a strained expression.

"That's right. His Excellency Tyrant mentioned it." Malekith's hands already had a layer of sweat on them.

It was only because both sides had given face to the Crimson Dynasty that they had become allies on paper. However, their relationship remained delicate, as the confrontation of both sides over the decade was hard to resolve. Now that Malekith had come with an invitation letter, this resulted in tension within the enemy camp.

Looking at Han Xiao, who was seated on his Mechanical Throne, Malekith had mixed feelings.

He had once tried to recruit Han Xiao, but after more than a decade, he was still the Chief Vanguard Official under the Tyrant, whereas Black Star had leapt toward the sky and become a Beyond Grade A, the same realm as the Tyrant.

Han Xiao tapped the armrest of his throne with his fingers, deep in thought.

He had once attended a party of the Tyrant's when he was following Ames. This was a party for the upper echelons of the Shattered Star Ring created by Heber, and all the major characters would participate in the show.

However, due to his defeat in the war, the Tyrant's reputation had taken a hit, and the Bloodshed Land as well as Klent had been silent for a while. Heber was eager to convene a new round of meetings as he had intended to stabilize his position.

Since the Tyrant wished to maintain his current influence, he would definitely take the chance to invite this new Beyond Grade A. Or, it could be because Heber was grudgingly agreeing to the request of the Crimson Dynasty, enduring and trying to be nice. Then again, this could also be a Hongmen Feast[1], but the chances of that were not high.

Because the secret war had not ended too long ago, there were still many conflicts of interest. Perhaps this meeting was also to clarify such matters.

As his thoughts spun, Han Xiao nodded.

"Return and tell the Tyrant that I'll attend."

Malekith breathed a sigh of relief and hurriedly bid farewell. Standing in front of Han Xiao gave him great psychological pressure.

The date of the meeting was set a month later. Because the secret war had just ended, Klent also had no choice but to endure their anger to negotiate with Purple Crystal to open the stargates at the borders of the Star Cluster, allowing both of their Star Clusters to be reconnected once more.

Based on the news that he had heard from those in the Purple Crystal Civilization, due to the intervention of the Crimson Dynasty, the negotiations between the two Star Cluster civilizations had gone pretty well, and they were expected to officially reopen the channels in the next ten days.

"In one month's time, well, by then, the expansion of the Black Star Army will be almost complete. The Crimson Dynasty will also send in their first batch of elites to accept the blessing from the Evolution Cube after this meeting, so the time is just right."

During the expansion, other than practicing Heber's Stellar Furnace Cultivation and reforming his organization, he did not have too many things to do. Thus, he had time to drop by the Tyrant's party to discuss things with the other organizations.

At this moment, Harmon suddenly pushed open the door, entering the room.

"Black Star, I'm leaving," Harmon loudly said.

"Oh?" Han Xiao recalled now. "That's right, you're returning to fight for the position of chief, right?"

Harmon was a main character template for the Luhan Beastman Tribe. The Luhan beastmen were an interstellar civilization, and their brutal tradition was governed by a tribal system where each tribe would control several planets.

Their system had a special origin to it. The Luhan beastmen were not indigenous people but nomads who had been exiled from other star systems a long time ago. They were scattered on different planets in the same area and had developed independently to form different tribes. All of them had the same origin tradition, but due to the long evolution, each tribe now had a different culture. When they finally united as one, they chose to retain each respective tribe's independence, resulting in this system.

Their method to select the chief was to randomly throw all their candidates to different planets in the universe, letting them hone themselves in the interstellar area, forming their own 'War League'.

When the stipulated deadline arrived, each candidate would take their own War League back to battle for contention of the chief's position. Since the campaign date for Harmon's Rockfall tribe was arriving, his mercenary career was about to come to an end, and he was ready to return to inherit his interstellar tribe.

In order to recruit Harmon more than a decade ago, Han Xiao had also joined his War League, and thus, this mission was still hanging on his interface.

"Black Star, you're part of my War League, and you need to come over to help me." Harmon snorted.

"The Luhan Beastman Civilization is located in the Seoul Star Cluster..." Han Xiao stroked his chin. "It's on the way to the Tyrant's Party. That's good. When the time comes, I'll bring you along."

This was an age-old tradition of the Luhan Beastman, and since he had promised it earlier on, Han Xiao was not prepared to go back on his words.

When Harmon left, Han Xiao took out his communicator and sent the news to the Dragon Emperor.

"Ames, the Tyrant has organized another meeting. Have you received the invite? Come over, we can set off together."

Very soon, he received the reply from Ames.

"Ok."

A few days later, Ames took a spaceship to the headquarters of the Black Star Army.

They were now allies, tied to the same thread, and already old friends. There was no need for formalities when meeting each other, and they were very easygoing.

Han Xiao only took his Black Star Guards along this time as he left the headquarters. Harmon and his War League were included within, as well as a few players who had accepted the mission of the War League. All of them travelled toward the battlefield together.

Since there were two Beyond Grade As inside this spaceship, alongside a group of high levelled Calamity Grades. The lineup could be described only as luxurious.

When they arrived at the border of the Star Cluster, because the stargates that had been closed due to the secret war had reopened, there were countless spaceships present, lining up to bypass the desolate universe belt. From afar, they resembled a winding dragon.

During wartime, the population from the two Star Clusters were unable to access each other's areas due to the traffic restriction. This had just been restored.

Upon entering the Seoul Star Cluster, Han Xiao adjusted the direction and shot toward the territory of the Luhan Beastmen tribes.

At the same time, on Luhan's Blood Planet...

This was a desolate planet almost totally covered in gray. It had a special place in the tradition of the Luhan Beastmen. Every tribe's candidate for Chief would use this planet as a battle platform.

Luhan's Blood Planet had a broken stone colosseum present. Each new tribal election would result in a new colosseum being built, leaving behind many wrecks and relics.

In a certain area of the planet, a fierce looking Luhan Beastman's spaceship rested on the surface, and surrounding it was a newly built colosseum, which would be the battlefield of the current chief candidates that the Rockfall tribe would use to compete for the inheritance.

The current chief of the Rockfall tribe, Faleta, was a burly Beastman. Based on the Beastman aesthetics, the number of hairs one had on their body indicated their age, and Faleta was almost completely covered in hair, showing his old age.

He was the father of Harmon, who was the second heir to the right of chief.

"Mogo, Getaw, Thaler... of the twenty-five chief candidates, only six have returned. The rest should have died in the Universe."

Looking over where the rest of the candidates were together in their respective War Leagues, he shook his head.

Most of the candidates were descendants of the superior tribes. The Luhan Beastmen were tribes that leaned toward the martial, and only the strong had the capability to rule over the tribe. After all the candidates were expelled from their home planet, they could not accept any kind of help from their tribes except the War League that they brought with them. This was to examine the candidate's comprehensive survivability, if they could live on and return. Such candidates would then be eligible to compete for the Chief position. This was a screening in itself.

The candidates could not actively contact anyone in the tribe as well, otherwise they would be disqualified and mocked. Candidates could only passively accept their tribal notifications, so Faleta was not sure of Harmon's current situation as well. He only knew that he had joined the Black Star Army and was still alive.

"Don't even know if his War League is strong enough..." Faleta secretly worried.

The fight for the position of chief was a battle of life and death. There was no tradition of the Luhan Beastmen showing mercy to their own enemies. The six candidates had returned after more than a decade, bringing with them strong War Leagues, of which Mogo and Getaw's were the strongest.

Mogo had joined the Bloodshed Land and brought many good warriors back with him, including many Grade B Supers. As for Getaw, he seemed to have become an important partner of some financial group, with a group of mercenaries behind him, but far less compared to Mogo's.

The two of them stared at each other across the distance, regarding each other as the greatest competitor this time round.

"Relax, Mogo. We're the elites from Bloodshed Land, and the enemy is only a bunch of ragtag warriors that have no fame. Their numbers are also fewer than ours. They are not our opponents." One of the Bloodshed Land officers patted Mogo on his shoulder. They had fought side by side for many years and had a deep relationship.

Mogo grinned, waving his war hammer twice as he replied, "Among all the candidates, I'm only afraid of Harmon. A pity he didn't come back, probably died in the universe. Other than him, the rest cannot defeat me. For someone like Getaw, I can settle him in a few blows."

On the other side, Getaw secretly whispered to one of the mercenaries, "Boss, I'll be counting on you later."

"Relax. With me around, you'll definitely get the position of chief." That man coldly laughed. He was called Riel, and his real identity was the leader of one of the rogue organizations around Seoul Star Cluster. He had a notorious reputation.

Getaw had entered this particular rogue organization. However, there was a rule in the chief selection that a candidate could not choose the path of an outlaw. Doing so would forfeit their right as a candidate since a chief could not be a wanted person in the universe. However, Getaw was not willing to give up the position of chief and thus tried to disguise the identity of his group as wandering mercenaries.

His reliance was on Riel, who was the only Grade A Super among all the candidates' War Leagues.

Riel had promised to help Getaw become chief, and in exchange, Getaw would provide them with supplies and logistics.

Although the Rockfall tribe was only one of the various tribes in the Luhan Beastman civilization, they had a few planets under their control, which meant that they were rich in resources.

The time passed while waiting, and dozens of other chiefs of the Luhan Beastman took their seats. All had come to witness the election of the Rockfall Tribe Chief. When the time was almost up, Faleta loudly spoke.

"The time is almost up. Mogo, Getaw... everyone is to take their War Leagues onto the battlefield and select a position. Prepare for battle!"

Everyone snaked onto the battlefield like fish swimming before taking up a certain area, confronting the others.

Faleta was anxious as he looked at the time. Candidates who returned after the official start of the war were considered late and directly disqualified, but Harmon had not yet arrived.

At this moment, Riel stepped out under the command of Getaw, releasing his Grade A energy fluctuations. His momentum rose into the sky.

"Calamity Grade‽"

The other candidates' faces changed dramatically.

Faleta was also shocked. As a star system civilization, the Luhan Beastman also had a dozen Calamity Grade Supers, of which three were in the stands. Getaw had brought a Calamity Grade into his own War League, and his strength immediately overwhelmed the other candidates.

At this time, two of the candidates on the battlefield suddenly threw down their weapons and raised their hands. This move represented surrender, and before they started fighting, the two men gave up their qualifications for the chieftain. While it might be shameful, they at least need not fight with a Calamity Grade and could keep the lives of themselves and their War Leagues.

There was a commotion in the stands as this happened.

"Are we really going to fight against a Calamity Grade?" Seeing the situation, the Bloodshed Land's officer also started thinking of retreat. He threw his originally eloquent words into the clouds and beyond.

"Fight!" Mogo's expression changed several times, but he gritted his teeth and held on tight to his war hammer.

"This... can I still give up now?" One of the Bloodshed Land warriors threw away his weapon, slowly retreating.

They were willing to help Mogo by being part of his War League due to their relationship, but they were not willing to throw their lives away.

Mogo's expression was also extremely ugly.

On the other side, Getaw raised his eyebrows and exhaled, a proud expression on his face as he arrogantly surveyed the audience. Standing beside Riel, he had the feeling of being a false sense of dominance.

Faleta, who was in the stands, was astounded and conflicted. At this moment, Getaw's father, who was at the side, opened his mouth.

"Chief, don't try to stall for time. Let us start now."

Getaw's father was also an upper echelon of the tribe, and while he was usually quite low key, he was different this time.

It's also good that Harmon is not back yet... Faleta sighed, and just as he was about to speak, a spaceship descended from the air, attracting the attention of the audience.

Whoosh.

The spacecraft landed in a corner of the battlefield. The hatch opened, and Harmon walked out with a group of people.

"Harmon is back!"

Many of the members from the Rockfall tribe felt their spirits get refreshed. Harmon was very prestigious in the tribe, and his bravery was recognized by the tribe members.

There was a flash of panic in Getaw's eyes. Having been pummeled by Harmon all his life, he had a deep shadow in his heart. However, the moment he remembered Riel beside him, he regained his confidence and stared at Harmon with gritted teeth.

"It's useless even if you come back. Whoever fights me today will die!"

Hearing the cheers from the stands, Riel knew that Harmon should be a competitor with some fame. He coldly snorted and revolved his strength, viciously pressuring Harmon and his group in an attempt to deter this group and force them to retreat.

At this moment, a voice sounded.

"Yo, little brother, you are a bit arrogant."

From Harmon's back, out walked several people. Han Xiao was at the very front, and he stared at Riel with a funny expression, as though watching a peacock challenge. His Black Star Guards that had expanded to nine people followed directly behind him.

Hila raised her brows and reversed the pressure in a flash.

The other party also has a Calamity Grade‽

Riel felt his chest tighten. He rubbed his eyes, and after taking a good look at Han Xiao and his entourage, he froze for a few seconds before suddenly turning pale and taking a few steps back, tumbling into Getaw's chest.

"Black Black Black... Black Star‽"

He uncontrollably screamed out the name, and everyone's gazes landed on Han Xiao and his group. Their expressions changed as well.

An uproar rose up in the stands. Everyone stared in shock, unable to believe their eyes.

That was... Black Star?

Beyond Grade A!

Harmon had actually invited a Beyond Grade A over‽

Faleta was dumbfounded.

Ding ding dang dang!

At this moment, all the competitors threw away their weapons.

Even Getaw quietly chose to forfeit, his heart extremely unwilling.

He had originally thought that being backed by a Calamity Grade would allow him to win the tribe chief's status. To think that Harmon would actually invite a Beyond Grade A over!

Who would be able to win against him‽

Mogo said in a tiny voice, "If only His Excellency Tyrant was willing to help me..."

"Are you dreaming?" The Bloodshed Land officer looked at him with an expression as though he was looking at an idiot. "What kind of status does the Tyrant have? Would he even notice you?"

Mogo pointed at Han Xiao in return, causing the Bloodshed Land officer to be rendered speechless.

Seeing this, the spectators of the various tribes in the stands went crazy. This is the only time in the history of the Luhan Beastman that all candidates had abstained, and it is also the first time that a Beyond Grade A has become part of the candidate's War League!

"Uh?" Harmon had a look of confusion. He scratched his head, still puzzled. "Why did all of them stop fighting? Is that it?"

Hearing this, everyone gritted their teeth, wishing nothing but to beat him to death.

A Beyond Grade A has arrived, and the gap in power is so huge. Why should we fight‽ Do you want all of us to die‽

"Just like that?" The interface showed the completion of the mission, and the players who followed almost fell over in disbelief.

They did not even do anything and only came here to see a cutscene. Their mission was completed like that?

We thought there would be a bitter battle!

The whole audience stared at him, causing Han Xiao to helplessly shake his head. With his current status, many low-level tasks could be completed directly by just showing his face.

It was good that he had gone to help Harmon get the chief's position.

[1] Hongmen Feast is a figure of speech used to refer to a trap or a situation that looks joyous but is in fact treacherous. Back

Chapter 788: Migration and Negotiation

Boom!

Two huge wooden barrels clashed together, and amber-colored liquid splashed out from the edge.

Harmon raised his head, gobbled it down, and exhaled with satisfaction.

Han Xiao shook his head with a smile and drank some too. The spicy alcohol flew down his throat. The ethanol was broken down as soon as it entered his body. To him, this was no different from water.

They were sitting in the Rockfall Tribe's flagship on the way back. Harmon had invited Han Xiao and the others to visit his home.

Usually, battles were unavoidable in the process of fighting to become the chief. However, because of Han Xiao's appearance, the other candidates had given up in despair. The chief position had gone to Harmon without question. Overjoyed, Harmon hosted a party on the ship.

They were old friends, so Han Xiao, of course, gave him face.

"Congratulations to the next Rockfall Chief." The other chiefs of the Luhan Beastman Civilization came to congratulate Harmon one after another, all looking at Han Xiao with envy.

They had no idea how Harmon had such a good relationship with a Beyond Grade A. The War League of the tribe's chief signified his network. With a Beyond Grade A friend, those chiefs knew very well that the Rockfall Tribe would rise after Harmon took on the position.

Watching Harmon be congratulated by his people, Han Xiao pondered. In his previous life, this storyline mission had been simple and rough—fighting from the start till the end. Harmon would then obtain the chief position through battle. Now, due to his interference, there was no battle. Therefore, he did not think any Dungeon Crystal would be created.

However, this did not matter to Han Xiao—he was not interested in such a little mission reward. He had gone to help because of his more than a decade long friendship with Harmon. Harmon had joined him when the Black Star Army was still the Black Star Mercenary Group. Han Xiao was never petty in helping an old friend such as Harmon, just like how he had treated Herlous.

On the table beside them, as Hadavy stuffed a huge chunk of Beastman-style burnt meat into his mouth, his eyes kept drifting toward Harmon. He moved his butt over to beside Hila and said softly, "Black Star has quite a good relationship with that Beastman. Is he always so caring about his officers?"

Hila was frowning and staring at the object that looked somewhat like an eyeball of a beast at the bottom of her cup. Hearing Hadavy's question, she glanced at him. Her eyes seemed to be saying, Get away from me.

Ignored, Hadavy moved his butt to beside Feidin and softly said, "Brother Feidin, is Black Star always this good to his subordinates?"

Feidin rolled his eyes.

"Go away, I'm Chen Xing."

Not far away, a group of players gathered and chatted while looking around at the many famous Black Star Guards.

"I heard Black Star is heading to the Bloodshed Land's headquarters this time. Could he be going there to make trouble?"

"No idea. But Black Star is going to meet the Tyrant again. There'll definitely be a good show."

After Harmon's War League mission was completed, Han Xiao gave these players new missions through the faction interface to make them follow him.

Although he initially did not plan to take players along to the Tyrant's party, leaving these people halfway in the Seoul Star Cluster was not suitable. He did not want to lose this stack of leeks. Therefore, he gave them a following mission with a rich reward so that they would not run around.

Bun-Hit-Dog was not there, but there were still people posting his whereabouts on the forums. Now all the players knew that Ames and he were going to the Bloodshed Land headquarters together. Some even said that they were on a honeymoon trip to fight with Heber—which was very Beyond Grade A like.

Ever since Han Xiao and Ames formed an alliance, there had always been discussions about them being a couple on the forums. The players felt they were perfect for each other, and there was definitely something going on between them. Someone even wrote an adult novel about Black Star rising in position to conquer this capable woman, and it was rather popular.

"Your Excellency Black Star..."

While drinking, Han Xiao heard someone call his name at the side. Han Xiao looked over. It was Faleta, who looked like he had something to say.

"What is it?" Han Xiao smiled. He was Harmon's elderly father, after all, so Han Xiao's tone was very friendly.

Faleta coughed and said, "Can we talk in private?"

Han Xiao nodded, put down the cup, and walked out of the party hall with Faleta. They came to an empty corridor on the flagship.

"What is it?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, I'm wondering... what's the exact relationship between you and Harmon?" Faleta asked cautiously.

"He joined under my command more than a decade ago and has given me a lot of help. When my mother planet faced a disaster, he was there to help me. I agreed to join his War League before I was even a Calamity Grade. Therefore, you don't have to worry. I don't have any ulterior motive." Han Xiao smiled. He knew very well of Faleta's worries.

After all, a Beyond Grade A personally helping someone fight for the chief position of a branch force within a Star System civilization looked suspicious in every way.

Faleta looked hesitant. Suddenly, he clenched his teeth and asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, I have a request... Does the Black Star Army accept race migration jobs?"

Han Xiao blinked, signaling for him to go on.

"The origin of us Luhan Beastmen is a stray civilization. Today, although we formed a Star System civilization, every tribe is still an individual nation. In terms of the development direction of the civilization, we have a lot of disagreements. I hope to migrate the Rockfall Tribe out of the Seoul Star Cluster."

"Why?" Han Xiao was curious."

"The Seoul Star Cluster is Klent Kingdom's territory. They have a very strong desire to control everyone. There are a few Star System civilizations in their Star System; us Luhan Beastmen are just one of them.

"The other few civilizations are more or less connected to Klent. They have been marginalizing us, squeezing our resources to force us to become Klent's vassal too. Our territory was three Star Zones wide more than a hundred years ago. Now, we only have one and a half. The Luhan Beastmen are brave and capable in combat. The faction of Supers in our people is very high. Klent has always had an interest in us.

"Our Rockfall Tribe hopes to maintain independence, and we are unwilling to become a vassal, but the majority of the tribes want to compromise with Klent. Our people who prefer independence are the minority, and we are all looking for a way out."

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and pondered. This was common in the universe. When a civilization had more than one government, there would always be disagreements when it came to the overall future direction of the entire race.

Such a political structure was not suitable for Star System civilizations. In Galaxy, where there were organizations everywhere, the decision of a civilization had to be made with the entire race in mind. However, having multiple governments meant they would have different interests, so conflict would occur very easily. Sadly, due to the Luhan Beastmen's past, they were forced to use this structure. It would be very difficult to change it even though they knew what the problem was—no tribe was willing to voluntarily give up their power.

The Luhan Beastmen Civilization was considered a comparatively weak Star System civilization. Every tribe ruled a few colonial planets, and they only had around a hundred planets in total, spread about different places.

A Star System usually had more than ten Star Zones. For example, a powerful Star System civilization like Godora would be able to rule an entire Star System and all the Star Zones. On the other hand, multiple Star System civilizations existed in some Star Systems. They all ruled some Star Zones and fought for resources. Of course, those Star Systems were weaker in comparison.

"You want to make the Rockfall Tribe independent, leave the alliance civilization, and develop in another Star Cluster as a branch of the Luhan Beastmen?" Han Xiao nodded.

"That's right." Faleta quickly agreed.

"Do you know the consequences of that? If you do that, a lot of your people will choose to stay and not migrate with you." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"I will settle that. There are quite many who are displeased with Klent in the other tribes," Faleta replied with a deep voice.

Han Xiao then stopped asking questions and slowly said, "Okay, when you've made up your mind, contact me anytime."

He only cared about carrying out the job in exchange for money. Someone else's tribe would be someone else's responsibility. With the Black Star Army's ability, taking care of a tribe's migration was no difficult task.

In the universe, it was not rare for a civilization's government to seek independence, so he was not surprised by this.

Faleta nodded continuously. The migration process would be very dangerous, so they needed guards. Initially, he had been hesitant. Once he saw Harmon and Black Star's relationship, he felt that the Black Star Army might be able to make this plan work.

The migration matter had to be discussed with the next chief, Harmon. However, with Harmon's personality and experience, he would most likely refuse to be Klent's vassal as well.

They arrived at the Rockfall Tribe's planet and stayed as guests for three days. Then, Han Xiao bade farewell to Harmon and continued to head to the Bloodshed Land.

Harmon went to be a chief, but if the Rockfall Tribe decided to migrate, they would still have the chance to meet in the future.

Ten days later, a thick blue stream of light dashed across the universe.

Planet Heber appeared in their sights. The blue stream of light stopped, and a spaceship appeared, slowly flying toward Planet Heber. At this time, there were already many spaceships landing on and leaving Planet Heber.

"It's been more than ten years since I last came." Looking at Planet Heber, it still had the same old look. Han Xiao turned to look at Ames and said, "I came with you last time too."

"You were much cuter back then." Ames smiled.

"Time sure passes fast." Han Xiao sighed and told Phillip to land the spaceship.

This was his second time stepping onto the Bloodshed Land's headquarters. More than ten years ago, he had been Ames' follower. Today, he had received an official invitation as someone that stood at the top of the Shattered Star Ring.

The spaceship had already reported their identity and flew into the port following instructions. As the ship landed, Hila and the Black Star Guards led the way at the front and disembarked from the spaceship first. Han Xiao and Ames then stepped onto the dock.

Both of them were wearing black. Han Xiao wore his black windbreaker, as usual, and a few mechanical hovering guards swam around him mischievously.

Ames wore her high-cut black dress as always. The dress complemented her long and beautiful legs, making her look royal and gorgeous.

"Your Excellency Black Star, Your Excellency Dragon Emperor."

The Vanguard Official captain, Fosters, was waiting at the dock to welcome the two of them. He greeted them with a stiff tone.

"Yo, isn't this an old opponent?" Han Xiao chuckled. "I remember you were saying you're going to kill me during the war. Why aren't you saying that now?"

Fosters clenched his teeth tightly and glared at Han Xiao, but he did not dare to respond. It was clear that the Tyrant intended to make peace with Black Star by inviting him this time, which actually made the Bloodshed Land officer feel quite resentful.

However, this was Heber's order, and they could not disobey it. They had no choice but to swallow their rage.

"Please. Follow. Me!" Fosters squeezed out one word after another between his teeth, turned around, and led the way, making up his mind about not responding to Han Xiao.

Seeing this, Han Xiao did not want to make fun of him anymore. He walked beside Ames and followed Fosters into the guest castle.

He attended a Tyrant Party before, so he knew the procedure. They would usually stay a few days in the guest castle, communicate with the representatives of the other organizations, and expand their network while waiting for all the guests to arrive. The party would then start officially.

The players who followed behind were filled with curiosity. This was their first time in the Bloodshed Land headquarters, so it felt refreshing. They secretly wondered what Han Xiao's intentions were. The Tyrant Party was an activity for those in high positions, so the players did not know about this at all.

After a peaceful walk, they arrived at the guest castle. There were already many representatives of large organizations inside. They were surprised to see Han Xiao and Ames, and the atmosphere became strange.

Many people looked like they could not wait to talk to them.

With the Evolution Cube in his hands, everyone wanted to get close to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao did not walk in immediately and asked, "Is the Tyrant not planning to see us now?"

"Don't know, don't ask me," Fosters replied with a stiff tone.

Just as he was about to turn around and leave, he suddenly stopped and looked at Hadavy. "You're now a member of the Black Star Army, huh?"

"Hmm?" Hadavy realized that Fosters was talking to him and nodded. "Yes, I'm now a Black Star Guard. The treatment's quite good. Do you want to come too?"

Fosters felt as if he was being ridiculed and was furious.

Hadavy had once worked with the Bloodshed Land, but it had ended after Jorde used him. He had then joined Han Xiao.

However, in Fosters' eyes, this felt like Hadavy had 'walked into the light from the darkness'. He was already enraged, and now he was furious and needed to vent it. "As a Bloodshed Land Vanguard Official, I challenge the Black Star Army's Black Star Guards. Who dares fight me?"

Hearing what Fosters said, Ames and Han Xiao's expressions became strange. They looked at each other's eyes and realized that they thought of the same thing as if they had communicated with their eyes.

Haven't we seen this before?

Isn't this similar to when you challenged that traitor, Carroll?

Han Xiao smiled with resignation.

In the past, he had taught Floating Dragon's traitor a lesson for Ames. Now, the Bloodshed Land's officers had become the side that were displeased and wanting to challenge his guards. How the tables had turned.

Fosters was loyal to the Tyrant. Heber had failed in establishing power, so Fosters wanted to try to earn some pride back. Hence, he targeted Han Xiao's officers. Although Han Xiao was an invited guest, the relationship between the two sides was odd. He was not willing to show friendliness to an enemy that had killed more than three digits of Bloodshed Land high-level combatants.

It was a just challenge, so it would be difficult even for a Beyond Grade A to stop it. Furthermore, the Bloodshed Land did not stop Han Xiao from challenging Carroll more than ten years ago.

Like thunder, his voice attracted the attention of the various representatives in the hall.

Hila narrowed her eyes and stepped forward. "Where are we going to fight?"

"Who are you?"

"Captain of the Black Star Guards, Hila!"

A murderous intent flashed through Fosters' eyes. Just as he was about to speak, a shadow suddenly shrouded him. A deep voice came from behind him.

"Get back."

The crowd looked up and their expression changed. It was the Tyrant, Heber.

Hearing Heber ordering him to stop the challenge, Fosters clenched his teeth and turned around and left, quickly disappearing from everyone's sight.

Hila took a few steps, too.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and looked up at the tiny mountain-tall Heber. Heber looked down at him with an expressionless face.

The atmosphere around seemed to become heavy. Other than Ames, everyone in the hall felt that it was difficult to breathe.

As the atmosphere kept getting tenser, Heber suddenly spoke and shattered the uptight atmosphere.

"Black Star, Dragon Emperor, follow me. Let's have a chat between us five Beyond Grade As."

Then, he turned around and walked into his palace.

It seemed like how the two of them treated each other in the future would be decided this time. Without hesitation, Han Xiao told Hila and the others to rest in the guest room while he followed Heber into the palace.

"All five?"

With a faint smile on her face, Ames followed him into the palace as well.

Chapter 789: Meeting and Goal

The two of them walked into Heber's palace and arrived at an enormous circular hall with five hovering thrones. Heber sat on one of them. Two of the other four thrones were already occupied. It was Austin and Psyker.

"Hehe, we meet again so soon." Austin greeted them with a smile.

This old man... Han Xiao thought in his mind and looked at Psyker on the other side.

Psyker almost never attended the Tyrant Party, but he had come. Han Xiao was quite surprised.

Er, maybe because he no longer has the Evolution Cube, he doesn't have to stay at home anymore?

"Black Star." Psyker nodded with a calm expression as if Han Xiao was not an enemy that had taken the Evolution Cube away from him.

Han Xiao could not guess Psyker's intentions. He nodded in response and did not speak.

Although they had a conflict of interests and personal hatred against each other, they were all Beyond Grade As of the Shattered Star Ring, so they would not start fighting as soon as they saw each other.

Ames floated up and sat on the throne. The eyes of the other four all focused on Han Xiao.

Han Xiao smiled, floated up, and landed on the last empty seat, the newly added fifth throne.

At this moment, he had officially entered this circle.

The five of them sat on the thrones—this was the new peak power structure of the Shattered Star Ring.

"Everyone is here. Let's have a proper talk," Heber said with a deep voice and turned to look at Han Xiao. "First, our problem. There are two choices in front of us. One is to continue to oppose each other, and the other is temporary peace."

"Hmm, I'm listening." Han Xiao did not make a stand.

"Since you are now an ally of the Crimson Dynasty as well, we have no choice but to become allies on paper, and we must stand on the same side," Heber said slowly. "During the decade-long secret war, you killed many of my subordinates. Many of your warriors died at the hands of my men, too. The hatred between us is too strong. You definitely won't be willing to take a step back, and neither am I. How about we put our conflict aside for the time being and get back to it in the future?"

"What you mean is, we shall slowly settle this after the Flickering World's exploration ends?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

Too many of their comrades had died at each other's hands in the past decade, so things would not be settled easily. This was already beyond what just the leaders wanted. If they forced an alliance, their subordinates would not be able to accept it. This would not be beneficial in the unity of their faction.

Heber nodded before shaking his head. "We don't have to work together. The Flickering World is very broad. We can ceasefire and do our own exploring, not interfering with each other. This way, the Crimson Dynasty's request will be fulfilled, and there is no need to compromise."

Han Xiao rubbed his chin. This proposal was quite sensible.

The two sides would not form an alliance but explore the Flickering World separately. To the Crimson Dynasty, as long as the two of them did not drag each other down, it would be acceptable. Even the Crimson Dynasty would not be able to force a Beyond Grade A to let go of his hatred and shake hands with his enemy.

He roughly understood what the Tyrant meant. Exploring the Flickering World was very important to the Crimson Dynasty. As a completely unexplored new Star Field, there were too many areas that could be developed in the Flickering World.

The results of their exploration would not just be the fundamentals of their own organizations' future development—the Crimson Dynasty would also reward them for the results of their exploration.

This meant that although they were allies on paper, they were also competitors—they were competing in their exploring ability in the Flickering World.

"No, the Bloodshed Land is not the only competitor. The Crimson Dynasty will gather their allies from the various Star Fields to explore this together. By then, I will have to fight with more organizations for resources."

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

His advantage in this respect was way too huge.

To just about every explorer, the Flickering World was an unfamiliar area, and they had to depend on luck to explore it. To him, however, the map of the Flickering World was crystal clear. He knew about the resources in the various areas; there was no way the other competitors would surpass him!

"Okay, I agree with this plan. We shall have a temporary ceasefire and mind our own business. When exploring the Flickering World, do what we can and don't drag each other down." Han Xiao nodded.

The Flickering World was the most important. At this crucial time, there was no need to drag each other down. The Tyrant felt this way, too.

After the Crimson Dynasty completed their initial exploration and obtained a large amount of resources, only then would they open the Flickering World to the entire Star Field. Only then would the non-ally organizations enter the new Star Field, shuffle the organizations in chaos, fight for territory and resources, and form the structure of the Flickering World.

The players all over Galaxy would then enter the Flickering World.

In his previous life, the update between Version 3.0 and Version 4.0 had been when the Crimson Dynasty carried out their initial exploration. However, because of his actions, the majority of the Shattered Star Ring players would be able to enter the Flickering World in advance. This was a rather significant advantage.

As the World Server to the players, many guilds had occupied desolate planets in the Flickering World in his previous life and built their own strongholds. During that version, guild wars had been very frequent, and the players had been more active. As the players of the Shattered Star Ring would enter before others, they would have more time to operate their strongholds.

However, the players now did not know that the Flickering World would become the World Server in the future.

"Okay," Heber slowly replied.

As Han Xiao had become an ally of the dynasty, he put the thought of using Han Xiao to build his reputation away, knowing that he could not do that. Therefore, he treated Han Xiao differently and saw him as someone on his level.

Having decided on the ceasefire agreement, Han Xiao nodded in his mind—the main goal of attending this Tyrant Party had finally been achieved.

Although true peace would not be achieved, it was enough for now.

This time, Psyker slowly said, "Now, it's time for us to talk."

Han Xiao looked over at Psyker and said, "The Evolution Cube is in my hands. If you're not planning to give it up, are you planning to continue to be my enemy?"

"The Crimson Dynasty has its eyes on the Evolution Cube and is willing to back you up. I know it's impossible for you to return it to me, so the only way is to snatch it back from you."

Psyker did not hide his intention of the Evolution Cube at all. "However, can the Crimson Dynasty protect you at all times? Even if they can protect you, can they protect your Black Star Army? You don't have to stare at me like that. I'm not threatening you, just telling you the truth. Even if I'm willing to give up, the Arcane Church won't give up, and even the Federation of Light will act."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "You don't have to threaten me. The Evolution Cube is the relic of a certain sub-Universal Civilization from the exploration era. It's indeed an amazing item, but you managed to hold onto it for so long, didn't you?"

"Our situations are different." Psyker glanced at Heber and suddenly said, "You'd better be careful about the Crimson Dynasty's allies."

"Hmm?" Han Xiao frowned.

"Those organizations going to explore the Flickering World are all allies of the Crimson Dynasty from various Star Fields. The dynasty can block the exterior pressure for you, but internal hostility..." Psyker narrowed his eyes. "What's important to the Crimson Dynasty is the Evolution Cube itself; the person that possesses it might not be so important. The Evolution Cube has immeasurable value to an organization. Some people might take the risk and target you. Once you die... what do you think the Crimson Dynasty will do?"

"I get what you mean, save the boring provocation." Han Xiao shook his head.

What Psyker meant was that the Crimson Dynasty's allies all had their own interests. There might be another Beyond Grade A from another Star Field interested in the Evolution Cube and would find the opportunity to kill him for it. As long as it did not get discovered before it was done, the dynasty would not do anything for a dead man. However, Han Xiao had once stayed in the Crimson Dynasty for many years and knew very well of the dynasty's way of doing things. The possibility of that happening was very low.

The Federation of Light might do something like this, but the Crimson Dynasty would not.

The dynasty would only use this as an excuse to acquire the Evolution Cube themselves. Even for a Beyond Grade A ally, as long as anyone broke the rules, they would still uphold their standards. It could be seen from the Crimson Tide event that the dynasty was very firm and stern.

Psyker's expression remained the same. His plan was not to threaten Han Xiao—this was just casual talk. He then said coldly, "Don't forget, EsGod also has his eyes on the Evolution Cube. If he finds you, you'd better pray you run fast enough."

EsGod...

Han Xiao thought of EsGod's number in the blacklist of his communicator, and his expression became odd.

"About the Evolution Cube, I will handle it, no need to trouble you." Han Xiao sized Psyker up. "I'm curious, what are you really doing here today? Just trying to scare me?"

"Who said I'm here for you?" Psyker shook his head.

He did indeed not come for Han Xiao. As he had needed to guard the Evolution Cube in the past, he had rarely left the Star Pupil Holy Race's territory. Furthermore, with the Evolution Cube in his hands, the support from the Arcane Church had come nonstop. He had a superior position and had no need to attend this kind of gathering.

Now, however, his Evolution Cube had been taken away. Like he had broken off his chains, he had decided to become active in the Star Field. This was not just because he wanted to but also because he would not be as important to the Arcane Church now that he no longer possessed the Evolution Cube. He planned to get out and move around, do some networking by attending the Tyrant Party, and work toward making his race a Star Cluster civilization.

Then, Psyker closed his eyes and did not want to speak to Han Xiao anymore.

Han Xiao then turned to look at Austin. Seeing that the old man was staring at him with bright eyes, he sighed and said, "Do you also have something to say to me?"

Austin extended his tiny finger and pointed at the Evolution Cube on Han Xiao's neck, chuckled, and said, "Let's make a deal. Let me use it once. I will fulfill one request for you."

"Hehe." Han Xiao did not smile at all.

When he was troubled in the past, Austin did not help him. Now that things had settled down, this guy finally came to make a deal with him, thinking that there would be more than enough chances to exchange a chance to use the Evolution Cube given Han Xiao's personality.

You damn old man...

Han Xiao was filled with resignation. His goal of obtaining the Evolution Cube was to gain favor all along. Using it to exchange for a Beyond Grade A's promise was worth it no matter how he looked at it. There was no reason for him to refuse.

"Any request?" Han Xiao snorted. He pointed at Psyker and said, "Then fight with me now and kill this guy."

Psyker was unaffected and continued to rest with his eyes closed.

"Stop messing around. You know I can't agree to that request." Austin shook his head with a bitter smile. With a luring tone like he was tricking a little girl, he said, "Request something else. How about you play with my Palace of Hidden Spells? I can lend it to you for a few months."

"Lend it to me? How about you give it to me?"

"Come on, we've known each other for quite some time. Don't be so greedy."

"This is a no, that's a no, what can you do for me?"

Austin contemplated, then shrugged, and said, "Don't know, but you won't make a loss."

Veins popped up on Han Xiao's forehead. You don't say. There's no cost to let you use the Evolution Cube. Of course I won't make a loss, but you will make a huge profit!

Suddenly, he had a flash of inspiration.

"How about you help me to deal with EsGod?"

"... Let's talk about killing Psyker."

Psyker's eyelids twitched uncontrollably.

The two of them negotiated back and forth for so long Ames started to yawn. Then Han Xiao and Austin finally came to an agreement.

First, a Beyond Grade A Mage could cross multiple dimensions and would frequently acquire some extremely rare materials. Austin had to provide some materials consisting of the genes of high-grade Void beings for free every year.

Second, the Hidden Red Robe Abbey would form a half-alliance with the Black Star Army. The Hidden Red Robe Abbey had to send high-level Mages to the army every year to train some Mages as well as teach some rare spells.

Last, Austin had to do something within his ability and not against his morals... and the final definition of 'morals' depended on Austin.

There was nothing Han Xiao could do about him. The two of them had quite a good relationship, and Austin even helped him a few times in the past. Thus, he was not willing to let that all go to waste over the Evolution Cube.

"By the way..." Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and threw an Observer's Mark over to Austin.

"What are you doing?" Austin was confused and casually shattered the Observer's Mark. As a Beyond Grade A Mage, breaking such a simple Void Energy application method was a piece of cake, even though Han Xiao was also a Beyond Grade A. After all, he was a Mage that could control energies of multiple dimensions.

Han Xiao did not give up and threw another Observer's Mark, and Austin shattered it with his eyes opened wide again.

The two of them stared at each other and repeated the process more than a dozen times. In the end, Austin gave up resisting and allowed the Observer's Mark to land on his forehead with resignation.

Only then did Han Xiao nod with satisfaction. He felt much better.

Heber felt a little bit of headache and regretted putting the two of them together.

The atmosphere had been so intense, but it was suddenly not serious at all!

Seeing that Austin had made a deal with Han Xiao, it suddenly occurred to Heber.

Among the five people present, it seemed like he was the only one that had no chance to use the Evolution Cube.

Heber looked at the Evolution Cube, then Han Xiao's face, and his eyelids twitched slightly. Without even thinking, he knew that Black Star would definitely not agree to let him use the Evolution Cube.

Suppressing the desire inside, Heber adjusted his emotions and slowly said, "Black Star and I will stay here. The three of you can leave."

"Looks like you guys had quite a good chat. Black Star, I shall leave first." Ames stood up and stretched.

She was not interested in the matters discussed there. It looked like she had just attended to show her face, but as Han Xiao's ally, showing up meant making her stand clear.

Among the five people present, she and Han Xiao were the only ones that were firm allies. Although the other three did not mention this, they knew it clearly. In terms of strength, given that Han Xiao and Ames were on the same side, they surpassed the other three completely.

The three of them left, and the gate of the hall closed again, leaving only Han Xiao and Heber in the room.

This time, the side door opened, and Zoel walked out with a smile.

"I'm glad the two of you have come to an agreement."

"Envoy." The two of them nodded slightly as a greeting.

Zoel was followed by a Klent representative. Everyone in the room was on the same side on paper, so it was clear that they were going to discuss official business.

As expected, Zoel pressed on his waist. A 3D star map projection appeared in midair, drawing out a new shining area in the wide universe map. It was marked as the 'Flickering World'.

"Using this opportunity, let me explain the current situation in the Flickering World, so you guys can understand the rough process of the exploration," Zoel said loudly. "Carefully prepare for your exploration plan. When the developments start officially, we're all going to have missions."

It seemed like this was for them to consider the areas they were going to explore...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Chapter 790: Main Storyline—[Flickering World]

The 3D star map showed the Flickering World area. In the black unexplored universe, there was an area that was shining. This was the rich Star Cluster the three Universal Civilizations discovered outside the Shattered Star Ring using their radar. It was named the Dawn Star Cluster.

The Dawn Star Cluster was the area first detected by the radar and, currently, the only Star Cluster officially belonging to the Flickering World. As the starting point of the exploration of a new Star Field, it was marked in green. Outside it were the extremely wide unexplored areas marked in gray.

Being the only one that was lighted up, the Dawn Star Cluster was like an island in the middle of a wide sea.

Developing a new Star Field was a huge task, and the expected date of it completing was unpredictable. After all, the actual exploration was different from astronomical observation.

The Crimson Dynasty had spent more than a decade obtaining the Dawn Star Cluster from the Federation of Light and defined it as the starting point of the new Star Field. Due to the two of them restraining each other, the development of it had always been on hold. However, the astronomical observation of the three civilizations had never stopped. After observing it for more than ten years, the rough area included in the Flickering World was already defined.

In the star map given by the Crimson Dynasty, the Flickering World was divided into roughly nineteen Star Clusters with various sizes. The size of the Dawn Star Cluster made up only three percent of the entire Star Field. Everything else was unexplored.

The size of desolate universe belts varied, and there would usually be many small to medium desolate universe belts inside Star Fields. Only the extremely large desolate universe belts would be considered as the border of a Star Field. The Flickering World was no exception. It was estimated that there were more than 7,000 small to medium desolate universe belts within it, some between Star Zones and some between Star Systems, spread across the entire Flickering World.

Therefore, to the dynasty's exploration team, selecting areas was very important. If the area they were going to explore was filled with desolate universe belts, the profit they made would be very low.

"The dynasty has decided to first explore the three Star Clusters around the Dawn Star Cluster for the first stage of the exploration," Zoel said while pointing them out on the map. "They're the Renault, Garu, and Crown Star Clusters."

Han Xiao, Heber, and the Klent representative paid careful attention to the star map. This was the initial star map created by astronomical observation. Due to the complicated universe environment, it would be somewhat inaccurate, but the rough distribution of planets was usually correct.

Among the three Star Clusters, the Garu Star Cluster was the largest. It had a number of obvious desolate universe belts, and the other two were ordinary.

There were two types of desolate universe belts. One had very sparse planets that were very far from each other or lacked Fixed Stars or some high energy astronomical bodies—those were areas discoverable by astronomical observation. The other type of desolate universe belt were the ones that had generally poor planets with little resources. This type of desolate universe belt was more difficult to find compared to the former, as it would look like a normal area until field exploration proved otherwise.

Although there was already a rough sketch of the star map, basically every planet's information was unknown. The aim of the Crimson Dynasty's exploration of it was to compile detailed information on every planet in it and adjust the astronomical observation errors, as well as occupy the rich planets within it in advance.

This was the task of the exploration team—even obvious desolate universe belts had to be explored.

There were a ton of planets in every Star Field. Even though the dynasty only planned to explore three Star Clusters first, it was still a vast project.

Heber looked at it for a while and made his decision. "Renault Star Cluster."

The Bloodshed Land and the Klent Kingdom would be developing the same area.

"Black Star, what about you?" Zoel turned around.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and said, "I shall choose the Garu then."

"I see, Garu, the number of people that have chosen this area is the smallest... alright." Zoel nodded.

Han Xiao smiled in his mind.

He knew that among these three Star Clusters, the Garu Star Cluster had the highest potential profit.

It seemed like the Garu Star Cluster had more desolate universe belts compared to the other two, but the other two Star Clusters had quite a number of hidden desolate universe belts, so the difference was not really that large. Furthermore, in the desolate universe belts of the Garu Star Cluster, there were some Galactic Civilization ruins that possessed archeological value.

In terms of resources, the Garu Star Cluster was slightly larger. It had many Fixed Stars, habitable planets, and slightly more resource planets. In terms of species, the Garu Star Cluster had more intelligent species that had formed civilizations, and the majority of them were still in the surface civilization stage. This meant that exploring would be easier.

In his previous life, the Garu Star Cluster had been one of the most prosperous Star Clusters in the Flickering World. Therefore, after thorough consideration, Han Xiao decided to develop the Garu Star Cluster.

Another important reason was that in Han Xiao's memories, that Universal Treasure in the Flickering World with no owner was located in a desolate universe belt near the Garu Star Cluster and not included in the areas for the dynasty's first stage exploration. He would only be able to head there if he was close by.

For now, no one other than me even knows the existence of this Universal Treasure. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had to obtain it.

This time, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered Grade S+ Chain Mission [Flickering World]

Mission Introduction: The Flickering World. A new Star Field represents a new structure. It's your job to explore this Star Field, so it is your opportunity.

Hint: Mission requirements, mission rewards, exploration points, and the Mission Rating depend on your faction.

You belong to the Crimson Dynasty and the Black Star Army.

Mission Requirements: According to the areas selected, explore the Flickering World for the Crimson Dynasty as a member of the Black Star Army.

You have received the first round of exploration goals.

Current Exploration Area: Garu Star Cluster

Personal Exploration Points: 0

Total Exploration Points: 0

Current Rating: E-

Remarks: Your mission reward depends on the Mission Rating. The Mission Rating depends on the Total Exploration Points.

Exploration Points are earned from the results of the exploration, such as completing the field exploration of a planet, improving the planet information, adjusting the star map error, discovering a civilization's ruins, contacting an intelligent species, operating a stronghold, discovering habitable and resource planets, discovering rare resources, and so on.

The main storyline mission of the Flickering World! Han Xiao was thrilled.

The scale of this main storyline was huge, and it was very complicated. It was considered a combination of a Chain Mission and Faction Series Mission. The main reason for it to be Grade S+ was because of how complicated and time-consuming it was.

Firstly, the details of this mission changed depending on one's side. Not every player was a member of the Crimson Dynasty. After the Flickering World opened to the world, the players of the various Star Fields would represent different organizations and have different areas to explore, hence the different ways in calculating their reward.

For example, for the Crimson Dynasty, the area they explored was broad, meaning it would be more difficult.

The Personal Exploration Points were one's own achievements, which would grant rewards when it reached a certain number. Compared to the other factions, the Exploration Points needed to trigger the reward under the Crimson Dynasty faction were higher, but the rewards were richer.

The Total Exploration Points were the total of all the Personal Exploration Points of the players in the same faction. This required the players of the same faction to work together. It also gave rewards once it reached a certain stage. The Total Exploration Points were also associated with the Mission Rating. When the Total Exploration Points were more than enough to increase the rating, all the players of the same faction would receive rewards distributed according to the players' Personal Exploration Points ranking.

Every exploration area meant one round of the Chain Mission. Once done, the reward would be given based on the rating. When going to a new exploration area, both the Personal Exploration Points and the Total Exploration Points would be reset to zero. The Grade S+ overall mission [Flickering World] would only be completed after the entire Star Field was explored, which would then give rewards based on the Exploration Points and Mission Rating of every area.

Han Xiao pondered. The exploration had yet to officially start. Now that he had this mission, he could distribute it to the army players and make preparations in advance.

At the same time, he could let the players know that they had a new main storyline after the secret war.

After the business was settled, the star map shrank back to the device on Zoel's waist.

Zoel smiled and said, "I will report your choices to the dynasty. There most likely won't be a problem."

The Shattered Star Ring was the nearest to the Flickering World, so the allies in this area would be at the frontline of the exploration. The areas they chose would mostly remain unchanged.

"One more thing." Zoel looked at Han Xiao. "The first batch of elite personnel to accept transformation from the Evolution Cube have already entered the Shattered Star Ring following the dynasty's transport team. They will arrive at the Colton Star Cluster in some time. Black Star, don't forget about this. The first batch of resources for you are with them."

"Hmm, I'll head over after the meeting." Han Xiao nodded before asking, "Who are the first batch of people?"

"I have a list here, take a look." Zoel transmitted a document to him.

Looking through the list, Han Xiao was surprised.

There was a total of 30,000 people, all elite soldiers from the army selected by the dynasty. At the top of the list, he really did see familiar names, and more than one.

Among them, he had a very deep impression of one name.

One of the future dynasty marshals... Teny Amenos?

Han Xiao's eyes widened slightly.

"After this group of elite completes the transformation," Zoel said, "a small group of them will stay to take part in the Flickering World while the rest will return to the dynasty. You can go along with them to the Central Galaxy and meet the dynasty upper echelons... Black Star, Black Star?"

"Oh." Han Xiao regained focus. "I heard you, let's do that."

"Okay." Zoel did not suspect anything. He nodded and said, "That'll be all."

The others nodded, and Han Xiao left Heber's palace directly.

Once returning to the suite, before Han Xiao sat down for long, someone suddenly knocked on his door. Hila opened the door, and a few people stood outside.

They were the representatives of a few other Star Clusters in the Shattered Star Ring. Seeing that Han Xiao had returned, they chased right after him and went to knock on his door almost immediately after he entered.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we hope to chat with you," one of them said with a smile.

"Please come in." Han Xiao invited them in and knew exactly why they were there.

As expected, they chatted for only a little bit before the topic became the Evolution Cube.

However, this was just a start. Right after, the various representatives attending the Tyrant Party all came to his doorstep.

Very soon, about ninety-five percent of the people in the guest castle had come.

The enormous suite suddenly became cramped.

Everyone wanted a piece of the Evolution Cube.

The Tyrant Party was initially an activity for Heber to toughen his influence, so the guests were all someone important in the Shattered Star Ring. This gave Han Xiao the opportunity to spread his network.

Using this, Han Xiao also started to talk about terms with the various organizations.

"As for the Evolution Cube, the Crimson Dynasty did not restrict my use of it. If you want to borrow it, it is possible if you can fulfill my terms," Han Xiao said with a smile.

Everyone in the room kept quiet and listened. Han Xiao's voice was the only sound in the room.

Ames looked at this from outside the room.

You really are good at operating an organization...

Chapter 791: Star Field Profit Blueprint

"I can give you guys opportunities to undergo a transformation, and the terms are very simple."

Han Xiao looked around at the others and said, "First, of course, money. You will have to pay me Enas every year in exchange for the fixed allocation of using the Evolution Cube. It doesn't have to be money—minerals, materials, and other resources can be used as well."

"How much every year?" a Star Cluster civilization representative asked.

"That depends on your needs."

"The lending fee every year will depend on the basic allocation number you want to purchase every year. Report it to me in advance, and I will arrange the schedule. Every organization can purchase up to a million allocations every year. I'm quite busy, after all."

Han Xiao's time was limited, so it was impossible for him to spend all his time using the Evolution Cube for the others. Furthermore, multiple uses of the Evolution Cube for an individual would weaken its effects.

Someone could not help asking, "What if we hope to have the entire race evolved?"

"Good question." Han Xiao raised his brows. "Other than basic allocations, you can purchase extra allocations, which doesn't have an upper limit. However, the price for that will be much higher than the basic allocations. I'm not underestimating your purchasing power, but given the large population of your civilizations, that will most likely be very costly."

Some civilization representatives felt a little regret. To them, having their entire race use the Evolution Cube at once would be best. Sadly, Han Xiao was clearly not willing to do that.

A Star System civilization would have a population of billions at the very least. The fee would be over the roof.

However, after thinking about it, having the entire race evolve was indeed unnecessary. Every high-level civilization had a ton of people that never contributed to society and were just waiting for days to pass. Purchasing evolution allocations for them was obviously a waste.

To have some of the elites' genes improved every year with the one million slots was acceptable for the representatives of the civilizations.

Han Xiao then said, "Secondly, business partnership. This depends on the nature of your organization. Civilizations can provide the rights to mining planets, transport channels, and military factory usage. Armed forces will have to form an alliance with the Black Star Army and share intelligence. Financial groups can provide more partnerships on the business side... These are the prerequisites of buying allocations from me."

The people there came from different organizations. Han Xiao did this to expand the Black Star Army's business to the various industries, hoping to bloom in all fields.

At the same time, through business partnerships, he could form a deeper partnership relationship with these organizations.

This was within their expectations, so they were not surprised.

Through the analysis of various information, they knew that Black Star was ambitious. Since there was a chance for his organization to become a Beyond Grade A organization, he would of course not be satisfied with it just being a pure armed force.

"Last... I hope to have a seat in the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

The Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference was similar to the Galaxy Central Civilization Court, a political civilization alliance. Being a Star System civilization was the entry requirement.

The civilization representatives exchanged looks. Someone said hesitantly, "Only civilizations can attend the conference. Black Star, although your forces are powerful, you're not a civilization."

Han Xiao smiled. "Don't worry, I know the rule. I'm planning to use my mother planet's name."

Planet Aquamarine?

They exchanged looks.

"If I remember correctly, the civilization on your mother planet has yet to reach the Star System level..."

Han Xiao shrugged. "Hence this term."

He would only have official political influence after he obtained a seat at the Civilization Conference. This way, even if Planet Aquamarine did not reach the Star System level, it would also be protected by the 'Peace Treaty'.

He would benefit from it, too. Not only would his personal position be higher, the Black Star Army under his command would also be a semi-government. The army members would be protected by all kinds of laws.

Simply put, if this was agreed, if other players attacked any Black Star Army members, including themselves, and it was discovered, they would all become 'red names' and lose Favorability with a lot of organizations.

Hearing Han Xiao's terms, the various civilization representatives sighed. This was beyond their authority. They all said that this was not for them to decide and that they had to ask their superiors before getting back to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao was not worried. The Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference was controlled by the Star Cluster civilizations of this Star Field. Since these Star Cluster civilizations wanted to work with him, adding him in as an exception would not be difficult. They just needed an excuse.

During the secret war times, quite a number of Star Cluster civilizations had secretly done things because they did not want to see Black Star rise. However, there was nothing they could do anymore. With resignation, they could only lower their heads and seek cooperation.

The Shattered Star Ring had been affected by the Crimson Tide for a decade. Its structure had changed in subtle ways. This was the time to grasp onto opportunities.

After roughly settling on the terms, the guests left one after another—they had only gone to express their intentions. The details had to be discussed by the corresponding departments of both sides. This would be Sylvia and Phillip's job.

Han Xiao tapped the table and pondered.

In his plan, this was a key step in the Black Star Army's expansion—using the Evolution Cube, he would form a connected profit network with the Black Star Army at its center!

Not only would he benefit from the partnerships, the channels of the various organizations would be linked as well, forming an enormous profit network.

In order to achieve this, his organization had to be strong enough. Of course, as a Beyond Grade A organization, the Black Star Army was qualified.

With this opportunity, the Black Star Army would be able to become stronger very quickly. Maintaining this profit network would indirectly turn the entire Shattered Star Ring into the Black Star Army's base, providing continuous resources.

Currently, the Evolution Cube was the key for this to work. As long as he could make the various organizations see that they could benefit from this, even without the Evolution Cube, they would still continue to maintain the cooperation. Similar to how Heber had made the Tyrant Party into a recognized party for the people at the top of the society, Han Xiao's goal was to make the Black Star Army the core of the Shattered Star Ring's profit network.

...

After three days, the guests finally all arrived. In the early morning, Heber invited everyone to the palace and officially started the party.

The hall was set up as a banquet. With the musicians playing their instruments in the background, the representatives of the various organizations formed small circles and spoke softly.

Han Xiao and the others occupied a corner, and many people gathered around them.

The players were taken there as well. They looked left and right curiously and kept throwing [Reconnaissance] at the people around. Everyone they saw was someone important. The few Beyond Grade As were chatting with people in the hall as well.

Over the past few days, the players had asked around about the Tyrant Party. Now that they had seen so many organizations' representatives, this party suddenly felt much more high class.

The guests there were basically the rulers of the Shattered Star Ring. It turned out that Black Star was at this level.

The players would usually not be able to come into contact with the activities between those high-level people. When these players shared the details of the Tyrant Party on the forums, only then did the players know that this existed. They all discussed it with excitement.

"So, this is the level of people that Black Star has been in contact with now."

"He's a faction leader, of course."

"All Beyond Grade As are there? Haha, won't they start fighting?"

"Isn't the Bloodshed Land our enemy? Why did Black Star go?"

This time, Heber stepped out of the crowd. The people stopped chatting, and they all looked at Heber.

"In the past decade or so, the Shattered Star Ring has been through many storms. Fortunately, I can still see so many familiar faces here today," Heber said slowly. "Before the party starts, I would like to make an announcement."

Then, he turned to look at Han Xiao and said, "After private negotiations, Black Star and I have agreed to a temporary ceasefire, and we will take part in the Crimson Dynasty's development of the Flickering World together. Everyone here shall be a witness."

The others turned to look at Han Xiao, and Han Xiao nodded in agreement.

"Flickering World?" many players murmured. This piece of information attracted their attention immediately.

Han Xiao smiled in his head. He had known for sure that Heber would announce this during the party. He immediately distributed the mission that he had prepared on the faction interface.

At the same time, on the list of acceptable missions on the many players' faction interface, the Grade S+ main storyline mission [Flickering World] was instantly pinned at the top.

"Oi, a new main storyline mission!"

"What, Grade S+? That's higher than the secret war!"

"This should be the next main storyline of Version 3.0."

"Develop the Flickering World. Looks like this will be the next big operation for the Black Star Army."

The army players were surprised, and many instantly accepted the mission.

A main storyline with such a high grade was clearly a huge event. After the secret war ended, many players had entered the free exploration stage with no clear goal, but now they had a new goal.

Due to the recent chain of events, the players had an overflowing sense of belonging to the army. In their eyes, the Black Star Army's storyline was basically the main storyline.

The players did not know much about the Flickering World. Countless posts appeared on the forums to discuss it immediately. Han Xiao scanned them and was satisfied with the impact.

However, the army players did not know that not only was [Flickering World] the Version 3.0 storyline after the secret war, it was also a large main storyline that would last the whole of the next version.

...

The business that had to be discussed had already been discussed a few days ago, and the official party was just a routine.

Since Heber had announced the ceasefire, of course, he did not allow his subordinates to cause any trouble. With his restrictions, no matter how resentful Fosters was, he did not make any trouble.

Han Xiao had basically achieved his targets for attending this Tyrant Party, so he was quite satisfied.

After the party ended, he did not stay for long. After he let Austin use the Evolution Cube, he headed back with Ames, Hila, and the others.

Hu!

When the spaceship left Planet Heber, Han Xiao turned on the communicator and contacted Bennett.

Over the past few days, those civilization representatives had relayed his message to their superiors. Those upper echelons had already responded and agreed with his terms.

Very soon, the communication was picked up.

"Han Xiao? How are you free enough to contact me?" Bennett's frank laughter sounded.

"I have to tell you something..." Han Xiao explained.

Hearing what Han Xiao said, Bennett said with an overjoyed tone, "You helped the Aquamarine Federation enter the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference? That's great!"

Planet Aquamarine was just an elementary galactic civilization, way too underqualified to enter the Civilization Conference. Being able to enter the conference as an exception was clearly an opportunity of a lifetime.

"Hmm, I'll be the representative of the civilization. Are you okay with that?" Han Xiao asked.

The seat in the Civilization Conference belonged to the entire civilization. Usually, the representative would be from the government. However, although Han Xiao was close to the Aquamarine Federation, they were still two separate organizations. By doing this, even though this seat belonged to Planet Aquamarine's government, they would only be able to express their opinions in the future through Han Xiao.

Bennett did not hesitate at all. "You're the one that gave us this chance. Plus, you're Planet Aquamarine's protector. Giving you the position will only be beneficial for us."

He had a very clear mindset. Planet Aquamarine would not have been able to achieve what the Black Star Army had achieved today even if they had many years. He did not want to see the Planet Aquamarine civilization making the wrong choices in the future. Therefore, he had been working hard to tie the Planet Aquamarine government and the Black Star Army together.

Han Xiao smiled, chatted casually for a while, and then hung up.

He decided to let Planet Aquamarine use the Evolution Cube on a large scale after returning. Since he had obtained a political seat on Planet Aquamarine, the better Planet Aquamarine grew, the more he would benefit from it.

Speaking of which, I shall go and take a look at the Black Spirit Race. I can let them use the Evolution Cube too, Han Xiao thought. This race admired him like a god, so he considered them to be on his side.

Chapter 792: Teny Amenos

Somewhere in the Shattered Star Ring, many streams of light hyperdrive dashed across the silent universe.

This was an enormous fleet, formed by metal, beast-like Crimson Dynasty ships.

This was a logistics team that the Crimson Dynasty had dispatched to the Shattered Star Ring. Other than transporting resources, they also had the ability to build assembly and military factories.

This logistics team had two main goals—provide the Shattered Star Ring garrison with logistics backup and enhance their military power, and head toward the Flickering World's Dawn Star Cluster to build the dynasty exploration team's main base on the spot.

As for transporting some resources to the Black Star Army, it was just a small matter.

The three Universal Civilizations had many inter-Star Field quick military passages made of enormous stargates that connected the Star Fields. They could also build small to medium-sized stargates between the desolate universe belt to carry out continuous teleportation.

This logistics team spent quite some time gathering the people, but the time taken to travel was not long in comparison. They arrived at the Shattered Star Ring very soon.

On the path of the enormous logistics team, a small recon fleet was leading the way. There were only twelve light recon ships.

Under the 3D map on the radar of the main recon ship, a middle-aged man stood firmly with his hands behind his back, looking up at the map.

Teny Amenos, 0014855 term outstanding graduate of the Dynasty's 'Journey' High-Level Military School. Averaged first among all graduates of the same term in all sixty-two subjects including Strategy, Tactics, and Combat.

Joined the dynasty military after graduation, dispatched into multiple military operations. Galactic wars experienced: more than 1,000. Independent commanding record: 170 times. Promoted multiple times due to exceptional achievements.

Now the colonel of the dynasty's 33rd army, an important person among the dynasty's younger generation. He was also one of the elites going to accept modification from the Evolution Cube.

Being in charge of the recon task for the transport team was his own request.

Teny looked energetic and admirable. The air around him was like a burning flame, bright and tough. His back was straight like a flagpole.

He had one semi-arc shaped alloy ring on each of his two ears. This was an advanced multifunctional analysis device built by the dynasty. It had functions such as communication, detection, analysis, tactical imaging, and so on.

He wore a high-grade officer uniform of the Crimson Dynasty. It was black and decorated with red and gold patterns, and it had the dynasty's national emblem on the chest.

All the high-grade officer uniforms of the Crimson Dynasty were made from nano-cloth. They were light, tough, and had excellent defense capabilities. It was also equipped with many combat and survival functions.

"Colonel Teny, the radar has received a distress signal. The coordinates are T406.B189.K22, right on our path. According to long-range observation, a group of galactic travelers is being attacked by a galactic pirate group. The pirates have thirty low-grade battleships."

The exclusive deputy, Corbus, bowed and reported the situation.

"Send an area announcement. Warn them and tell them to leave our route immediately," Teny quickly said.

"... The announcement has been made. They have not responded."

Corbus looked at the image detected and said, "They have strengthened their attacks, intending to quickly finish the galactic traveling group."

"Report the situation to the main team. The rest of you... switch to combat formation. Level two alert. Initiate the long-range kiting strategy," Teny ordered calmly.

His mission was to scout the route and eliminate unstable factors. As an elite officer of the dynasty, he did not like to be involved in matters of the others. The galactic traveling group's rescue request was not within his consideration. However, these people happened to be blocking the hyperdrive route of the main team, which was why he commanded the fleet to engage.

The twelve recon battleships formed a fan shape and headed toward the galactic pirate. They started to fire as soon as they were in range.

Those galactic pirates attempted to fight back but to no avail. They could hardly land any attacks on the recon team. Under Teny's command, the recon team maintained their maximum attack range, which was far superior to the galactic pirates'.

Destroying a few enemy ships with ease, Teny switched strategy. He commanded the recon fleet to swiftly surround them while maintaining their distance.

Although he had fewer than half of the battleships the enemies had, Teny could always create opportunities where they outnumbered the enemy in partial battles.

Under his command, it was as if these galactic pirates were slowly being chipped away despite having the advantage in numbers.

Teny was used to fighting in large armies; commanding a small group in combat was not his strength, but he was still amazing at it.

His strategic style was as firm as a mountain, calm and slow like an adult toying with a child. No matter what those galactic pirates did, he countered them with ease.

The galactic pirate could not even find the opportunity to escape with hyperdrive. They were overwhelmingly beaten.

With the immeasurable difference in strategic capabilities and the large difference in spaceship performance, this battle lasted barely a moment before the galactic pirates were wiped out without surprise. Teny suffered basically zero damage, only some energy used to maintain shields.

"Tell the main team that the problem is solved," Teny said with a calm tone. Having witnessed so many large galactic battles, the battle earlier was not even a warmup.

"Colonel, the spaceships of this galactic traveling group are heavily damaged and can't support long-range travel. They have asked to board our ship." Corbus' voice was thunderous.

"Refuse them," Teny said without changing his expression. "Activate scanning probe and detect the individual energy level of the people inside this traveling group. If no abnormalities are found, release small cabins for them as carriers."

Teny was experienced in this. There were way too many examples of using distress signals as a trap in history. He was used to being alert against traps.

Even if no abnormality was found, he would not let outsiders board his battleship but would give the unoccupied small cabins to throw these stranded passengers to the nearest colonial planet. He would not waste time guarding and giving them a ride.

Corbus suddenly received a message. "Colonel, a person in these passengers wishes to speak to you. There's information about him in the database. He's the leader of a small financial group in the Shattered Star Ring. His history is clean. He said he knows Black Star."

"How does he know that we're going to meet with Black Star? This feels like a poorly planned trap." Teny raised his brows.

"That might be easily explainable." Corbus looked at the data, shaking his head. "The news about the dynasty forming an alliance with Black Star has spread widely in the Shattered Star Ring."

Teny thought for a moment and said, "Pick up the communication. I'll speak with him."

Usually, he would not bother about a request from an irrelevant person like this. However, that person had mentioned Black Star, which was a topic he had recently been very curious about.

Black Star was the dynasty's new ally, and Teny knew that he was on this trip to meet Black Star and accept modification from the Evolution Cube.

Be it friend or foe, he always would find out as much as he could about the person he would come in contact with.

This came from his military habit. He had already finished reading through Black Star's data on paper. More information about Han Xiao was exactly what he needed.

Du...

The communication connected. This leader of the financial group's face was filled with excitement and nervousness.

When attacked by the galactic pirate, he had thought that misfortune was about to fall. To his surprise, they were saved by the Crimson Dynasty. Having seen an opportunity to contact a Universal Civilization, he tried his luck to attract their attention and mentioned Black Star's name.

"How do you know Black Star?"

This person could not wait to reply. "More than ten years ago, I hired Black Star's mercenary group and had close contact with Black Star. This is all recorded."

"Okay, tell me from the start." Teny narrowed his eyes.

Even over there in the Central Galaxy, there was no example of such a quick rise. It could be said that Black Star had broken the record for the shortest time an ordinary person had become a Beyond Grade A Super.

Teny was very curious about this legendary person.

Furthermore, Black Star was a Mechanic just like him. Teny even had some thoughts about seeking guidance.

...

As Han Xiao returned from Planet Heber, he brought back the partnership intention of a ton of organizations. Sylvia became busy, negotiating and dealing with different organizations every day.

Luckily, she had the physique of a Calamity Grade. If it were an ordinary person, that person would probably pass away from overworking.

Sylvia was exceptionally hardworking, which Han Xiao was glad about. If his Managing Director was Jenny, she would probably sacrifice her own life to kill him by running into him carrying a psionic bomb.

Ames did not return to Floating Dragon but actively looked to walk along with Han Xiao.

It did not matter where they were going—it was mainly because she would have an old friend who was on her level to chat with. Furthermore, she felt that interesting things would always happen around Han Xiao.

The dynasty's elites were still on the way. Han Xiao decided to complete the evolution for Planet Aquamarine and the Black Spirit Race first.

Planet Aquamarine would need time to gather its citizens, which he had Bennett take care of. Han Xiao went to the Black Spirit Race first. The Black Spirit Race had their Mind Network, so they would be easier to gather.

...

Ever since the Black Spirit Race planted their roots on this unpopulated planet, the planet's name on the star map had officially changed to Planet Black Spirit.

Hu!

A spaceship penetrated the atmosphere and slowly landed. The gray and green surface expanded in his sight.

The radar showed the vital signal's source location. Han Xiao piloted the spaceship and headed to the Germinal Tribe's territory cave with familiarity.

There were no clouds in the sky.

Dashing past the surface mainly made of rocks and the sparse forest, an enormous pit appeared before his eyes.

This was a large open cave, and densely packed holes filled the cave walls. This was originally an underground cave. The Black Spirit Race had taken away the ground above them and exposed it.

Han Xiao had once taken a group of Black Spirit Race to mine resource planets. Impacted by the various cultures in the galaxy, the Black Spirit Race had started to learn about intelligence and civilizations.

As their Mind Network had a highly unified group conscience, knowledge spread extremely efficiently. In the past decade, the Black Spirit Race had tried to leave their beast habits behind and started learning to use tools, building caves above the ground.

This open cave also had some messy rock piles in it, which were actually prototypes of buildings. The Black Spirit Race had gradually come up to the surface from the underground. This place could be considered the basis of a city.

An enormous Prophecy Stone totem stood at the heart of the cave. It had been carved into a strange shape.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, trying to identify it for quite some time. Only then did he confirm that this statue with pieces of carapace, spikes all over its body, and sharp teeth in its mouth was supposed to be him.

Han Xiao did not know whether to laugh or cry. He could somehow recognize who this statue was supposed to represent despite all the 'add-ons' it had. The Black Spirit Race's rock carving technique was really unbelievable.

But their aesthetic senses...

The spaceship hovered above the cave. The Black Spirit Race of the Germinal Tribe all climbed out from their caves and looked up at the spaceship.

Han Xiao walked out of the hatch and slowly descended from the sky. The Black Spirit Race below all lowered their bodies as if they were worshipping.

Feidin released prophecy stones energy and let Han Xiao log into the Prophecy Stone group chat server.

As soon as Han Xiao entered the Black Spirit Race's Mind Network, countless voices sounded. The internal thoughts of every Black Spirit Race member became crystal clear.

"Such a powerful aura, it's beautiful."

"Black Star God, you've come to see me again."

Countless Black Spirit Race members spoke in the Mind Network, expressing their love and admiration for Han Xiao.

The Black Spirit Race referred to him as 'God'. His relationship with them had always been [Reverence].

The voice of the Germinal Tribe's leader sounded. "Black Star God, what do you need us to do?"

"I came this time to help you people evolve..." Han Xiao talked about the use of the Evolution Cube.

The Black Spirit Race was thrilled, mumbling strange prayers and feeling like this was a blessing from their god.

Through the Mind Network, all the Black Spirit Race members in this cave received the message almost instantly. They all moved and surrounded Han Xiao, kneeling with their front limbs on the ground in a respectful position. Their gathering speed was extremely quick.

"What a highly efficient race." Han Xiao could not help feeling that way.

He had always felt that the civilization potential of the Black Spirit Race was extraordinary.

Their natural Mind Network made them extremely unified and in sync. Any group activity would be astonishingly convenient.

The Mind Network could also share their knowledge and intelligence, so spreading knowledge was almost instant. The Black Spirit Race's one-hour long communication might achieve the effects of what would take some races decades and centuries.

Chapter 793: Golden Leek!

A small silver cube floated above the totem, gushing out black cloud-like energy.

Evolution energy spread in the nest, covering the Black Spirit Race one after another. In just a short time, the nest was already filled with black cocoons.

With a flash of Mechanical Force on Han Xiao's fingertips, the small silver-white cube obediently returned to his hand, and he wore it back on his neck.

Han Xiao nodded. "Now, I just have to wait. I wonder what the Black Spirit Race will evolve into."

Advanced civilizations more or less controlled secret technology that others could not replicate. The Evolution Cube was a relic of a civilization very close to becoming a Universal Civilization. The technological essence within it had long been lost. Even when it was in Psyker's hands, the Arcane Church could not understand it. Han Xiao had only tested the various parameters of the Evolution Cube.

There were comparatively fewer restrictions on this Universal Treasure. The Evolution Cube would absorb multi-dimensional and dark energy to charge up automatically. The method to use it over a large area was to cover an entire area with the Evolution Cube. That way, all the creatures within that area would be evolved.

This evolution energy was considered in the rage of Space Wonders—safe, no side effects, and exceeded all kinds of gene medicine and gene hormones. It was as if countless years of natural evolution were all concentrated in one individual.

After a short wait, a sudden clear and crisp sound appeared.

Ka-cha!

One black cocoon cracked open, showing the Black Spirit Race member inside.

The Black Spirit Race were originally black insects with strange appearances—they had hair between the gaps of their carapace, and their mouths were cone-shaped and could penetrate stone. They had no eyes, only four antennae that functioned as their sight organs. They had four muscular legs and a shovel-shaped tail covered in carapace. Basically, they looked like very vicious beasts.

Now, however, the appearance of the Black Spirit Race had drastically changed.

The proportion of their carapace and their muscle became much more balanced in a streamlined shape, much more aesthetic to the eyes. The hair in between the gaps on their carapace was all gone. They looked much neater.

The sharp fangs in their mouths became tidy. Two of the four antennae on their heads became longer and thicker, hanging on the back of their head like hair. The two antennae below disappeared and became bean-sized azure eyes. The antennae were previously organs to help them to adapt to living underground, but now the Black Spirit Race had started to get used to sunlight and were trying to live above ground. Originally, it would take many years for them to slowly develop and evolve into having eyes. However, the Evolution Cube had drastically reduced this process.

The Black Spirit Race still used four feet, but their two back feet became much more muscular as if they could easily stand up.

Kaching!

With the first Black Spirit Race completing its evolution, it seemed to start a chain reaction. Tons of black cocoons started to shatter. The brand new-looking Black Spirit Race appeared and looked around with confusion.

The surprise of the Black Spirit Race spread quickly in the Mind Network. To Han Xiao, these internal thoughts sounded as young as the voices of a child.

"Wha—What is this feeling?"

"I can see so clearly. Is this what sight is?"

"The sun is so blinding..."

Having gained normal sight for the first time, countless Black Spirit Race members felt curious and adapted to their new organ.

Han Xiao suddenly realized—the biggest change that the Black Spirit Race had undergone was not their appearances but their minds. They were born with connective minds, which meant that the Black Spirit Race had a very high talent in that area. Now, that talent was amplified... The most direct impact was that the brains of the Black Spirit Race became much more developed.

This time, a clear voice appeared in Han Xiao's mind, which shocked him a little. This voice did not come from the Prophecy Stone group chat server but was a voice sent to him through direct psychic communication.

"Black Star God, we will remember the blessing you've granted upon us forever."

Han Xiao looked over and saw that the Germinal Tribe leader was noticeably larger than the normal Black Spirit Race members and was staring at him with his bean-sized eyes. The voice came from him.

"You can use psychic power?" Han Xiao wondered.

The Prophecy Stone was the base station of the Black Spirit Race's Mind Network. Without it, the Black Spirit Race could not previously connect their minds. Now, however, the Germinal Tribe leader was able to transmit his voice without the help of the Prophecy Stones. This had exceptional meanings.

"I don't know. I just felt that I could suddenly do it. I seem to be able to do this too." The Germinal Tribe leader shook his head and suddenly picked up a small Prophecy Stone, bit it, and swallowed it. Right after, a circle of invisible energy spread from his head.

Feidin was slightly shocked. "Such special energy, there are traces of the Prophecy Stone in it..."

The next moment, the Germinal Tribe leader's psychic energy formed a new Mind Network and turned him into a chat server. He had undergone some kind of positive mutation during the evolution, which tremendously stimulated his psychic talent. There were dozens more mutants just like him.

Han Xiao was surprised. Every complete Prophecy Stone was equivalent to an individual Mind Network server. Only the Black Spirit Race members in the same server could communicate with each other. Now, however, some mutants had become able to create their own servers, once again increasing the mobility and unity of this race.

This had extraordinary meanings to a race. With their race-specific talent enhanced, they would be able to adapt to more environments.

With such high potential, maybe this race can really grow into a powerful civilization in the future.

That was how Han Xiao sincerely felt.

He was truly glad that he had kept the Black Spirit Race alive back then. Han Xiao had a feeling that this insignificant investment of his might yield more profit than he had ever expected.

After bidding farewell to the Germinal Tribe, Han Xiao did the same for the other tribes one after another.

As the Black Spirit Race had migrated as an entire race back then, although the various tribes lived separately throughout the years, they were still relatively close in terms of distance. So, it did not take too much time.

Han Xiao had gifted them the evolution opportunity, so the Black Spirit Race felt gratitude toward this 'god' of theirs from the depths of their hearts. Their belief became more deeply rooted, and they believed that they were a race blessed by God.

After Han Xiao left in the spaceship, all the tribes started to sculpt new wall paintings—of a small man representing Han Xiao floating above the ground, worshipped by the Black Spirit Race under him.

This day was forever recorded in the Black Spirit Race's history.

...

Completing the Black Spirit Race's evolution had taken less time than Han Xiao expected. He took his time looking for Fixed Stars to train Heber's Energy Training Technique on the way and finally arrived at Planet Aquamarine.

"Welcome home."

At the dock, Bennett looked at Han Xiao as he walked down the spaceship, smiling with the joy of reuniting with an old friend.

Home...

Han Xiao's thoughts drifted away for an instant before he suppressed the sudden surge of some kind of emotion and sized Bennett up.

Bennett still stood as straight as he always had, and his white hair was neatly combed.

Behind Bennett were a ton of officers that looked like they were filled with nervousness and panic. When facing Black Star, their protector, only Bennett could remain casual. Everyone else was overwhelmed by the pressure.

Black Star's 'wiping away nations with a few words' deed had only been a few years ago. The example of the Six Nations was still crystal clear in the minds of these people. They could not control their anxiety when facing someone who could decide the life or death of their entire government with a few words.

However, the impact of what Black Star had done back then had already shown throughout the past years. From the perspective of an entire civilization, uniting the government was indeed beneficial. It drastically reduced internal conflict, and making decisions was much more efficient. Had they entered the galactic society with multiple governments, they would have ended up like the Luhan Beastmen.

"You look well." Han Xiao nodded. He then looked at the small boy beside Bennett.

Nero looked up and stared at Han Xiao with curiosity.

He had seen Han Xiao countless times in textbooks. He even memorized his deeds before. However, this was the first time that he had seen him in person.

"God—Godfather," Nero stuttered with a shy tone.

"Good boy." Han Xiao smiled. He then lowered his waist and picked Nero up, firmly holding him in his arms and tapping Nero's forehead.

Nero was Bennett's child. Bennett had decided to stay and guard Planet Aquamarine and given his child to Han Xiao to take care of. Of course, he was willing to take care of an old friend's child.

Nero had initially been a little nervous because of how high Han Xiao's position was, but Han Xiao was very friendly and warm to him, so he became relaxed in no time and laughed joyfully.

"This toy is for you." Han Xiao casually waved. Nanoparticles flew out from his shirt and quickly turned into a black and gold hovering guard flying around Nero.

This was high-level Orange equipment; its energy core was a stable dark energy reaction furnace. It had both offensive and defensive abilities and multiple other functions.

A bright blue and gold electric spark lit up on Han Xiao's palm and flew into the floating guard. He gave this machine permanent [Emperor's Gift] and [Machinery Fusion] blessings, giving it increased capability.

"This Hovering Guard is a gift for you to protect yourself. You can give it a name."

Then, with a snap of Han Xiao's finger, he created a nano-level nerves connection device and planted it into the back of Nero's head without him feeling any pain. He added, "It can move with your thoughts. However, this thing is very powerful. You'd better not use it recklessly, especially not to hit your father."

An orange equipment made by a Beyond Grade A Super was extremely powerful. Even without his Mechanical Force bonuses, this hovering guard alone would be able to easily defeat any Grade C Supers. This type of machine had no level limit. It was basically god-tier equipment to low-level Supers. He did not even sell this to the players.

Nero tried to control the hovering guard. With a thought, the hovering guard followed his commands and moved around smoothly as if it was his own body. Nero's eyes sparkled immediately as if he had discovered a new continent.

"Thanks, godfather!" With a face full of surprise, Nero hugged Han Xiao's neck and expressed his excitement.

"Go play." Han Xiao chuckled, put Nero down, and turned around to head to the political building with Bennett.

On the way, Bennett started to report the situation.

"I've announced gathering orders in the various cities. It's almost done. There's nothing I can do to those we've missed."

He had explained the situation about the Evolution Cube to the people of Planet Aquamarine. Those who wanted to evolve would gather on their own. This would save a lot of time.

However, some people were unwilling to gather due to various reasons.

"Let them be. I'm not forcing everyone to accept the evolution." Han Xiao shook his head. "By the way, I'll let you use it first."

Bennett smiled bitterly and said, "I don't actually want to use it..."

"You're different." Han Xiao waved his hands. "This is an evolution involving an entire civilization. Don't you want to experience it for your people beforehand so that you have nothing to worry about?"

Bennett shook his head with resignation and did not oppose it.

"By the way, Nero too..." Han Xiao paused. "Let me take him into the galaxy. I'll help him become a Super."

"Isn't he too young?" Bennett hesitated.

"The earlier he becomes a Super, the better. Since you're planning to let Nero live his life in the universe in the future, it's best to let him get used to that life as early as possible. Plus, there's me. What do you have to worry about? He's my godson. I'll take him to travel for a few months in the universe before bringing him back."

"Sigh, alright then." Bennett was initially hesitant, but he nodded in the end. He decided to stay and guard his mother planet, but he did not want to limit Nero's future because of his own reasons.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something.

He thought about seeing Nero's attributes.

He turned and looked behind. Nero was following behind them and playing with his new toy.

Han Xiao secretly released a tiny bit of Mechanical Force, turning nanoparticles into a metal needle invisible to the naked eye. He remotely controlled it and stabbed Nero's butt.

"Ow!" Nero felt a pain on his butt and yelled with shock. He looked around hastily but did not notice anything.

As this dealt 1 damage to Nero, combat information appeared on the interface, and Nero's attributes were fully listed in Han Xiao's eyes.

Han Xiao scanned through. Suddenly, a tint of shock flashed past his eyes.

Nero was still an ordinary child, so his attributes were basically empty. However, under the list of talents, there was a bright and shining list that shocked even Han Xiao.

The Molding Talent—[Advanced Luck Glow]!

Thi—This is Feidin's level of Luck Glow. This kid is a high-level protagonist character‽ Han Xiao was so in disbelief he almost wanted to rub his eyes.

In his previous life, Bennett's life had been completely different, and Nero did not even exist.

Bennett had Basic Luck Glow, and his son had Advanced Luck Glow. What are the chances of that? Did this thing run in their blood‽

This time, a daring speculation appeared in his mind.

Could it be that... Nero's Advanced Luck Glow has something to do with me?

Come to think about it, Nero's dad is the Aquamarine Federation's leader, his godfather is Black Star, who's known across the entire galaxy, and he will receive personal mentorship from a Beyond Grade A at a young age! Isn't that exactly extraordinary luck‽

Han Xiao had no idea that such a high-quality leek would come to grow in his own leek field. He was so surprised that even the way he looked at Nero changed.

Although Nero was just a kid, in Han Xiao's eyes, this kid had become a treasure overflowing with luck.

If he had decided to take care of Nero because of personal reasons before, he now truly wanted to train this potential stock!

For a high-level protagonist-type character, he would at least become a Calamity Grade in the future!

What a pleasant surprise...

Han Xiao was thrilled.

Chapter 794: The 'True Protagonist'

The first group to accept the evolution from the Evolution Cube the next day were the residents of the capital, Black Star City.

The spaceship with Han Xiao and Bennett and the others in it slowly passed from above the city. The energy released from the Evolution Cube covered the people below.

"Maybe this will be a new chapter for the Planet Aquamarine civilization." Bennett could not help but feel that way when looking at this.

He had already undergone the evolution the previous night and felt the effects of the Evolution Cube clearly. It was as if he had returned to his peak in his younger years. His body felt energetic, and his mind worked much faster. The enhancement the Evolution Cube provided to ordinary people was focused on strengthening their mind.

Turning to look at Han Xiao's back, Bennett had a lot of thoughts in his mind. Planet Aquamarine had been able to achieve the era it had all thanks to this old friend of his.

Twenty years ago, who would have thought that a traitor of the Germinal Organization could ever reach such an unbelievable height?

Galactic spaceships would take no time to go around a planet. Very soon, the process was completed.

Han Xiao did not pay attention to how overjoyed the people were. Bennett would take care of the aftermath. He would definitely promote what he had done and might even include this in the textbooks.

As Han Xiao was done with this task, he did not want to stay much longer on Planet Aquamarine and wanted to leave immediately. He got a message from Sylvia that the Crimson Dynasty's team were about to arrive at the Black Star Army headquarters, so he had to return.

As the spaceship returned to the dock, a gentle woman waited there, holding Nero's hand.

Bennett brought his officers to the dock, shared a few words with the woman, and pushed Nero's back a little, signaling for him to board the ship.

"Go, your future is in the galaxy. Black Star will take care of you," Bennett said slowly.

Nero's eyes were red. He had found out that he would be following his godfather into the universe the night before, and he almost thought that his daddy did not want him anymore. He cried and cried, and only after Bennett talked and explained it to him for very long did he accept this.

He had only read about the galactic society in textbooks and on the internet; this was his first time entering the galaxy. Thinking about those weird-looking aliens that existed in the universe, he was both afraid and secretly looking forward to it.

Nero climbed up the gangway tiredly with his tiny legs. Han Xiao stood beside the hatch and pulled him in.

Han Xiao exchanged looks with Bennett, and they both nodded at each other.

"Shut the gate," Han Xiao ordered.

Whoosh.

The hatch closed slowly. Nero looked around. Through the gradually shrinking gap of the gate, he saw that Bennett and his mother were standing on the docks, waving goodbye to him.

Ka-cha.

The last gap disappeared. The hatch shut tightly as if separating the two worlds.

"Follow me."

Han Xiao shook his head and brought Nero to the cockpit of the spaceship.

Through the porthole, Nero saw the city quickly shrinking below his feet and the sky above him turning from blue to black.

The spaceship trembled slightly and left the planet's atmosphere. The full look of Planet Aquamarine appeared in Nero's eyes. He stared at it with his eyes and mouth wide open. This experience was too marvelous for a kid like him.

He tightly grabbed Han Xiao's legs—this was the only support his tiny heart currently had.

Han Xiao stood beside him with a smile and did not move. After the spaceship entered hyperdrive, he brought Nero out of the cockpit and toured the entire spaceship while teaching him the general knowledge of the galaxy.

"These are the things you need to remember. Don't worry. With me here, most people in the universe won't be able to hurt you."

The two of them came to the hall. Ames, Hila, and the rest of the Black Star Guards were chatting casually. When they saw Nero, they all took turns to tease him with friendly and loving looks on their faces. They all quite liked this cute and obedient kid. Even Hila suppressed her cold aura, and her eyes looked gentler.

"So this is Uncle Bennett's kid." Aurora hugged Nero in her arms and could not let go. Originally, she was the youngest there, but now there was finally an even younger one. She was overjoyed. Furthermore, this was the kid of someone she knew.

Nero's face blushed completely. He stood in place stiffly and did not dare move.

Han Xiao could not help but pull Aurora away and say with resignation, "Stop hugging him. Do you want to suffocate him?"

Looking down, Aurora slightly blushed. She snorted softly and heavily bashed Han Xiao's waist, which, of course, was just a tickle to him.

"By the way, Uncle Han Xiao gave you a gift. I shall give you one too." Aurora's eyes suddenly brightened. She extended her palm, and a clump of golden energy appeared in her hands. She pressed it into Nero's chest.

"Wha—What is this?" Nero was shocked. Then, he suddenly felt a sense of warmth and comfort all over his body, as if an infinite amount of strength was suddenly born inside him.

He touched his chest confusingly as if he could not understand how that clump of golden energy entered his body.

Aurora blinked and proudly said, "This is my Esper Ability. I gave you some concentrated vital energy, which will make you never sick and continuously vitalize your cells. Your body will gradually be enhanced, and you'll be even taller and stronger."

Not only could her Esper Ability heal people, but it could also give people buffs and stimulate the growth of beings.

For example, that fatty white bear who stayed in the Black Star headquarters and did nothing became a powerful individual after absorbing vital energy while being near Aurora for a long time. In more specific terms, Aurora's vital energy could give someone stronger attributes.

Seeing this, Hila, who rarely talked, spoke up. "Then I'll give you a present, too."

She snapped her fingers and shot out a red energy bullet, hitting Nero's back of his hand.

"Ah!" Nero suddenly felt a burning sensation on the back of his hand. He yelled with pain and rubbed his hand with droplets of tears in his eyes.

He looked down and saw a bright red pattern on the back of his hand that extended to his wrist, like a tattoo.

"This is a Dead Spirit Mark. For every creature you kill, this mark will absorb its remaining soul and enhance your psychic power." Hila's tone was casual and normal.

Although it was not really appropriate to mention murder to a kid, the people there were all used to it. Almost everyone there was a Calamity Grade who had killed hundreds of thousands, so they were not keen on painting 'the world is a fairy tale' image to a kid. Furthermore, since Nero would be guided by Black Star, he would definitely not be ordinary in the future. Therefore, they did not avoid this topic.

Nero was a little scared. He carefully pulled his sleeve and tried to cover the tattoo.

"Then I'll give you something too." Feidin smiled. His overflowing friendliness made Nero feel relaxed immediately.

Feidin released a wave of invisible psychic energy into Nero's mind, forming a Calamity Grade psychic barrier, preventing others from hurting him through psychic means.

The various other Black Star Guards were not petty and took out things to gift to Nero one after another. Although they were not worth much in the eyes of Calamity Grades, every single one of them could be considered a treasure in the eyes of lower-level Supers.

Looking at this, Han Xiao felt a sense of familiarity.

Why does this... look so familiar?

Isn't Nero exactly one of those types of blessed protagonist type characters who is loved by a bunch of old men from a young age‽

So, it's this type of Advanced Luck Glow, Han Xiao thought it was funny. Having received so many treasures, this kid's path ahead is wide and bright.

Lastly, it was Hadavy's turn. He searched his body and realized that there was not anything that was worth gifting.

Seeing that everyone was staring at him, he thought for a moment and took out a set of Wayne Cards from his pocket with a chuckle.

"How about I teach you to play cards?"

"Piss off!"

Bang!

Han Xiao moved like lightning and instantly kicked Hadavy onto the ground. Nanoparticles turned into cuffs and tied him up tightly.

Nero was startled and backed off hastily while the other Black Star Guards looked around as if the environment outside was marvelous.

"Hmm..." Hadavy's mouth was sealed by alloy. Not a single muscle on his body could move, leaving only his eyes moving around frantically.

"Stay on the ground and reflect!" Han Xiao was furious.

Teaching someone Wayne Cards is an unforgivable sin!

Never mind the fact that you're not giving my golden leek fertilizer, how dare you poisoning it‽

Do you want my golden leek to walk Herlous' path and fall deep into the abyss of achieving nothing‽

Ames caressed her chin and looked at this with a light smile on her face. Suddenly, she waved and signaled Nero to come over.

Nero obediently walked over to Ames. He was a little nervous. Although Ames looked just as friendly as everyone else, she felt very different from the other Black Star Guards to him. It was as if she possessed a unique sense of nobility. In front of her, Nero subconsciously felt restrained.

"Don't be nervous. I'll give you something too."

Ames smiled lightly. Suddenly, she took off the obsidian necklace on her neck and placed it into Nero's hands.

Han Xiao was a little surprised. This necklace did not have any special functions. It was just an ordinary accessory. However, Ames always wore it. Han Xiao wondered what story it had.

"Take care of it," Ames said with a light smile, not planning to explain the meaning of it. Then she faintly glanced at Han Xiao.

Nero hastily nodded and carefully pocketed the necklace.

After all the 'old men' finished sending their gifts, Han Xiao called Nero over and said with a smile, "I promised your father to raise you to be a powerful Super. You've definitely learned about Supers in school on Planet Aquamarine. Do you still remember how many types of Supers there are, right?"

"Yes." Nero nodded heavily. Then counting with his fingers, he said, "There are five—Psychic, Esper, Mechanic, Mage, and Psychic!"

"Now, it's your time to choose. What kind of Super do you want to be?" Han Xiao asked with a smile.

He did not know what kind of Super talent Nero had, so he asked him directly.

Everyone became quiet.

Choosing a Super system was the decision of a lifetime. Black Star seemed to want to strongly raise and teach Nero, so his choice was very important.

Nero hesitated for a while and looked up at the hovering guard flowing above him. His eyes became firm.

"Godfather, I want to be a Mechanic!"

"Haha, good choice!"

Han Xiao was overjoyed. Since Nero had chosen the Mechanic class, he would rightfully become his student. In the Shattered Star Ring, he was the peak of the Mechanic class. No one was more qualified than him to teach others.

Hearing that, many Black Star Guards secretly sighed.

Alas, why did you choose not to live like a human being?

Han Xiao activated Nero's Mechanical Force right on the ship. With his current strength, the method used to activate Mechanical Force in others was no longer the 'electric chair' that Sylvia had once experienced. It became safer and painless.

Planet Aquamarine was very close to the Black Star Army's headquarters. Han Xiao and the others returned not long after.

One day after, the Crimson Dynasty's transport team finally arrived.

The enormous fleet shrouded the sky. It was as if an eclipse was happening on Planet Golden Gate.

The army's headquarters became more boisterous.

The first batch of resources given by the Crimson Dynasty was unloaded and transported into the army's warehouse.

The first batch of dynasty elites to accept evolution also stepped onto the Black Star Army headquarters' docks.

There were four captains, representing elite members of their own faction respectively. Teny was one of the captains. He represented the dynasty military's Youngsters Faction.

These elites followed the army's receptionist into the hall, looking straight ahead all the way.

Upon arriving in the hall, the elites of the dynasty saw Han Xiao, who was waiting on his throne, immediately.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

Pa!

The tens of thousands of dynasty elites did a dynasty military greeting simultaneously and instantly. Their boots stomped the metal ground and made a crisp, loud sound.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. He walked down from the throne. The four captains stepped out of their formation and came to shake hands with Han Xiao one after another.

These four were all renowned NPCs in the previous life, among whom, Teny was the most famous. Almost no one in the Crimson Dynasty Faction did not know this renowned dynasty marshal. This was also the person whom Han Xiao paid the most attention to.

Compared to his appearance in Han Xiao's previous life, Teny was still very young. He gave off a very sharp, energetic vibe.

When it was time to shake Teny's hand, Han Xiao stared closely at his face and suddenly gave a mysterious smile.

"Teny Amenos, I've heard a lot about you."

Teny was stunned.

Black Star did not say anything when shaking the others' hands. Why did he just speak to me?

Heard a lot about me... has my name already spread to the Shattered Star Ring?

Then, the intelligence he had collected in the past few days flashed through his mind. A few days ago, he had discovered one of Black Star's abilities from this data.

This person has some kind of foresight ability.

There's definitely a reason for him to only speak with me!

This thought flashed through Teny's mind, but his face did not express any change. He shook Han Xiao's hand firmly and let it go.

Chapter 795: Goal

The dynasty's elite soldiers were always quick and direct. The four of them briefly explained themselves. They did not request to rest and immediately asked to accept the Evolution Cube modification.

Han Xiao agreed. He would have more than enough time to communicate with them after that.

Buzz!

With a flash of blue and gold Mechanical Force, a small silver cube hovered above his head. He activated it with the password. The evolution energy flew out instantly and spread in the hall like a tsunami, shrouding the tens of thousands of dynasty elites.

Han Xiao deactivated the Evolution Cube, looked at the black cocoons all over the hall, and nodded with satisfaction.

He then looked at Teny's cocoon, smiled slightly, and thought, Since you came to my doorsteps, how can I not invest in you?

It could be said that he was extremely familiar with this future dynasty marshal. He was one of the renowned NPCs of the dynasty that existed through multiple versions.

In the later days, he led many large fleets of the dynasty alone and called them the 'Dynasty's Iron Hoofs', which fought many legendary battles. His performance was exceptional throughout many versions. The players under the Dynasty Faction could choose to join under his command and become his soldiers or officers, where they would receive plenty of War Missions.

There were two things that Teny was best known for. One was during the [Calamity of the Supers], where he led the fleet under his command and killed a notorious Beyond Grade A without any help!

The other was during the World Tree Civilization invasion event. For the sake of the entire war, he put his own life on the line and led his troops to charge into hundreds of Star Systems, restraining the enemy's overwhelming invasion. He penetrated countless lines of defenses and entered the heartland of the World Tree Civilization, earning a ton of time. In the end, his troops were wiped out by the enemies. Dragging alongside countless strong enemies, he was killed in battle and met a tragic end.

Teny was just a Calamity Grade.

He was an extremely strong commander, strategist, and leader of fleets. The dynasty's fleets could achieve astonishing strength in his hands. To the dynasty, such a military talent like him was even more important than Beyond Grade As.

According to his life's direction, in the future, Teny Amenos would obtain a very high position in the dynasty and have masses of soldiers under his command. Since an opportunity to build a relationship with the dynasty's future military boss was right before him, Han Xiao was not going to let it go.

There were many factions in the dynasty. The first group of dynasty elites was selected from the various factions. The Military Youngsters Faction, which Teny represented, was a very strong faction, and he would become one of the faction's representatives in the future. He was worth Han Xiao wooing.

Han Xiao knew his place. Although he had become the Crimson Dynasty's ally, it was just the beginning and far from being carefree. Even as an ally, he had to think of ways to increase his influence within the dynasty. After all, he was not the only Beyond Grade A in the dynasty.

I've operated in more than twenty years in the Shattered Star Ring, so I'm considered quite important. In the Central Galaxy, however, there are more Beyond Grade As. Plus, many of them are seniors that have lived many years. I have limited influence over there, Han Xiao thought.

Universal Civilizations had many powerful individuals and allies. Their profit network was complicated and broad. Although he had some power within the dynasty, it was pathetically little, and this included the bonus from the Evolution Cube.

The other three captains beside Teny were also known characters whom Han Xiao was familiar with. They did not achieve as much as Teny would eventually, but since they were all leeks right at his doorstep, he decided to not let any of them go.

The evolution lasted about half a day. The tens of thousands of dynasty elites came out of their cocoons one after another.

Teny was the last to complete the evolution. He extended his hand and clenched his fists, familiarizing himself with the changes in his body.

"This feels amazing..." His deputy, Corbus, was overjoyed. He was not initially qualified enough to be selected, but because he was Teny's deputy, he was able to obtain this opportunity.

"It's indeed magical. It feels even better than the Federation of Light's Gene Adjustment." Teny nodded firmly.

All the newborns of the Universal Civilizations would usually experience free Gene Adjustment right after their birth to increase their potential.

Federation of Light's Gene Adjustment technology far exceeded the other two Universal Civilizations' as it was one of their specialties. Federation of Light's Super ratio was the highest in the entire Galaxy.

The army's officer who had been waiting at the side walked over and said, "Friends from the Crimson Dynasty, the Army Commander told me to wait here for you to complete your evolution. I will now take you to the army's guest area to rest."

The people nodded. Some of them would be following the dynasty's main logistics team to go to the Flickering World and explore, which planned to rest for some time in the Black Star Army headquarters. Therefore, they would be waiting there.

The rest of the dynasty elites were there purely for the evolution and would return to the Central Galaxy after it was done. Teny was one of them. Han Xiao would be traveling with them as well, and Zoel had already told them about it. Therefore, they would be staying in the army's headquarters and waiting for Han Xiao to head to the Central Galaxy together.

They came to the guest room area and settled down. Not long after, Han Xiao came. Teny and the other captains went to welcome him.

The first thing Han Xiao asked about was how they felt after the evolution. He then moved the topic onto the situation within the dynasty and started to chat casually.

The elites from the Crimson Dynasty were indeed different. Maybe because they had met many Beyond Grade As since they were officers of a Universal Civilization, their attitudes were very natural. They were neither nervous nor arrogant, just chatting with Han Xiao normally.

Han Xiao's goal was to improve his relationship with these people who would have high positions in the dynasty in the future so that it would be easier to become friends with them later.

He knew a lot about the people present. The chat was going very pleasantly.

However, Han Xiao noticed that Teny was the calmest and kept observing him. It seemed he was a little wary against him.

Han Xiao did not speak too much in their first conversation. He stood up and left after briefly familiarizing himself with the others. Making non-profit focused friends took time. It would only achieve the opposite effect if he was too hasty.

After sending Black Star away, Teny looked at his back and pondered.

What's with this guy?

"Teny seems wary of me. This doesn't seem easy..."

After returning to his office, Han Xiao tapped the table and contemplated it.

It was indeed not easy to bond with someone so talented. He had to focus on Teny's likings.

Han Xiao nodded—this was his advantage. He knew about Teny's likings. This was all hidden intelligence dug out by the players in his previous life after countless wrong attempts. He wondered how many strange and weird gifts Teny had received throughout those years.

"He doesn't have much fondness for many material possessions; he only likes special types of gifts. Hmm, I think he has a hobby to collect Star Core samples? If I remember correctly, he also likes reading mechanical theory books written by high-level Mechanics... Sigh, even the hobbies of outstanding people are high class."

Han Xiao shook his head. Since Teny had such a specific preference, even if he wanted to give him any gifts, it had to be subtle. Otherwise, it would expose the fact that he had a motive and would make Teny think that he had researched him, which would only achieve the opposite effect.

"Mechanical theory books..." Han Xiao murmured. "I'm a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, so he might even ask about it."

He put this at the back of his mind for the time being and called the Hila sisters, who were taking Nero around headquarters. He then called Reynold there as well.

Not long after, Reynold opened the door.

"Army Commander, were you looking for me?"

"I have a mission for you."

Then, he turned to look at Nero, whose face was filled with curiosity about the alien, smiled, and said, "Nero, you will be learning mechanical theories from Reynold for the time being. I have some business to do outside. I'll teach you myself after it's done."

Nero was suddenly worried and said with an indignant tone, "But you promised to bring me to travel the universe..."

The universe was a completely unknown environment to him. The only person he could rely on was Han Xiao. When he heard that he was going to be left in the army's headquarters, he instantly panicked.

This reminded him of his father, Bennett. He promised to take him to play time after time, but he always used work as an excuse to disappoint him again and again. In his limited view of the world, adults never kept their promises. He was afraid that Han Xiao would do the same.

"Don't worry, after I come back, I will definitely take you to somewhere fun..." Han Xiao comforted him.

There were many strong people in the Central Galaxy. Even he did not know what he would face. Nero was way too weak; it would be dangerous for him to follow Han Xiao. With so many officers and allies, Nero would be safer in the army headquarters.

Furthermore, Nero had just awoken his Mechanical Force and needed to learn a ton of theories—he would have to do homework anyway, so where he did that homework made no difference.

Giving Nero to Reynold to teach temporarily was also a decision made after thorough consideration. In the time that Nero spent learning the basics from Reynold, his Advanced Luck Glow might give him this guy's Perfect Mechanical Sense. After all, Nero was a high-level protagonist character, so everything was possible.

"No problem, leave it to me." Reynold nodded.

Han Xiao paused and suddenly thought of something. "By the way, is your sister still in the army?"

"Hmm?" Reynold was confused for a moment. "She is, why?"

It seemed that Rossellin had yet to leave with those three guys. Han Xiao caressed his chin. Rossellin and he were the only ones that knew about that; even Reynold did not.

"Then, what has she been doing recently? Has she done anything abnormal?"

"Abnormal... it seems so." Reynold thought about it. "I realized that she hasn't been going out much recently and has been spending a lot of time in her room doing who knows what. She hasn't been coming to chat with me recently. I've asked her a few times. She said that she's writing something, but I don't know what that is. Do you need me to ask her for you?"

"No need." Han Xiao waved his hands. He could roughly guess what Rossellin was writing—probably the plan for the Silver Revolutionary Army.

Although the goal of these founders was to overthrow the three Universal Civilizations, give other civilizations a chance, and help one ruler overthrow another, there was no way they could use these words to convince ordinary people, and they knew that full well. Rossellin was the spiritual leader; she wrote most of their slogans and beliefs and used her Esper Ability on those ideas.

He was not intending to interfere with the birth of the Silver Revolutionary Army because this would be a choice of the era. He alone would never be able to stop the windmill of an entire era. In conclusion, this storyline would be the first time that various advanced civilizations would work together to challenge the ruling position of the three universal civilizations, ever since the start of the exploration era and the countless years of peace. No civilization was willing to be ruled forever. When ambition and strength reached a certain threshold at the same time, the new and the old would clash. It was unavoidable.

Therefore, he might as well watch it happen and let the people he knew about climb up in position. This way, he would at least have an advantage, and it would be easier than dealing with the people he was unfamiliar with.

Han Xiao casually grabbed the aggrieved Nero and put him onto his knees. He then called Sylvia and Herlous.

"I'll be going to the Central Galaxy in a few days. Are the manpower, battleships, and resources I've asked you to prepare ready?"

They nodded.

"Good." Han Xiao exhaled.

This trip to the Central Galaxy was not sightseeing. He had many things to do.

Speaking of which, this was his first time leaving the Shattered Star Ring and heading to another Star Field in this life.

Chapter 796: Plan

The main goal of heading to the Central Galaxy this time was to meet the upper echelons of the dynasty and enter the dynasty allies circle. Then, he would officially step into the Central Galaxy stage and be known in the heart of the universe.

Other than that, Han Xiao had two more important goals.

One was to try to obtain Ultimate Knowledge from the dynasty during this trip.

The dynasty had generously given him all the Mechanic class Cutting-Edge Knowledges, but Ultimate Knowledges were much more valuable. Even Beyond Grade A allies would have to make some contributions before getting rewarded with it. The dynasty was generous to give him all the Cutting-Edge Knowledge at once, but keeping the Ultimate Knowledges back was a rule.

Resources were not given completely free to the Beyond Grade A allies of Universal Civilizations. Han Xiao estimated that he would only be able to request Ultimate Knowledge after he finished exploring the Flickering World. However, he wanted to go to the Central Galaxy and see if he could get it in advance.

Due to the EXP penalty he received from the Evolution Cube, his strength growth was paused. Han Xiao planned to look for other ways to become stronger like the other Beyond Grade As.

Other than talents, blueprints, and abilities, there was only class knowledge left. Ultimate Knowledges could make anyone from any class tremendously stronger.

Currently, the highest-level knowledge he had was only Cutting-Edge Knowledges. His [King's Mentor] required Ultimate Knowledge to be activated.

Another goal was to grow new leek fields.

Only some of the players were in the Shattered Star Ring; there were a lot of players in the other Star Fields. In the past, due to how far the distance was and how the army was not strong enough, Han Xiao could not reach them.

Now that there was a chance to borrow the Crimson Dynasty's military inter-Star Field channel, he could bring some people to the dynasty's territory to grow new leek fields.

This way, the fame within the players he had been accumulating throughout the last three versions would be of use. The name of The Black Star Army was attractive to the players of the other Star Fields too, and the players of the Shattered Star Ring were the best examples.

He might be able to bring some of the Central Galaxy players back.

Han Xiao smirked.

"This trip might take about two to three months, but I will return in time for the official exploration of the Flickering World. During this time, I will leave the matters of the army to you guys."

"It's thanks to you bringing back so many Shattered Star Ring allies that our partners are spread all across this Star Field," Sylvia said with a serious face. "The expansion of the army is almost complete. We will be able to stabilize as long as we follow the plan. You don't have to worry."

"I'm not worried when you guys are taking care of it." Han Xiao nodded with a smile.

The Black Star Army had officially become a Beyond Grade A organization and was now a giant in the Shattered Star Ring. According to the planned blueprint, it would continuously build more than ten thousand bases that would be spread across the various Star Clusters and Star Systems in the Shattered Star Ring.

The expansion of business was going very smoothly too. Through the channels provided by the partners from various industries, the Black Star Army had officially stepped into the various business industries. They were now involved in financial group trading, intelligence dealing, tourism transportation, mercenary production, and many more. Of course, most core businesses were still mercenary requests, resources mining, and armed alliance businesses. These three were the pillars of the army.

Among all the business models, the only one that was not replicable was the profits brought by the Evolution Cube. There was only one Evolution Cube, so it rightfully became the specialty of the Black Star Army. This was also the reason that the Black Star Army's expansion was going so smoothly.

The Evolution Cube was accessible for the army members as well. They just had to exchange for the right to use it with Contribution Points. This was also how the army was able to attract many more newcomers than it had estimated, building the fundamentals for the army's large-scale expansion.

As the Tyrant had ceased fire and Psyker had admitted his loss, no organization in this area could threaten the army's position.

It could be said that the Shattered Star Ring had become the Black Star Army's headquarters. The army had built a strong and firm base there. The next step was to open new markets.

"I will bring some Black Star Guards with me. Vice Commander Lagi will be responsible for the high-level combatants here. Don't let him slack..."

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and added, "Also, announce to the entire army that I've been invited to the Crimson Dynasty."

"No problem." Sylvia did not ask why.

Since he was going to open new leek fields, Han Xiao did not plan to not use the players' information channel. He wanted to spread this news through the forums and let the players over there in the Central Galaxy be mentally prepared beforehand.

Han Xiao was not worried about someone messing with his headquarters after he left. The Tyrant had become his ally on paper, and they had agreed to a ceasefire, so causing trouble would not be beneficial to Heber at all.

Psyker was temporarily lying low as well. Through getting a seat for the Planet Aquamarine in the Civilization Conference, Han Xiao had given Planet Aquamarine political protection. If Psyker did something to the army while he was not present, it would be a law-breaking act. Furthermore, Psyker still had his race behind him, so he would not do anything rash.

The Evolution Cube was on Han Xiao at all times. If someone wanted to get it, they could only snatch it from him. Therefore, attacking the Black Star Army was meaningless. This applied to EsGod as well.

Han Xiao was even less worried about enemies below Beyond Grade A causing trouble—with so many Calamity Grade officers in the army, anyone who dared look for trouble would be asking to die.

After resting for two days, the long-distance fleet heading toward the Central Galaxy officially gathered.

It was the day of their departure.

The fleet was formed of 3,500 battleships, and the main ships were three mobile satellite bases. Although they were rather bulky, they were also equipped with hyperdrive devices, just not very high-speed ones.

Han Xiao did not produce Eternal Light flagships on a large scale—it would be too flamboyant for him, a Crimson Dynasty ally, to use the Federation of Light's flagship. Han Xiao took it as a secret weapon and built it discreetly, storing it in the hangar. He did not plan to use it publicly for the time being.

Teny and the other dynasty elites had been invited by Han Xiao to take the same battleship.

In the command room, the people at all posts readied and stared at Han Xiao's back, waiting for his order.

Before the enormous porthole, Han Xiao stood side by side with Ames and looked at the sea of stars outside.

The light from the thrusters of the battleships around illuminated their faces.

"Are you sure you want to come with me?"

"It's not like I've never been to the Central Galaxy." Ames smiled. "I'll treat it as sightseeing."

Aesop, who was beside them, caressed the beard on his chin and said, "I can visit my old friends."

Han Xiao nodded. His deep voice then appeared in the communication channel, sounding in every battleship.

"Depart."

Rumble!

The ship shivered slightly and started accelerating, leaving the Black Star Army headquarters.

The fleet had left.

Very soon, the spaceships turned into streams of light and disappeared in the black universe.

When the fleet departed, countless army members were watching from the headquarters satellite.

Following Han Xiao's orders, Sylvia publicized Han Xiao's whereabouts to the entire army. Everyone knew that their army commander had been invited to the Crimson Dynasty and was going to the dynasty's capital to meet its leader.

That's the head of one of the three universal civilizations, the most powerful person in this entire universe!

Countless army members were excited and honored. The army players expressed their shock actively on the forums—Black Star was the first person they knew about to cross servers!

This news piqued the interest of the players of the various Star Fields.

In the past, the Shattered Star Ring had always enjoyed the Black Star Army's benefits alone, causing a lot of envy in the players of the other Star Fields.

Tons of the Black Star Army's deeds were already circulating on the forums. Along with the sensational news that Han Xiao had become a Beyond Grade A, the benefits of the army had already spread to the players of all the Star Fields. Comparatively, the players of the other Star Field realized that the privileges and benefits their own factions gave was not even worth mentioning—no one would refuse to enjoy the army's benefits.

Now, the opportunity to come into contact with the Black Star Army had arrived!

The players of the Central Galaxy were overjoyed. This topic exploded on their forums.

"Is the Black Star Army finally growing beyond its Star Field?"

"Haha, fantastic, we finally have a chance to join the Black Star Army."

"Alas, only if they're coming to the Primeval Star River too."

The Shattered Star Ring players did not think much of it. The stronger the Black Star Army grew, the prouder they would feel. They also felt curious—after the army commander expanded into other Star Fields, would he bring back players from the other Star Fields?

To the current players, crossing Star Fields was way too difficult—they had no right to borrow the Inter-Star Field Stargate and could not afford spaceships that were fast enough. No player had crossed Star Fields for the time being. Furthermore, they had yet to even finish exploring the Star Field they were born in.

The players in the various Star Fields all played on their own and would only meet others on the professional stages and never in any other way.

"What if, since the Black Star Army guided us into the galaxy in Version 2.0, it will also be the faction to guide us to cross Star Fields in the future too?"

"That's actually highly likely. The army has now become an ally of a universal civilization, and its next step will be to explore the Flickering World. It feels like it's opening an inter-Star Field era for us.

There was a lot of speculation on the forums.

At the same time in the Bloodshed Land...

"Black Star has departed?"

"Yes, just."

Heber sat on his throne. His fist supported his face, and he looked straight forward blankly at the palace gate.

As an ally of the Crimson Dynasty, he had been to the Crimson Dynasty long ago, exactly as Han Xiao had been invited.

As if his vision crossed the wide universe, an odd emotion appeared in Heber's eyes as if some of his memories had resurfaced.

"Those guys in the Central Galaxy... are not the friendliest."

On the Crimson Dynasty's mother planet was Tarunamir Palace, the office space for the government affairs of the dynasty. Including the leader of the dynasty, all the core upper echelons dealt with their official duties inside. It was extremely large and could be considered a city on the mother planet.

This was the center of power of the dynasty. It was solemn, serious, and tightly guarded. The government officials that passed each other almost never spoke to each other.

A short person and a tall person walked side by side down a long corridor in Tarunamir Palace. Warm light shone from the windows on the left and painted their shadows on the wall.

The government officials that saw the two of them on the way all showed admiration by standing still and bowing, expressing their respect.

"This gathering is for you guys to meet that new ally."

"I think he's called Black Star?"

"Yes, he's from the Shattered Star Ring, only became a Beyond Grade A recently."

"Oh, a new Beyond Grade A from the Shattered Star Ring. When was the last time a new Beyond Grade A was born there? I can't remember."

"I have forgotten too."

"Isn't that quite tough-skinned Heber from the Shattered Star Ring too. Is he coming this time?"

"Don't think so."

"Sigh, then it's no fun..."

"Who knows? The data shows that this new ally became a Beyond Grade A in the shortest time ever in history. His combat capability is not low, and he fought on par with Psyker and Heber. Furthermore, he has a nickname called 'Indestructible Body'. Although he's a Mechanic, his body is very tough."

"Oh? This sounds fun. I wonder who's more durable to beatings, him or Heber?"

The two of them chatted casually.